Chapter 788: Excellent Era’s Trainees

Chen Yehui grew excited the moment he thought of the idea.

They had previously been using pro gamers like Liu Hao for support. Even though they couldn’t use pro players anymore, they could still use trainees from their training camp. Chen Yehui was confident that so long as the opponents weren’t pros themselves, not many people could contest against them.

The more Chen Yehui thought about the idea, the more reliable the idea felt, but he didn’t dare carry it out carelessly. He would first find manager Cui Li and tell him about the plan.

Cui Li’s eyes brightened when he heard about Chen Yehui’s idea, but he quickly restrained himself and said: "Even if they’re from the training camp, if they’re facing off against Ye Qiu, the distance between their levels might still be too great!"

"At least we can give it a try! If I send my people out, it would be like telling them to lie down and be stepped on! Even though the skills level of the trainees will certainly be below Ye Qiu’s, we might be able to catch them by surprise, no? We only have to win once, and we will gain an upper hand in the topic. The ridicule from the fans would be more than enough, and we don’t have to do anything." Chen Yehui said.

"What if we still lose?" Cui Li asked.

"We’ll be taking accounts from the guild, so even if we lose, someone else can take the responsibility. No one will know that they came from the training camp." Chen Yehui said.

"Well... we can give it a try. Alright, come with me to pick the people." Cui Li said.

Cui Li and Chen Yehui came out of the office and went down two levels to where the base of Team Excellent Era’s training camp was located. The moment they reached the level, the bustling noise of children could be heard. The noise was no different from a school’s classroom.

Although there were quite a lot of children, not all of them were children. There were many that were 17, 18, or even almost 20 years old. People in the training camp included those who were recruited by the club, and those who enrolled themselves. Needless to say, the former would be valued much more by the club. After all, if the club recruited them, it meant that they already had a certain amount of talent; but as for the latter, the club would take them in accordingly. One couldn’t be accepted just by enrolling, their skills would also need to be tested. How could a club’s training camp accept a player who couldn’t tell the 24 classes of Glory apart? They weren’t there to give free education!

Training was divided into four terms:Term One, Term Two, Term Three, and Term Four. At the end of each term, there would be an assessment that decided whether a trainee would get to stay or leave. Those who managed to stay to the end had the potential to be promoted to the team.

The training camp’s arrangements and schedule were diverse. For example, the summer of every year was a break for the pro players, but it was a busy time for the training camp. This was because children of this age group were mostly students. Nothing was more suitable than joining the training camp during their school holidays. Although the same could be said for the winter holidays, Chinese New Year made it less continuous.

The majority of the youths would join the training camp during the summer or winter breaks, while some locals would participate in the training whenever they had time off school. It was extremely rare to have a trainee live in the club building. Putting their actual skill aside, their passion and commitment to the game were worthy of being looked into as potential recruits for the club.

The practice rooms, like the teams, were located on both sides of the floor, but the size was much greater. There were no more than eleven or twelve people in the team, but for the training camp, it was not excessive to have one or two hundred people during the summer holidays. However, not all of the trainees that joined the training camp were sincere in becoming pro players. Quite a few youths that played Glory treated it as a summer camp. This was both amusing and annoying, because the club couldn’t do anything to prevent it. As long as the participants kept it to themselves, who would know their intentions? The club couldn’t do anything about those who never returned after joining for the summer break.

Cui Li and Chen Yehui didn’t halt. They kept walking deeper towards a certain area of the floor. The deeper the trainees lived on the floor, the longer they had been there. When the trainees first saw the two, they were surprised, but curiosity slowly took over. Members who had been a part of the training program for several terms recognized these two important figures in Excellent Era. Especially with Cui Li’s appearance, many trainees, that knew about how the club operated, became excited.

For the manager to appear in the training camp at this time, it was highly probable for him to pick people for the team for next season! Only Xiao Shiqin joined Excellent Era, while three others were transferred away. Even though they were only playing in the Challenger League, if they were cautious, they would still need to add in two people to complete the team.

With Excellent Era’s current circumstances, not many pro players were willing to sacrifice a year to gamble on Excellent Era’s future. Speaking of this, it would have been easy for a top player like Xiao Shiqin to make such a decision. A top player would have to have more self confidence. Firstly, they had to believe that they could help the team get through the Challenger League. Secondly, they had to believe that their efforts wouldn’t make the team discard them after the Challenger League.

If an unsuccessful player from a relatively minor team were summoned by Excellent Era at this time, they wouldn’t be too pleased. Although they would be used by Excellent Era to go through the Challenger League, after returning to the league, would they have any right to stay on the team? After all, this team would aim for the championships, but the player was only a small figure from a small team.

With this sort of realization, it was much easier to recruit a God. This was why it was difficult for Excellence Era to get much out of the transfer market. It was only natural for the club to promote players from the training camp at this time.

People who knew the team’s affairs would have thought about this, which was why they were excited to see Cui Li appear, but they seemed doubtful when they saw it was Chen Yehui whom came with Cui Li.

If they were picking people to join the team, no matter what happened, it should’ve been the team captain who came, not the guild leader.

The trainees were doubtful, but no one dared to ask. The supervisor in charge of the training had received a message in advance, and came out to greet Cui Li and Chen Yehui. After the two revealed their purpose in coming, they waited for the supervisor to recommend someone. Only he knew who had the best skills in the training camp.

"Come with me!" Without giving it much thought, the supervisor seemed to already have someone in mind. He turned and led the two to walk farther in, and finally entered the deepest training room. The supervisor gestured towards a certain seat. "What about him?"

"Him..." Cui Li only needed a glance to immediately recognize him, Chen Yehui also knew about this youth.

Qiu Fei, age 17, class Battle Mage. As a member from the training camp, he was pretty well known. Nearly everyone in Excellent Era knew his name.

This was because Ye Qiu, the previous captain of Excellent Era had thought very highly of him. Everyone knew that this junior might have been viewed as Ye Qiu’s successor, someone who might wield Battle God One Autumn Leaf after Ye Qiu’s retirement and become Excellent Era’s new ace. However, all this became naught after Ye Qiu’s retirement. Qiu Fei was still Qiu Fei, but the club had purchased the new generation’s God Sun Xiang to inherit One Autumn Leaf instead.

Sun Xiang was not much older than Qiu Fei. It would be impossible for Qiu Fei to inherit One Autumn Leaf after Sun Xiang’s retirement. Qiu Fei’s position in Excellent Era became extremely awkward following the purchase.

Everyone knew this, but it was as if this guy didn’t understand at all. He still worked as hard as he used to, practicing his Battle Mage. Due to Cui Li and Chen Yehui’s arrival, the teenagers were a bit distracted. Only Qiu Fei didn’t make any moves and continued to stare at the screen. His left hand on the keyboard and his right hand on the mouse seemed unwilling to let go for even an instant.

He was always like this - he used to be and still was. It was as if he didn’t know of Sun Xiang’s existence on the team, and that it would be difficult for him to stand out as a Battle Mage player. It was not as if he didn’t understand this reasoning. Qiu Fei used to be one of those players who attended the training camp during the break time like a day student. He then transferred to train full time at Excellent Era. So far, it had been a year. If not for Ye Qiu’s departure and Sun Xiang’s arrival, if the succession from senior to junior went smoothly, as Ye Qiu’s appointed successor, he would have been a member of the team in this upcoming season.

"Would he be a bit unsuitable?" Chen Yehui said, and felt unhappy about it. He also knew why he felt in such a way. He was envious.

Chen Yehui was extremely envious of Qiu Fei, because he also used to dream about becoming One Autumn Leaf’s successor, but this dream was shattered by Ye Qiu. The previous captain clearly pointed out that he was unsuitable to become a pro player. As for Qiu Fei, he was always thought of highly by Ye Qiu. When he was in Excellent Era, he never hid his recognition towards Qiu Fei.

Even though that appreciation didn’t seem to make Qiu Fei content or self-satisfied, he became even more diligent. Even so, Chen Yehui felt very sour towards him. After Ye Qiu left and Sun Xiang took up One Autumn Leaf, which meant Qiu Fei would no longer have such an opportunity, Chen Yehui rejoiced at his misfortune.

Of course, he wouldn’t deliberately find Qiu Fei to humiliate him. The envy, jealousy, and hatred that Chen Yehui had against Qiu Fei was hidden inside him. Those two usually wouldn’t be in the same area anyway.

But now that the supervisor was recommending Qiu Fei, Chen Yehui found it to be inappropriate. Qiu Fei had ability, but if one were to tell him to fight Ye Qiu, it would be like telling Su Mucheng to fight Ye Qiu. What would the results be?

"Haha, I know what leader Chen is worried about. Don’t worry, there won’t be a problem." The supervisor of the training camp laughed.

"Oh? What is it?" Cui Li took interest when he heard about it.

The supervisor didn’t reply, he only called out. "Qiu Fei."

Qiu Fei was too focused in training, he didn’t even hear his name being called. It was only until the supervisor called louder while walking towards him, did he turn his head around.

"Come." The supervisor beckoned for Qiu Fei to come.

Qiu Fei’s hands finally left the keyboard and mouse, got up and came over. He saw Cui Li and Chen Yehui, as well as the look of envy of his partners in training, but his expression remained unchanging.

Chapter 789: An Opportunity Bestowed by the Heavens

"Kid, you’re still so spirited!" Cui Li greeted Qiu Fei warmly. He wasn’t like Chen Yehui who had so many private feelings held within him. From a manager’s perspective, a young player, who practiced hard and never demanded anything, was very good.

However, as a professional, he couldn’t do things just because he had a good impression of them. A manager had to think of the team as a whole. For example, the current Excellent Era had God Sun Xiang. It would be very difficult for Cui Li to promote Qiu Fei to the team. If he had to, he could only offer him a position as a substitute player. However, that would be too much of a waste for someone of his talent.

Although Ye Qiu was now their sworn enemy, no one would question Ye Qiu’s skill. Anyone Ye Qiu looked highly upon was someone worth considering. Team Excellent Era’s performance had been in shambles recently. The thoughts of everyone on the team had changed. Even the trainees in the training camp felt like their future was bleak.

When the team was relegated, no changes to the team had been made yet. However, many in the training camp left like rats abandoning a sinking ship. Even under this environment, Qiu Fei not only maintained a positive attitude, but he was still steadily improving. Cui Li wouldn’t follow his progress closely every day, but the training camp had its own supervisor who gave weekly reports on the training camp. Qiu Fei was always mentioned the most.

"I feel like Qiu Fei already possesses the skills to become a pro player." The manager seized the opportunity to give a recommendation to Cui Li.

Cui Li felt a bit unhappy at this recommendation. You could have me this recommendation at any time, but you chose to do it in front of him? No matter how skilled Qiu Fei was, could he be any better than Sun Xiang? Did this supervisor not know the team’s current situation? Qiu Fei was talented, but with Sun Xiang on the team, there was no position for him. Was the Club supposed to create a new dual Battle Mage team composition just for this rookie?　

In Cui Li’s eyes, the supervisor’s recommendation wasn’t at a suitable time. He didn’t have any complaints about Qiu Fei. It was just that Qiu Fei’s situation was too awkward with the team’s current composition. The supervisor should understand this, yet he insisted on raising the topic. Is he trying to give me a hard time?

Cui Li was simply thinking about things from a practical point of view. Chen Yehui carried resentment. When he heard the supervisor’s recommendation, he felt even more unhappy. He obviously couldn’t say any malicious words directly. With Qiu Fei’s conduct at Club Excellent Era, there were no unpleasant things that could be said about him. To oppose it, Chen Yehui shifted the topic from the supervisor’s recommendation to their reason for coming.

"Qiu Fei, do you know about the stuff going on with Ye Qiu right now?" Chen Yehui asked.

As soon as this name came out, Qiu Fei’s eyes jumped. His expression had never changed much, but at this instant, it became complicated.

How could he not be conscious of Ye Qiu’s name? Practically everything he knew about Battle Mages were taught to him personally by Ye Qiu. What type of special honor was that? The team captain and ace player spent the time to personally coach him.

Chen Yehui wasn’t the only one who was jealous of Qiu Fei. A child’s world wasn’t that pure or innocent. Making things difficult for Qiu Fei was a common occurrence.

It was easier to do so in other areas, but embarrassing Qiu Fei in Glory was too too difficult. He was, without a doubt, the most outstanding trainee in the camp.

That was up until Ye Qiu retired and quietly left the club. The trainees in the training camp only heard about this news, when the club officially announced it to the public. At the press conference, the club also announced the addition of Sun Xiang as the successor of One Autumn Leaf. The trainees in the training camp had a decent understanding of how pro teams operated. Let alone the fact that even an ordinary fan could figure out the implications.

At this moment, everyone turned to look at Qiu Fei, because the position of the training camp’s pet favorite instantly became extremely awkward. Some took joy at his misfortune. Some felt sympathy. Others pitied him. The ones who watched in schadenfreude looked forward to Qiu Fei’s downfall.

But who would have thought that not only was Qiu Fei not bothered by it, he worked even harder.

But no matter the case, his position had already changed. From here onwards, he would no longer have the team captain run over to coach him every day. A lot of groundless talk about Qiu Fei flew around. Some mocked him because, no matter how hard he worked, it would all be fruitless in the end. How could he hope to topple Sun Xiang? Some even said slanderous words, blaming Ye Qiu’s decline on him spending too much time on nurturing Qiu Fei.

Qiu Fei quietly endured everything. During this period of time, Excellent Era was under fire too. The team already had too much to handle. Who would care about what was going on with the training camp?

Truthfully, after Cui Li saw Qiu Fei again, his good impression of Qiu Fei popped up again in his mind. During the greater part of the year, he had already forgotten about him. It was only until he met him again did he think about Qiu Fei’s problematic position.

Cui Li was thinking about the situation as a whole. Chen Yehui had already started talking business though: "You probably know about everything that’s happened recently, right?"

Qiu Fei nodded his head. Even though he didn’t usually pay attention to gossip, it had become an extremely hot topic. It was related to Excellent Era too. Even if he didn’t follow it closely, others would talk about it constantly. He knew more about it than what he didn’t.　　

"We’re not really here for much." Chen Yehui was quite evil. His words would strike down any of Qiu Fei’s hopes, telling him not to be mistaken: we aren’t here to ask you to join the team. Unfortunately, Qiu Fei didn’t look as disappointed as Chen Yehui had expected. Helpless, Chen Yehui paused for another three seconds before continuing: "Many players have organized teams to challenge Team Happy, but all of them have failed. So we’re planning on having our trainees take up the challenge. Will that be a problem, Qiu Fei?"

Qiu Fei shook his head. He didn’t say anything more.

"Okay, that’s one then. Is there anyone else you want to recommend?" Chen Yehui asked the supervisor.

The supervisor’s recommendation for Qiu Fei was brought down just like this by Chen Yehui. He could only sigh to himself. It’s not like he didn’t know his place. He knew that his recommendation made Cui Li extremely uncomfortable. He wouldn’t pursue it endlessly.

"There are a few other pretty good ones." The supervisor led Cui Li, Chen Yehui, Qiu Fei around, and called out a few names.

The ones who were called out revealed expressions of joy and rushed over expectantly.　

After hearing the reason, they were sorely disappointed.

Along with Qiu Fei, the supervisor recommended six people to the two seniors. Two of them were a bit older, while the other three were around Qiu Fei’s age.

Afterwards, they left the training camp. Cui Li and the six trainees talked for a bit and went to his office. Chen Yehui then took the six trainees to his game studio.

Chen Yehui wasn’t planning on personally going over to take up the challenge. Even if he went, he wouldn’t be able to see them in real life, so what was the point? After returning to the studio, he gave each of the six trainees account cards according to their respective classes and provided them strong equipment from the guild’s storage.

"Is there a need for this?" The oldest of the six called Li Rui spoke. He would turn 20 years old in September. If he started his career at this age, it would be later than when most pro players started. Even worse, it still didn’t seem like there was hope for him to get promoted. Excellent Era being relegated only made him lose more hope. The Challenger League was too easy. Even if he was promoted as a regular to the team, he might not be able to prove his own strength.

Li Rui had a strong imagination. He often dreamed of being the hero of a team. In the practice room, he often prattled on about being born at the wrong time. He just happened to be there when Excellent Era was in a mess. If not, he claimed that he would have been promoted to the pro team a long time ago and became an official pro player.

Li Rui’s words weren’t completely without reason. His skill level was quite high. For many people, he was skilled enough, but he just lacked the opportunity to do so. Li Rui had the same thoughts. He felt like he just lacked the opportunity, and the current Excellent Era couldn’t provide him this opportunity. He already had thoughts of looking for other teams to try to join, but now, Cui Li and Chen Yehui suddenly showed up at the training camp looking for people to play a match. The others seemed disappointed, but Li Rui was excited.　　

Recently, nothing attracted more attention than this event. Did these guys fail to see that if they could beat Happy right now, they would have a chance to shine?　

Especially since Happy wasn’t some sort of powerhouse. They were just an Internet cafe team. Of course they could bully some regular players, but they were up and coming pro players trained by a club. Wouldn’t dealing with these guys be like taking candy from a baby? It was perfect that their opponents were weak and the interest was high. Wasn’t this an opportunity bestowed by the heavens?

Li Rui didn’t want those guys to notice this opportunity, but he was also afraid that they wouldn’t take this seriously and hold him back. In the end, he tugged at their ears and analyzed it for them.

When those guys listened, their spirits also rose. Getting attention from the public was exactly what these trainees wanted the most. Quite a few had extraordinary skill, but their team had no place for them. If they tried looking for other teams to go to, they were completely unknown. It was hard to be accepted by them. After all, despite being unordinary, if they couldn’t get a spot, they weren’t future Gods. If not, their club would have put them out onto the market if there was no spot for them in their team.

"Play well!" Li Rui told everyone, except for Qiu Fei.

Chapter 790: Narrow Minded

Qiu Fei was in an awkward position. Li Rui was definitely among one of the few who took joy at his misfortune. He never accepted the attention Qiu Fei received and frequently complained about it with his friends. Even in this situation, Qiu Fei still practiced hard. To Li Rui, that was an act of pure stupidity.

If he wanted to show off, he should have switched teams. There was no position for you in Excellent Era. Even if your diligence moved the team and they decided to promote you, you would be Sun Xiang’s substitute at best. Are you really willing to just be a sub?

But be that as it may, Li Rui also knew that for trainees, finding a new path wasn’t so easy. If a trainee switched teams and started practicing from the new team’s training camp, it was hard to say if you could even be promoted. Every team had their own hierarchy. A fierce dragon crossing the river to snatch away other people’s opportunities would never be liked by others. It might just be a waste of time. It was because of this reason that the rather conceited Li Rui stayed in Excellent Era’s training camp. He kept on hesitating and could never make up his mind.

Opportunity! I just need an opportunity!

Li Rui held onto this belief. Now that an opportunity had come, he needed to properly seize it. As for Qiu Fei, Li Rui couldn’t help but concede that he was a formidable competitor. If Qiu Fei couldn’t see this opportunity, that would be perfect, but that wasn’t too likely. Someone who went all out even during practice wouldn’t relax for even a moment.　

What is this guy thinking now?

Li Rui observed Qiu Fei the entire way, but he didn’t see anything out of the ordinary. However, he was only concerned about the issue of the opportunity. When he saw Chen Yehui give them the best possible equipment he could find, Li Rui couldn’t help but speak out.　　

The equipment on Team Happy’s characters weren’t considered to be too amazing in game, let alone for in a pro team. All of this had been discovered long ago by the players who had fought against Team Happy. Li Rui was thinking about the future. If he used superior equipment and beat the opponent, it would be a blemish on the victory. He hoped that when he won, everyone would see that it was because the player was more skilled, not the character being stronger.

"It’s best not to be careless." Chen Yehui heard Li Rui’s words and chuckled, "Those guys aren’t as bad as you think they are. Senior Ye Qiu is there too. I know that you guys are outstanding, but I’m sure you guys have noticed that Team Happy’s arrogance isn’t without reason. They haven’t lost a single time yet, even if those victories were against in-game players. Isn’t that still telling of their strength? That’s why we should do what we can, whether that’s you or your character."

The others nodded their head in reply. Qiu Fei didn’t say anything. Only Li Rui objected. He sneered: "If they can’t even keep up that win rate, creating such a commotion would be nothing but a joke."

"In short, let’s do everything we can!" Chen Yehui said. He continued to equip these characters with the best pieces of equipment from the guild storage. At the same time, he asked each of them what type of equipment they preferred. He finished equipping each character one by one and then handed out each account card according to their respective classes. The only two left who hadn’t received account cards were Qiu Fei and Li Rui. They were both Battle Mages. With so many people in the training camp, let alone two people using the same class, it wasn’t anything strange if there were eight or ten. Even more so, as a Battle Mage in a team that used a Battle Mage as a core.

If the training camp supervisor didn’t need to consider that he would need to choose six trainees to participate in a team competition, he would have recommended even more Battle Mages.

Chen Yehui was also a Battle Mage player, so he was very familiar with the class. He had undergone professional training before, so he was actually quite skilled. As a result, he was naturally adept at picking Battle Mage equipment. When he picked out the equipment, he told the two of them: "If there’s anything that doesn’t suit you, just tell me!"

At their skill level, every player had a preference towards their character’s stat and skill distribution. For example, some liked to jump higher. Other liked to run faster. Chen Yehui first picked out the strongest equipment. The details would be adjusted according to their desires.　

Neither of them said anything though.

Qiu Fei’s expression never changed. As for Li Rui? He had said that "better equipment wasn’t necessary". If he was picky about his equipment right now, wouldn’t he be slapping his own face?

Chen Yehui quickly finished one Battle Mage. The people behind him were silent. Chen Yehui didn’t ask any further questions. Afterwards, he logged out of the game and turned around to hand over the account card, but he wasn’t sure who to give it to. In the end, he asked: "Who wants this one?"

Qiu Fei and Li Rui exchanged glances. Qiu Fei extended his hand and grabbed the account card.

Chen Yehui quickly equipped another Battle Mage. Even though Excellent Dynasty had an enormous guild storage, they didn’t have a large number of every piece of equipment, especially for Battle Mages, which was the most popular class in their guild. Equipment could be exchanged for contribution points by guild members, so there was never enough Battle Mage equipment. After choosing the best equipment for one Battle Mage, the other Battle Mage didn’t have the same options.　

Chen Yehui finished the other one and gave it to Li Rui: "This one is a bit worse, but it’s not like you care, right?"

Chen Yehui’s remark was somewhat caustic. Chen Yehui may be jealous of Qiu Fei, but it’s not like he had a good opinion of Li Rui either. Li Rui was just some trainee. Chen Yehui regarded his behavior disdainfully.

Li Rui didn’t mind the remark. His Battle Mage was slightly worse than Qiu Fei’s. Normally, he would be unwilling to accept it, but today, he needed to seize this opportunity to attract attention to himself. His character being inferior a bonus point for him. If the two fought at around the same level, others would say: "And Li Rui’s equipment isn’t as good!" Wouldn’t that make it seem like his skill level was higher?

When Li Rui took the account card, he was already imagining this scene. Chen Yehui gave him the card and then stood up to say to everyone: "Okay, everyone find a seat and get used to your character. I’ll be arranging the match with Team Happy. I’ll notify everyone when the time comes."

Everyone nodded their heads. They went into the game studio, found a seat, and started familiarizing themselves with their character. Chen Yehui also logged into the game. A match with Team Happy would require a reservation, but Chen Yehui didn’t want to reveal his identity as part of Excellent Dynasty. He understood the situation very well. It didn’t matter who beat Happy. As long as they could do so, it would be a fierce blow to the other side. When that time came, there would naturally be many who would argue noisily: if you can’t even beat some randoms, how could you think about challenging Excellent Era? If he went int as Excellent Dynasty, he could make the waves rise even higher. However, Chen Yehui was too afraid.　　

Ye Qiu might not be in the official team lineup, but in an online match, who knew if Ye Qiu would be there or not? If Ye Qiu participated, the trainees wouldn’t be good enough. He just hoped that Ye Qiu wouldn’t be too shameless and play in the individual competition and group arena. Thinking about this possibility, Chen Yehui placed his hopes on the team competition. No matter how capable Ye Qiu was, he couldn’t control five characters at once. There would definitely be people dragging him down. No matter how strong an individual was, the team competition required coordination to win. For example, in Samsara, it may seem as if Zhou Zekai alone decided the outcome in Team Samsara, but if you had him play with four random normal players, that team would get smashed.

In any case, Chen Yehui wasn’t completely confident because of the existence of Ye Qiu. As a result, he decided not to appear on stage using Excellent Dynasty’s name and went in as random group. If they won, they could brag about it. If they lost, they could just leave it alone and let the loss fade away into nothingness!

After making his decision, Chen Yehui logged into the game and contacted Happy. Right now, almost no one went over directly to Happy Internet Cafe to request a match anymore. The experts in City H had either already been slaughtered by Team Happy or felt like it was better not to humiliate themselves. Most of the requests for a match were done online through contacting a character called Chasing Haze.

Chen Yehui obviously used an alternate account, so he wouldn’t be exposed as someone from Excellent Dynasty. He tried adding Chasing Haze as a friend with the message: Challenge.

Chen Yehui’s luck was quite good. If this had been a few days earlier, Chen Guo’s message list had been like a flood. Every day, she would ignore quite a few messages. Online, there were even more face slappers. Happy couldn’t respond to them all.

But as more and more experts fell, more and more people had an estimate of Team Happy’s strength, and fewer and fewer experts challenged them. Chen Yehui’s request for a match was quickly accepted by Chen Guo.

"Individual or group?" Chen Guo replied through the friend request.

"Let’s go by the official competition rules!" Chen Yehui said.

Chen Guo smiled. These days, many of the experts asked for the match to be played according to the official competition rules, but after playing to the group arena, these experts didn’t know what to do anymore. The individual competition and group arena was more than enough for them to see the difference in skill. Their losses were so ugly that they no longer had the courage to try a team competition. Very few challengers were able to finish their way through the entire match. Now another player had asked for the match to be played in this way. How long would he last?

"What time?" Chen Guo asked the opponent.

"At night." Chen Yehui replied. Their side had gathered together already, but they needed to familiarize themselves with their characters. Even more so, he reckoned that the other side wouldn’t agree if they asked to fight immediately. Team Happy always fought at around the same time in the same Arena room. When it was about time, spectators would rush to that room. Team Happy was undoubtedly gathering attention on purpose. If Chen Yehui requested for a private match, the other side had no reason to agree! It’d be better not to act childishly and just follow the normal procedure.

"Okay." Chen Guo obviously had no issues with it. She replied back and told Chen Yehui the room number. It was the same one that was always used. Over all these days, the room had never left Happy’s hands.

Chapter 791: Pressure

Evening fell.

With the name Team Happy, room 28529 in the Arena was undoubtedly the most popular room these days. Or perhaps you could say, since the launch of Glory,, there had never been an Arena room that had maintained such popularity over a long period of time.

Tonight was no different. Starting from six o’clock at night, players scrambled to the room. No one sat in the seat for competitors. Everyone ensured that they sat as a spectator.

Would anyone challenge Team Happy tonight?

The spectators guessed. Ever since talk of Team Happy exploded, numerous experts challenged them. During that period of time, there would be plenty of matches to see every night. Some of these experts came to embarrass Team Happy. Others came purely out of curiosity and just wanted to have some fun.

Team Happy had yet to lose. Not even once.

But Team Happy’s line up was certainly strange. The vast majority of matches were won by the Battle Mage, Soft Mist. In the individual competition, she always appeared first. In the group arena, she also always appeared first.

In the eyes of the players, this Soft Mist was terrifyingly skilled. Rumors of Soft Mist being Ye Qiu spread. Many were suspecting that Ye Qiu was controlling this character from behind the screen. These were just guesses from normal players. The pro players paying attention to this commotion could tell that this Battle Mage was different from Ye Qiu’s Battle Mage. Especially Excellent Era. After learning about Lord Grim not being Ye Qiu, they wanted to find some way to prove that Ye Qiu was definitely at Happy. However, from the material gained through the matches played recently, they also felt that Soft Mist wasn’t Ye Qiu.

It was hard to say though. After all, the challengers were merely random in-game level players. For God Ye Qiu, he didn’t need to go all out to crush them. He could fool around and win. From the perspective of people like Chen Yehui, who would think about Ye Qiu from the worst point of view possible, they were convinced that Ye Qiu was deliberately making things confusing.

If Soft Mist wasn’t being played by Ye Qiu, then who else? This was one of the countless questions posed when talking about Team Happy.

At 7 o’clock sharp. Soft Mist appeared and sat a a competitor seat.

As for her opponent? Would there be an opponent today?

The spectators waited anxiously. Less and less opponents were coming. Last night, the first challenger appeared at eight o’clock and then lost without any suspense.

At this point, the players could tell that Team Happy was truly a strong team. It looked like normal players wouldn’t be able to stop them. With their skill level, maybe they could actually make it into the pro scene?

This was also talked about. From the start, everyone thought Team Happy was being too arrogant, but now they started having different thoughts. Most of the spectators wanted to see Team Happy lose, but many were also thinking when they would lose. These two schools of thought sounded similar, but the slight difference between them indicated that quite a few people were starting to lean towards Team Happy’s side.

Team Happy’s marketing campaign had some results. Chen Guo’s risky move paid off.

"It’s time!"

At Club Excellent Era’s game studio, after Tang Rou’s Soft Mist appeared in the room, Chen Yehui immediately called out to everyone. He had been waiting among the spectators long ago. Today’s matches would obviously need to be recorded.

‘Who’s going first?" Chen Yehui asked.

"I’ll go!" Li Rui smiled, rushing to be first.

Chen Yehui nodded his head. He didn’t care who came up first. He didn’t forget to say a few words. "Be careful. This person has stood out the most in the team. I think that might be Ye Qiu playing." Chen Yehui warned solemnly.　

"Ye Qiu?" Li Rui sneered. He wasn’t looking down on Ye Qiu’s skill, but rather Chen Yehui’s eyes.

"She isn’t him." Li Rui remarked bluntly. It didn’t sound like he was opposing Ye Qiu, but completely denying Chen Yehui’s suspicion was not giving him face.

Chen Yehui was furious in his heart. He started feeling conflicted. He was even slightly hoping that Li Rui would lose to show him his place. He’s just a trainee from the training camp. If he one day became an ace player of a team, was he going to use his nose to talk to him?

Li Rui ignored Chen Yehui’s feelings. He logged onto his character and entered the room in the Arena. Soft Mist standing out the most was something he obviously knew of. He had pursued this topic quite a bit. It was precisely because of this that he was eager to be first. If he could strike her down, he would certainly receive the most attention. Li Rui couldn’t miss such an opportunity.

Demon Fighter.

This was the name of Li Rui’s Battle Mage. He quickly entered the room and appeared in the competitor seat. Soft Mist was across from him.

"Demon Fighter. Is that one of yours?" Chen Yehui received a message from Chen Guo on his alternate.

"Yes." Chen Yehui replied.

Once Chen Guo confirmed it, she said to Tang Rou: "This is the one. Go for it!"

Soft Mist pressed ready. Demon Fighter pressed ready. The match began.

Tang Rou’s aggressiveness didn’t need to be said. Once the countdown ended, Soft Mist rushed towards her opponent. Just like before, Tang Rou often started with Dragon Breaks the Ranks. However, after so many days, the challengers were becoming more and more skilled, so Tang Rou wouldn’t use this kind of unreliable initiation. In fact, against experts, it would certainly put her at a disadvantage.

Soft Mist steadily approached and initiated with Dragon Tooth. Demon Fighter had not moved yet as if he were very calm.

In reality, Li Rui was very nervous.

Yes, nervous. He hadn’t thought that once the match began, he would become nervous.

The outcome of this match was very important. He regarded it as a turning point in his career, so he kept reminding himself that he absolutely could not fail. As a result, when the match came, he became nervous. He had given himself too much pressure. Only victory, no defeat.Very few could endure that kind of pressure.　　

Li Rui felt like he could hear his heart thump. His two legs underneath the table uncontrollably trembled and this trembling was spreading. If it spread to his two hands, it would be over…..

The more he thought about it the more he couldn’t control himself. Li Rui discovered that his two hands had actually started shaking.

How shameful!

Li Rui thought. He looked left and right. Fortunately, the others were focused on their screens, watching the match. None of them saw his two hands shaking, easing some of the pressure off him. The trembling in his two hands seemed to have lessened as well.

But while he was distracted, Soft Mist had closed in on Demon Fighter and stabbed at him with Dragon Tooth. Demon Fighter did not react and was hit.

Dragon Tooth induced a brief stun effect. For Dragon Tooth, the stun was more valuable than the damage it dealt.

How to follow up after the stun was a basic skill for Battle Mages.

Tang Rou used it very well. When she started with Dragon Tooth, she didn’t think it would be so easy to land the hit. She followed with Sky Strike, knocking Demon Fighter into the air. The magic chasers generated by Dragon Tooth and Sky Strike flew at their target and exploded. Soft Mist’s next attacks arrived…...　

Li Rui turned his head back at this moment and saw his character tumbling in the air. Two chasers struck him. Li Rui, who had just eased up a little bit, suddenly became nervous again. His brain seemed to have stopped working all of a sudden. His mind blanked. He forgot what to do in this situation. His left hand hovered over his keyboard and his right hand gripped his mouse. He wanted to move them, but they refused to listen to his instructions. He didn’t know how he could get them to move again.

Sot Mist continued with her combo. Finally, she landed a Falling Flower Palm on Demon Fighter, pushing him away, and fired a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Her spear melded with magic, transforming into a dragon. Before Demon Fighter could hit the ground, he was devoured by the dragon. The crowd let out gasps of surprise.

Hitting an airborne target with Rising Dragon Soars the Sky wasn’t as easy as it sounded, even more so when chasing after a target that had been blown away by Falling Flower Palm. The inputs had to be very quick. If not, there wouldn’t be enough time. Soft Mist being able to strike a blown away target with Rising Dragon Soars the Sky was proof of her hand speed. Without a fast enough hand speed, this play would not have worked.

As for Demon Fighter, did anyone care about him? He just stood there and took the Dragon Tooth. After being launched into the air by Sky Strike, everyone focused on Soft Mist’s relentless combo. For normal players, this type of combo seemed perfect and inescapable.

But for Li Rui, that shouldn’t be the case. Unfortunately, his mind blanked out. Everything he had learned instantly disappeared. He was like a spectator, watching as his character was pummeled in the air. After a direct hit from Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, Demon Fighter’s health had gone down by a third.

A single combo for a third of his health. For a pro level fight, it was disgusting. There was no such thing as an inescapable combo. It all depended on whether you could find an opportunity to escape.

When Li Rui had turned his head, no one had been paying attention to him. But now after losing a third of his health in one go, everyone turned their heads.

It was too outrageous.

A trainee from the training camp might not be an official pro player yet, but they were at a pro level. To be comboed in such a way, what was he doing? Was he doing it on purpose?

From their understanding of Li Rui, they all thought of this possibility.

Chapter 792: Thinking Too Much

Faking carelessness and losing health before suddenly pulling himself together to defeat his opponent in one go. If one gave it more thought, this kind of thing fit with Li Rui’s personality. This must have been deliberate.

That’s what Li Rui’s companions believed. They would never have thought that the prideful Li Rui they usually knew, the Li Rui that gave little care for his opponents, would be nervous to the point that his mind had turned blank. He didn’t deliberately lose his health, he didn’t even have time to think about it. After the countdown from three, two, and one for the match, he was carried away.

Li Rui’s companions completely misunderstood him, so none of them were worried about him. Instead, they patiently waited for Li Rui to show his might. In the match, Soft Mist’s wave of attacks came again.

This time, Li Rui wasn’t lost in thought, he hastily made his response. However, his fingers were frozen, and refused to listen to his command. This situation looked terrible, if he didn’t do anything, then he would suffer a chain of attacks from Tang Rou. If they were evenly matched, then both sides would repeatedly be exchanging their skills to test each other. Until now, Li Rui could make responses, but they weren’t good. As a result, he fought in a strained manner.

"Is he still pretending?" Li Rui’s companions discussed as they messaged each other.

"He’s pretty good at faking."

"Hehe, exactly, as if he really is struggling.""When he breaks out later, the opponent will definitely be mind-blown!"

"Too bad we can’t see his opponent’s expression!"

"Yeah, what a pity. But Li Rui is really despicable."

"Of course, too despicable! He’s evil from heaven to hell!"

The two friends talked back and forth, while while watching Li Rui "fake" his flustered composure.

"It’s about time for him to make his move!" Some replied. "Mhm, about time."

"Hehe." The two sent the drooling emoji to each other. But after numerous movements, Demon Fighter lost another chunk of health.

"He’s still not making his move, he can really hold it in!"

"He must be planning to make a complete and grand comeback! He really has the guts!"

"Yeah, he’s too confident, tsk tsk!"

The two sighed repeatedly, and continued to watch Demon Fighter’s health go down. "His health bar has turned red, he will definitely be making his move. He even waited for his health bar to go red, how ruthless." Someone said.

"Indeed, I can’t help but to feel worried for him." Another said.

Half a minute later.

"Say, perhaps we should really be worried for him."

"What’s up with him? Something’s not right!!"

After Demon Fighter’s health bar turned red, they still failed to see Li Rui break out. All they saw, was him struggling and the health bar of Demon Fighter continue to fall. The two no longer continued to watch the match. They turned their head to see Li Rui. Li Rui’s face was a bit pale. Even though the temperature at the end of August was still a little hot, the workshop’s strong air conditioner continued to operate, so the workshop was chilly. But Li Rui’s head was covered with thin beads of sweat. The wind was cool, so was his sweat. Finally, the word "Glory" shone on the screen. Li Rui stared dumbly with a paralysed face. Everyone gazed at one another, speechless.

It’s alright to lose! But what happened just then? He lost in such an unsightly manner! Was there any difference between him and those experts online that were bullied?

The people from Excellent Era were in shock. But the audience had no idea that Demon Fighter was a hidden pro. For them, this match was no different from the previous days they had crowded around to see. Before Soft Mist, all the players were abused like this. It seemed like this Demon Fighter was pretty good! He managed to hang on for so long. Perhaps, his future might be promising with more practice?

A rough start!

Chen Yehui sighed. But it wasn’t him who had lost, so his mood wasn’t too bad. Instead of going up to give comfort, his eyes gazed at Li Rui disdainfully. That’s what you get for pretending!

"Do I need to switch players?" Soft Mist asked from the Arena room.

According to the standard competition rules, three people would need to come forth for individual matches. One person for each match. Soft Mist would need to switch with another player after one match, but the people who challenged her might not be in a team, so they didn’t need to follow the standard competition rules. Tang Rou would be facing the challengers by herself. Only fighting one match wouldn’t be enough for her. So even though Chen Guo said that they would be fighting according to the competition rules, she still asked.

In the Excellent Era workshop, Li Rui suddenly jumped up and rushed before Qiu Fei with impatience. "Lend me your account."

"Mm?" Qiu Fei was puzzled, he was already logged into the game, so he could watch the match! When Liu Rui suddenly ran over for his account, Qiu Fei didn't understand what he meant. On the contrary, Chen Yehui used to be in the training camp and currently managed the guild, so he was someone who had connections in both the online circle and professional circle. As a result, it was easy to guess what Li Rui was thinking.

This guy must have wanted to gain publicity through a match that drew a lot of attention. Who would have thought that he would lose in such an unsightly manner. But he refused to give up and still wanted to grab onto this opportunity. It wouldn’t have been enough if he used the same account to win back something he lost. Luckily he was online, so no one would know who was behind Demon Fighter. This guy just wanted to switch characters and win, so he can speak about this victory as a pretense.

"Lend it to me to try again." Li Rui asked Qiu Fei without explanation.

It was unknown if Qiu Fei thought about it. He only glanced at Li Rui again. Qiu Fei didn’t hand Li Rui his account, but he got up to give him his seat.

"Thank you." Li Rui said and sat down hurriedly, while he shouted at Chen Yehui that he would "Try another round". He didn’t care about Chen Yehui’s respond as he had already switched to Qiu Fei’s character and rushed into the arena. "No need to change. Come!" A text bubble popped above his character’s head.

"Didn’t they say they would follow the competition rules?" Chen Guo found it hard to understand.

"It doesn’t matter." Tang Rou said.

"You must be more than happy to fight. Of course it doesn’t matter." Chen Guo said helplessly.

Tang Rou smiled and entered the match without minding at all. "Don’t be careless with the previous guy, he was actually quite good. He just performed badly." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh? Is that so?" Chen Guo wasn’t able to tell at all.

"Mm, he showed a glimmer of it, but he just played badly." Ye Xiu said.

"Why so?" Chen Guo asked.

"Within our circle, this type of circumstance is called performing poorly." Ye Xiu said.

"..." Chen Guo was speechless. "Performing poorly" could be used to explain all sorts of things. All reasons could be summed up with "performing poorly", but there was nothing wrong with saying that.

"Mm." Tang Rou answered as he listened to Ye Xiu’s words. She never underestimated her opponent. The opponent before her was called Silent Night, and was another Battle Mage

After experiencing nervousness to the point of going blank in the first round, Li Rui finally adjusted his mindset. He breathed deeply, and after the countdown, he immediately made his move.

This was a match that couldn’t be lost, but now that Li Rui finished adjusting his mind-set, his mind was no longer completely blank. He prepared to take her down with his full power, so he took the initiative to launch his attack when the match started. The two Battle Mages clashed together in the center. The two spears danced together. A hoarse, clashing noise sounded from time to time. Attacking and blocking were something that players loved to watch. Clashes between weapons would make the competition seem more intense.

This round, they were truly evenly matched.

The onlookers continued to watch, and their mood gradually rose. This was the scene that they have been waiting for! Even if, from what they have seen so far, the opponent was even at best, but the previous opponents of Soft Mist have only been oppressed, tossed, and turned. Now that there was finally an expert who could get out a fight. It was enough to raise everyone’s spirits.

The faceslapping group that had been silent for a long time started to liven up. A large number of cheering messages started to flood into the chat. The two that were fighting could see it. Li Rui saw that the competition drew a lot of attention, and now that he fight normally, he managed to bring hope to many! Win, I must win. If I win, I would become the hero of these people. They would spread news of this victory without me needing to do anything. If my identity is revealed, everyone’s attention will be focused onto me. Who knows, maybe fans might even block the club door to ask Excellent Era to make me an actual player!

But signing a contract with Excellent Era isn’t perfect! We’re only fighting in the Challenger League this season, and One Autumn Leaf is controlled by Sun Xiang. I have no chance at all! Speaking of age, I’m even older than Sun Xiang!

But if I don’t go to Excellent Era, this match’s victory wouldn’t draw the attention of other teams. I would only become a hero for the fans of Excellent Era for slapping Happy’s face. Fans from other teams are just there for fun. I might become well known, but it’s hard to say if my presented skills would be favoured by other teams!

Or maybe, that team would sign a contract with a well known player like me to bring attention to the team themselves? Mm, it’s not impossible, but the teams that would do this wouldn’t be a top team. It might even be the two teams that joined in this year. That Heavenly Swords is very rich. A rich team’s prospects would be pretty good, wouldn’t it? Moreover, the conditions they could offer me must be very generous. This player seemed pretty good. When Li Rui thought such, he thought too much. He suddenly realised that, this time, he could almost picture it before his eyes. Yes, he pictured it, but the match that he expected to happen didn’t appear.

Li Rui was alarmed, his mind had been distracted. Have I been playing subconsciously the whole time? When Li Rui regained his focus and saw the match. F*ck, I’m in the air.

But this time, Li Rui’s mind wasn’t blank, he quickly rescued himself from the airborne situation. However, he was stunned once again, when the word ‘Glory’ shone on the screen.

Silent Night, the character he lent from Qiu Fei, had fallen.

Chapter 793: A Player Switch

Li Rui lost again!

The studio fell silent. Everyone seemed to be staring at their own screens, but they couldn’t help but sneak a glance at Li Rui.

Li Rui’s expression was even uglier than before. His heart was filled with resentment, but he could not help but admit that his opponent was not as simple as he had anticipated. Anyone with a bit of skill could see that. Someone without any skill could still tell from the final health points on each character.

When Li Rui’s Silent Night fell, Soft Mist had hit red blood. She had less than ten percent of her health left.

These two players were roughly evenly matched. Who won or lost each confrontation wouldn’t be a surprising result. It just depended on who performed better at that time.

Li Rui had originally been playing well, but unfortunately, he was thinking about too many things. Mid-match, he saw everyone cheering his name and his train of thought flew too far. If he couldn’t focus, how could he hope to beat an equally skilled opponent? Li Rui understood this point, so the regret in his heart couldn’t easily be described with words. He stood up fiercely and stepped towards Chen Yehui. His face was red with embarrassment: "Give me another Battle Mage!"

Of course he would be embarrassed. He lost two matches and exchanged two accounts. Now he was asking for a third. He knew that his thoughts had been seen through, but in order to prove himself and seize this perfect opportunity, the ambitious Li Rui had to throw aside his dignity. He had seen the cheers and support from the fans earlier. If he could beat Soft Mist, he would certainly win a substantial amount of attention.

Chen Yehui’s heart was filled with disdain towards Li Rui, but he couldn’t show it on his face. He was just about to laugh out loud, when he saw the screen. He smiled: "Wait first. Qiu Fei is already up."　　

Li Rui was surprised. He checked his screen. Sure enough, Qiu Fei had taken Demon Fighter and stood at the competitor seat.　　

"Why is it this guy again?" The spectators didn’t know that this account was being exchanged back and forth. Seeing the loser Demon Fighter jump out again, they were both puzzled and scornful. To the spectators, this Demon Fighter was overestimating his own abilities.

Why was Demon Fight being looked at with contempt? Wasn’t it because Li Rui fought in such a disgusting manner? When Li Rui saw the public opinion towards Demon Fighter, his face burned white-hot. Aren’t they talking about me? Right now, Qiu Fei had taken Demon Fighter and was being criticized for it. Li Rui turned his head to take a look at him. Qiu Fei, who had his character standing on the competitor seat, acted the same as during practice. Qiu Fei sat upright in his chair. His eyes were focused only on the screen. His left hand rested on the keyboard and his right hand gripped his mouse tightly as if it would never let go.

"Watch Qiu Fei first and then we’ll see." Chen Yehui said plainly and ignored Li Rui. Even though he didn’t like Qiu Fei, he couldn’t bear Li Rui’s cockiness. He was looking forward to seeing Qiu Fei give Li Rui a slap to the face.

Tang Rou didn’t refuse the match. She didn’t care if that Demon Fighter returned. Chen Guo was furious though. Didn’t they say that the match would be played according to the official competition ruleset? It’s fine if we don’t need to switch out if we win, but when could you ever try again after losing?

Chen Guo despised how unreasonable the opponents were being, but it wasn’t reason enough to argue. The purpose of this exhibition wasn’t to follow the official competition rules.

The two Battle Mages were sent to the field. After the countdown, another match began.

Tang Rou’s victory over Li Rui had not been easy. The exhaustion felt from battling against an evenly-matched opponent could not compare to the exhaustion felt from bullying normal players. Even so, when the match began, Tang Rou was the first to act.

Her opening move was the same as the previous match. As soon as she found the perfect distance, she sent over a Dragon Tooth.

This time, Demon Fighter did not wait foolishly to be hit. When the Dragon Tooth came, he stepped slightly to the side, just barely dodging it. At the same time, his spear stabbed back with Dragon Tooth.

Soft Mist turned her body to avoid the attack. She switched up her offense and her spear swept in a horizontal arc: Tyrant’s Destruction!　　

Demon Fighter did not change skills. He seemed to insist on using Dragon Tooth, but his body had started moving according to the direction of Tyrant’s Destruction.

A character’s movement speed couldn’t compare to the speed of a weapon. Even if Demon Fighter rotated, he would still be hit by Tyrant’s Destruction. However, just this slight movement was able to win him just enough time for Dragon Tooth to hit.

This tiny time difference was too subtle. Spectators who weren’t matching the fight closely might not even have noticed Demon Fighter’s slight rotation. Only true experts would know that without this rotation, Demon Fighter would not have gotten this result.

Dragon Tooth, hit!

The brief stun interrupted Soft Mist’s Tyrant’s Destruction. Although Dragon Tooth was a low-level skill, it was very useful. How could Qiu Fei not be proficient at utilizing the brief stun induced by Dragon Tooth? He flicked his mouse and followed up with Tyrant’s Destruction, Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm, and various Chasers. He weaved low-level skills with high-level skills, following a standard flowchart for his combo. In an instant, Soft Mist was completely suppressed.

This time, the spectators were dumbstruck. How did Soft Mist suddenly end up in this state? In the first match, Soft Mist’s fight with Silent Night hadn’t even been this dominant.

No, not just Silent Night. Everyone had come to this room to watch the PvP exhibition every day and had never seen Soft Mist be at such a disadvantage. Demon Fighter had created history. But the problem was that everyone’s memory of his sluggishness was still fresh in their minds. How did he suddenly become so incredible?

The spectator chat suddenly stopped moving. The players didn’t know what to say.

Tang Rou wasn’t like Li Rui, whose brain crashed and died in one combo. In the midst of the combo pressure, she quickly found an opportunity to escape and pulled the match back to the starting point. But from their health bars, she was already on the losing side. For the spectators, this was unprecedented. After a long pause, someone finally typed: "A player switch?"

Such a dramatic difference made the crowd think of this possibility, which happened to be the truth. But the truth behind the truth was that Li Rui’s Demon Fighter shouldn’t have lost in such an ugly fashion. If he had found an opportunity, he would have also been able to snatch the first glory and combo Soft Mist. Unfortunately, he played so sluggishly that even he wanted to switch accounts to pretend he was a new player.

Qiu Fei didn’t care at all. He took the considered stupid character and gave everyone a shock. The halo of stupidity left by Li Rui didn’t affect him at all. He was the expert in the crowd’s eyes. They would not mistake him for that idiot from before.

Li Rui naturally felt embarrassed. As he sat foolishly at his seat, his face changed from red to white. The opportunity that he had been waiting for was going to be taken by Qiu Fei? After the spectators recovered from their shock, they had begun cheering for Qiu Fei. This time, Qiu Fei’s Demon Fighter held the advantage. The crowd’s excitement and cheers for Qiu Fei were naturally more intense than when Li Rui used Silent Night.

Li Rui tightened his fist. His fingers dug into his hand, but he didn’t feel pain, only jealousy and resentment. Why did he fail to grab at that opportunity? Why did Qiu Fei take it instead?

If Qiu Fei took this match, it would break Team Happy’s perfect win streak. Li Rui knew very well what type of attention such an outcome would bring. If not, he wouldn’t have cared to go first. Unfortunately, his dreamed moment was gradually floating farther away!

Lose! Why aren’t you losing! If you lose, this chance will still be mine!　　

Li Rui became a supporter of Happy. He wanted to see Happy win this fight more than anyone else. He prayed for Soft Mist to suddenly gain momentum and for Qiu Fei to make a mistake.

Reality failed to meet his prayers.

Qiu Fei fought steadily. He didn’t relax because of his advantage nor did he underestimate his opponent for being from an Internet cafe team. He didn’t think about the future like Li Rui had. In his eyes, this was a match. The purpose of a match was to beat his opponent and win, nothing more.　　

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

The two Battle Mages actually chose to use the same move. The two spears whistled through the air and clashed. It looked as if they came out at the same time.

That was just for normal players though. For skilled players, they could see that Soft Mist had started up the skill earlier! That was a contest of hand speed. 　　

In that instant, Li Rui felt overjoyed. This Soft Mist was really tenacious. If this strike hit, the tides might shift. By riding on this momentum, she could gain a lead.

"Beautiful!" Li Rui couldn’t control himself because he was waiting for this moment to happen. It was only after he shouted it out did he realize that his words were inappropriate. Even if he didn’t Qiu Fei, it wasn’t a suitable time. It was a problem with his integrity!

But who would have thought that at this moment, the one to be hit by Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart was actually Soft Mist. Both players saw the same opportunity, but the one to seize it was Qiu Fei. 　　

Li Rui, who let out a slip of the tongue, was stunned, but the others were all looking at him with admiration. He couldn’t help but blush with shame. He knew everyone had misunderstood. They probably also thought that Soft Mist would win the exchange. However, Qiu Fei actually struck first. His "Beautiful!" made it seem like his eyes were exceptionally perceptive.

"It looks like today’s opponent has some background." At Happy, Wei Chen was watching the battle too and gave a sigh towards Ye Xiu. But he didn’t think he wouldn’t get a response. When he turned his head, he unexpectedly saw Ye Xiu staring dumbly at his screen!

Chapter 794: Another Player Switch

"What are you looking at?" Wei Chen moved closer to look at Ye Xiu’s screen. He was starting to suspect that he wasn’t watching the match. Why else did he look so distracted? The skill level of those two were shocking when thrown into the normal player crowd, but as seniors of the pro scene, it wasn’t that stunning!

But when he went over, Ye Xiu really was looking at the match.

Maybe it was because he was astonished at how Tang Rou’s situation wasn’t looking good? Wei Chen had also noticed it. Wasn’t that what he wanted to talk about? Of the three opponents fought today, both Ye Xiu and Wei Chen could tell that the first opponent wasn’t bad. He just performed poorly. The second opponent was evenly matched with Tang Rou, but Tang Rou performed better and also won that round. As for this round…..

Wei Chen turned his head back to look at his screen and commented: "Do you think this Demon Fighter is a different person?"

The players felt so because the difference between this round and the previous round was too great. It was actually more difficult for Ye Xiu and Wei Chen to be certain because they could see that the Demon Fighter from the previous round was actually quite skilled.

"He’s different." Ye Xiu was quite certain, "The person from the first and second round are the same person. The current one is a different person."　　

"What’s your reasoning behind that?" Wei Chen was puzzled. No matter how experienced he was, without actually being there, how could he guess that Li Rui had been distracted by his thoughts?

"I don’t know." Ye Xiu shook his head, but he was still watching the current round: "But I recognize this one here!"　　

"You recognize him? Who?" Wei Chen was astonished.

Chen Guo was pleasantly surprised. To Chen Guo, being able to fight evenly with Tang Rou was already incredible enough. If they encountered anyone skilled, they could try recruit him or her. This was one reason why Chen Guo arranged this exhibition match. Now that they had run into someone skilled, who Ye Xiu even recognized, it was too perfect!

"Who? From where? How old? How do you know him?" Chen Guo asked a string of questions.　

Ye Xiu shook his head. He didn’t immediately reply and continued to watch the match seriously. Chen Guo was surprised. From Ye Xiu’s behavior, this opponent might not be someone who could easily be recruited?

On stage, the fight between the two players was approaching the end.

The same opportunity, the same skill, but in the end, it was Qiu Fei who hit Soft Mist with Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. At that instant, Tang Rou’s hand speed had surpassed Qiu Fei’s, and Soft Mist started the attack earlier. While that was an advantage, it didn’t decide everything. Qiu Fei may have been slightly slower, but his angle was more precise and efficient. Qiu Fei’s greater familiarity with the skill revealed itself. He may have started slower, but his attack’s path was more efficient, allowing him to strike first.

This attack determined the outcome of the fight. Qiu Fei did not make a mistake. EVen though Tang Rou tried hard, she was unable to escape. Soft Mist finally fell.

Glory!　

These two eye-catching words flashed onto the screen. The spectators stared blankly. It was only until a few seconds later did they erupt. A flood of messages instantly jumped out into chat. In this instant, everyone in Happy could deeply feel that they truly were the villains.

Only a few praised Qiu Fei’s performance. The vast majority of the crowd were cheering at Happy’s downfall. The face slappers had been waiting too long for this moment. They had almost given up, thinking that Team Happy might really require pro players to take down. Quite a few were burning incense and praying for Happy to run into Excellent Era in the first round.

Who would have thought that they wouldn’t need to wait until that day came? Someone had stood out and taken down Team Happy today.　　

The crowd completely forgot about the nature of competition. Losing and winning was very normal. No matter how strong a team or a player was, no one had a 100% win rate. After beating Soft Mist, the spectators felt like Happy could no longer recover as if this loss would result in their complete collapse.

The content of the ridicule was brilliant. Compared to the common insults, the trash talk experts among the crowd were absolutely at a professional level. Tang Rou, who lost the previous round, raised her head to look at everyone. Her eyes were filled with regret. However, she was no longer a noob, who would refuse to accept the results and immediately try again like she did when she lost to Ye Xiu. Glory was entirely skill-based. There was a reason for every win and loss. And Tang Rou could evaluate her opponent’s strength, especially since her opponent used a Battle Mage too. She could identify her opponent’s methods. Who was better or worse couldn’t be determined with just a few matches. At the All Star Weekend, Tang Rou had taken Team Samsara’s Du Ming by surprise and won a few matches, but did that mean her skill level was higher than Du Ming’s?

Tang Rou understood this reasoning very well. So when she lost, she didn’t make excuses. Although she was unwilling to admit it, she had to concede: "Today’s opponet is very good."　　

"Yes." Ye Xiu nodded his head and got up, "Let me try."　　

"You?" Everyone was astonished. Up until now, there was no record of Ye Xiu ever appearing! It made those who opposed Excellent Era use this fact as an argument: you’ve been challenging them for so long and you guys can’t even force out the boss! And you still want to slap their faces?

And now, Ye Xiu took the initiative to come out.

"Do you want to use my account?" Tang Rou saw Ye Xiu heading over to her and guessed his intent.

"Yeah, they didn’t switch out, right?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I don’t think so." Tang Rou looked at the stage. That Battle Mage was still standing there, not saying anything as if waiting for them to switch players.

"Directly start." Ye Xiu said. Tang Rou pressed ready and got up to give her seat to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu sat down and quickly typed: "Again."

The other side didn’t reply, but pressed ready. When the spectators saw that the two were going to fight again, they immediately started jeering at Soft Mist. They weren’t leaving themselves an escape route. If Soft Mist won, what would they do?

Li Rui was the most depressed among everyone.

The opportunity he had been waiting for had been snatched away by Qiu Fei. Was that his fate? Qiu Fei had been favored by Ye Qiu as One Autumn Leaf’s successor. But when the team made a chance and Ye Qiu left. His position became awkward. But why did fortune favor him this time? Why did he snatch away this opportunity too?

Li Rui completely forgot that this opportunity had originally been given to him twice, but he failed to seize it. He only felt jealousy for Qiu Fei’s victory right now.

But no matter how much resentment he harbored. It would not change reality. The most eye-catching opportunity had been seized by Qiu Fei. His only option was to perform outstandingly in the following confrontations and attract attention that way. Should he switch accounts again though? He had done okay on Silent Night. If he didn’t switch accounts, it would be hard to get the same "it’s a different person" result. It would be more reliable if he switched accounts.

Li Rui was still racking his brain, when Soft Mist already pressed ready, saying "Again."

Chen Yehui immediately said: "Ignore them. Wait for them to switch!"

Chen Yehui understood very well! Qiu Fei was more skilled, but only to a limited extent. He couldn’t crush Soft Mist like he could against normal players. So if he played another round, it was possible that Qiu Fei might lose.

They were here to embarrass Team Happy. If only a single player fought all the matches, but only won a single match, it wouldn’t make a big impact. But they had only lost two matches so far and they had cleanly taken down Soft Mist. Looking at the crowd’s reactions, the crowd looked highly upon this victory. It wasn’t a lucky victory that had only come out after a hundred crushing losses.

Speaking of which, Chen Yehui had to thank Li Rui’s coverup. Luckily, Silent Night lost so badly the first round. If not, the crowd wouldn’t have thought that the players had been switched. If the first round had been an even battle, if Qiu Fei won this round, the effects wouldn’t have been so spectacular. Two evenly-matched opponents going back and forth wouldn’t be considered a slap in the face, no?

The face slap had been hugely successful, but if Qiu Fei challenged Soft Mist again and lost, the face slap effect wouldn’t be as complete. As a result, when Chen Yehui saw the opponent press ready, he thought that the other side had thought of this. How could he fall for that trap? He immediately told Qiu Fei to ignore it. However, Qiu Fei had already pressed ready. The owner of the room was Team Happy, so how could the fight not start immediately?

"Sigh!" Chen Yehui slapped his leg. It was such a perfect opportunity. Why was Qiu Fei so stupid?　　

Chen Yehui was annoyed, but he needed to rely on Qiu Fei not losing. He put aside his envy towards Qiu Fei and cheered him on: "Little Qiu, good luck!"

"Mm." Qiu Fei replied. The match began. On the other side of the field, the image of Soft Mist gradually became clear.　

Is she going to attack first again? Qiu Fei didn’t have as many thoughts as Li Rui. He was purely focused on guessing what Soft Mist would do. In the previous three rounds, Soft Mist had taken the initiative. Qiu Fei had to be wary as soon as the fight started.

Who would have thought that this time, Soft Mist did not move and instead said: "Is that you, Qiu Fei?"　

This is….. Qiu Fei heard the other side’s voice and stared blankly into space.　　

Ye Qiu? Is he really at Happy? Is he really planning on forming his own team and fighting against Excellent Era in the Challenger League?

Chapter 795: Enduring Faith

"It’s you?" Qiu Fei’s tone was incredulous.

All those rumors regarding Ye Qiu and Lord Grim had been flying around nonstop for the past half year or so, and it was no different in the training camp. And since they were closer to those involved, there would often be someone who would act act all mysterious, willing to divulge what truths they knew, saying that the information came directly from the team or someone who was in the know.

As more rumors came to light, all the different tales grew in detail. For their training camp, there was a saying that Ye Qiu couldn’t stand how terrible Excellent Era was becoming, but the club wouldn’t let him go, so he just decided to retire and build another team from scratch.

This version was detailed and refined. For example, problems like why Ye Qiu become so active so soon after his retirement were explained in this version. After retirement, pro-players weren’t bothered by their teams or constrained by any contracts, so they were free to do as they wished. That’s one of the reasons why the Alliance declared that a retired player could only come back a year after their retirement, so that pro players wouldn’t exploit this.

This version obviously favored the team and tarnished Ye Qiu’s image. Whether these versions that came from within Excellent Era were formed from the rumors that spread from person to person, or perfected by people who intentionally let slip scraps of information, no one would know.

This version was logically sound though. Ye Qiu’s retirement was very sudden and the club didn’t give him a goodbye party either, not even a goodbye match. Considering Ye Qiu’s position in Excellent Era, there was obviously something strange going on. And Excellent Era had long since addressed these issues. They said that after he retired, Ye Qiu immediately left the club and went out of contact.

That was the truth, and no one could find any faults in the tale.

There were many sayings and guesses as to the truth of the matter, but no one had a solid conclusion. As for Excellent Era, they never expressed contempt or anything like that towards Ye Qiu either.

About Ye Qiu’s retirement, the training camp also had a joke about how Captain Ye was playing a very difficult game of chess.

With the recent Team Happy debacle, Ye Qiu created a team to go against Excellent Era and revealed the team fully to the public. Most Excellent Era fans were thunderstruck. This was, after all, the greatest god in the history of their team, and now he was coming out to fight with them to the death in the Challenger League. This was something most fans could not accept.

Ye Qiu’s situation was a bit different from Zhang Jiale.

Zhang Jiale’s actions were, in simple terms, to switch teams for his own future. Fans might feel cold towards him, but, apart from a few sentences of mockery, they weren't exactly seething with rage.

It was different for Ye Qiu. Creating a team to participate in the Challenger League was a case of life and death. If Ye Qiu succeeded, then he would’ve done so by stepping on Excellent Era’s corpse. The fans wouldn’t just be scornful, they would be hurt and furious. Never mind those who supported the team, it wouldn’t be surprising if even those who were fans of Ye Qiu turned against him.

With so much hatred being hurled at Ye Qiu, little attention was paid to the news of Zhang Jiale’s return, and not without reason; it wasn’t just because Ye Qiu had a larger influence than Zhang Jiale.

There were still people who still supported Ye Qiu of course, but they were few and were completely drowned out by the cries of condemnation. It wasn’t just Excellent Era fans and those who turned on Ye Qiu among these cries, but also people who didn’t like him from the start and even those who were ambivalent towards him. His own fans had turned against him, so was it surprising that those who were neutral would too?

The number of people whose faith in Ye Qiu endured decreased with each passing incident.

But Qiu Fei was one of these people. He was someone who had been taught personally by Ye Qiu, and he knew more than anyone about the loyalty Ye Qiu had for Glory, and the feelings he held for Excellent Era.

Ye Qiu would do something like this? He didn’t believe a word. He had heard all of the rumors flying about, but he didn’t go and argue against them; he just dismissed them with a smile. No matter what anyone did or didn’t say, those who were innocent were still innocent, and those who weren’t remained so or so Qiu Fei believed.

Until the club declared that Lord Grim from Team Happy was Ye Qiu.

Who would suspect the official announcements from the club? Discussions erupted in the training camp, and Qiu Fei continuously received meaningful looks from the people around him.

Though Qiu Fei had never spoken up against those rumors, his disbelief was very much apparent. Everyone knew, this guy always looked up to and had faith in Ye Qiu, but now with the official announcement from the club, do you still dare to not believe?

Qiu Fei seemed completely unaffected.

No one knew the pain and conflict that this announcement brought out in him.

The truth diverged too far from what he knew. Would the ex-captain he thought to be loyal to Glory and the team truly do something like this? Did he really retire to get rid of the team he thought was holding him back? The one who always guided him, who fought for victory, who never gave up, would he really abandon his team at a time like that? What is he trying to accomplish doing something like this to Excellent Era? First he abandons the team, then uses them as a stepping stone to success?

The faith Qiu Fei had towards Glory was crumbling. Everything he thought he knew was crafted by this person. Yet now that this person went back on his word. How could Qiu Fei continue to have faith in him? To suspect this person was to suspect the beliefs he had always held.

On that day, Qiu Fei’s practice was filled with flaws, yet no one noticed. Qiu Fei was always a responsible child, unlike those who liked to slack off or would get distracted, he didn’t need someone watching over him.

Everything he had given to Glory, what was it all for?

Qiu Fei’s ideals had begun to shift. Everything he knew was in suspect. He was lost.

And yet at this time, the media made a statement. Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu.

For Excellent Era, this was humiliating news. For many fans, it was embarrassing. But for Qiu Fei it was great news. So, the club got it all wrong.

Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, everything was just a rumor.

Qiu Fei was elated because what he had believed in and supported was true once more. However, the club then made another announcement. Though Ye Qiu didn’t apply with Lord Grim, he was definitely at Happy.

But for Qiu Fei, he was like the radical fans that had been pulled around by these mixed messages. They wouldn’t listen any more.

Last time, they believed the club. The radical fans besieged Happy. Qiu Fei’s beliefs crumbled, beginning to suspect everything he had worked hard for. After the media came out with their news, the radical fans besieged Excellent Era. Qiu Fei found it in himself to continue believing. Then the club announced something different, so the fans retreated from the doors of Excellent Era, but wouldn’t go after Happy again. As for Qiu Fei, his wouldn’t crumble, but he felt gloom overcome him nonetheless.

He really hoped the truth was not as they said.

Yet, here and now, in front of him was an account from Team Happy and Ye Qiu was behind it, greeting him.

Qiu Fei didn’t dare believe it, or rather, didn’t want to believe it.

So Ye Qiu really was at Happy. He just didn’t use Lord Grim to apply. But the Challenger League wasn’t as strict with regulations as the Pro League, especially in the switching of team members. There was a lot of freedom there. Apart from not being able to change accounts freely, it was fine if someone applied to join or leave in the middle. Though there were some limitations, adding another member to the team was easy.

Having already experienced one breakdown, Qiu Fei didn’t shatter like he did before. Especially with who was in front of him, Qiu Fei seethed with anger. The feeling of being lied to burned.

The other seemed to have said something else, but Qiu Fei didn’t hear. He took the initiative, and charged.

The audience cheered.

Of course, they didn’t know that these two had a short talk and didn’t know that this match had a more depth to it. They just wanted to see Happy humiliated and cheered wildly for Demon Fighter, making Li Rui go green with envy.

"What’s the rush for?" Ye Xiu was a little taken aback by Qiu Fei’s advance. That kid didn’t even answer his question yet. He could only respond. He swiped his mouse. There was the sound of metal on metal, two spears clashing. But the battle would not pause with this impact. Demon Fight turned, taking half a step, and pressed a Falling Flower Palm at Soft Mist.

Soft Mist also immediately took a step, her spear rising upwards with a Sky Strike.

Though it seemed as if this trade of techniques would result in injuries for both sides, an expert could see that this Sky Strike was faster than the Falling Flower Palm. Falling Flower Palm didn’t give the user any Super Armor advantages, so this slight difference in speed was enough to negate the attack.

Qiu Fei didn’t recklessly press on and quickly switched skills. Falling Flower Palm was cancelled, and he attacked even as he dodged Sky Strike.

Chapter 796: Battle Mage Duel

Chapter 796: Chapter 796 - Battle Mage Duel

Dragon Tooth!

Ye Xiu had Soft Mist use Dragon Tooth to meet his opponent’s attack.

Qiu Fei did another micro movement. His Demon Fighter shifted slightly and Dragon Tooth brushed past his body. Demon Fighter’s spear looked as if it was about to strike Soft Mist, when Soft Mist twisted her body and her spear swept across horizontally along with her movement.

Ding! The two spears collided with each other. Ye Xiu did not want to waste his Dragon Tooth in order to dodge. Instead, he twisted to shift directions, turning his Dragon Tooth into a block. (TL Note: Guard->Block)

Blocks had numerous uses. It was a basic technique that all pro players needed to firmly grasp. It was most used in fights between the same class. In fights between the same class, both sides had the same skill options and similar stats, so their attack priorities were naturally about the same. As a result, blocks were very dependable.

However, Battle Mages were an exception. Experienced pro players would try not to block opponent attacks.　

Because blocks relied on an attack’s priority to reduce the opponent attack. According to the system, if an attack was blocked, it would still count as a hit. The attack simply hit the opponent’s weapon, so it would not deal much damage.　　

Even so, it satisfied the requirements for a chaser to spawn.

Magic chasers were a Battle Mage’s main method of attack and provided a buff. A Battle Mage without a chaser was no different from an elderly tiger with no teeth.

In addition, the Battle Mage awakening skill, Battle Spirit, relied on combos to stack. An attack being blocked would still count as a hit, so the combo count would also increase by one.

Blocking several attacks in a row looked super cool, but if the opponent was a Battle Mage, it was the same as waiting for the opponent to activate Battle Spirit and engulf you in chasers!　　

Facing Battle Mages, controlling the creation of chasers was very important, so blocking should generally not be used when possible.　　

But on the flip side, as a Battle Mage, creating chasers was very important and blocking an attack was a good way to obtain chasers. Blocking an attack and an attack being blocked were both considered as hits for both sides.

Because of this class characteristic, every Battle Mage would emphasize blocking practice. Every Battle Mage player was an expert at blocking.

The two Battle Mages battling needed chasers. At the same time, neither side wanted the other side to generate chasers, making the battle much more complicated.

Ye Xiu used Dragon Tooth as a block. Qiu Fei had also used a skill that could generate a chaser. After the block, both Battle Mages had a magic chaser floating around their bodies.

Soft Mist had a white neutral chaser from the Dragon Tooth. Demon Mist had a pale blue ice chaser from Double Stab.

Before the two chasers could completely form, the two fighters jumped backwards away from each other. Closely following afterwards, their chasers flew out from their bodies.

Boom!

As if the two chasers had agreed on the path beforehand, the chasers crashed into each other. With a light ding and without any flashy visual effects, there was a slight magic fluctuation before the two chasers disappeared. This type of collision also counted as hit. As a result, the two Battle Mages each gained a buff according to their chaser’s effects.

A light blue aura emanated from Demon Fighter, freezing the surrounding air like an armor made of ice. Ice chasers gave a defense buff to the user.

As for Soft Mist, the white aura only emanated from her two feet. It looked as if she were standing on a cloud. Neutral chasers gave a movement speed buff to the user.

The difference between the two chasers suddenly became the breaking point of the match. When Soft Mist rushed forward, her speed had clearly increased significantly. Demon Fighter’s defense buff put him on the defensive. He did not gain any advantage until an attack hit.

Buffs given by chasers lasted 20 seconds. How could Ye Xiu waste this opportunity? Utilizing his superior movement speed, he moved nimbly into a position to use Sky Strike.

Demon Fighter was at a disadvantage in terms of movement speed compared to Soft Mist, so he had no way of dodging it. Qiu Fei immediately thrust his spear in order to block the attack. However, Soft Mist’s spear suddenly twisted and completed an N. Demon Fighter failed to block the attack and he was launched into the air.

"Your decision-making still isn’t good enough. You see me use Dragon Tooth, yet you give me a chaser for free. You could have cancelled your Double Stab there. Why are you in such a rush?" Ye Xiu said.

The previous exchange of skills hadn’t been necessary. Even though Soft Mist had blocked the attack, Qiu Fei had used Double Stab, which attacked in two stages. In between the two stabs, the spear had to be retracted. How else could there be a second stab? At that moment, Qiu Fei could have cancelled his skill. If he timed it well enough, he could have retracted it in the middle of the first attack, so Dragon Tooth wouldn’t block it. Then, he could have followed with the second stage and completed the attack.

Qiu Fei, whose character had been launched into the air, immediately realized it too. So I can do that there….. I really was too hasty.

Qiu Fei grinded his teeth. He turned his character in midair, but he couldn’t see any sign of Soft Mist.　　

Vanishing Step!

This was a high-leveled technique used to combo in the air. Against normal players, using such a high-leveled technique was superfluous. Very few normal players could steady their characters while in the air. As for pro players, in order to counter this, they invented Vanishing Step.

Qiu Fei still wasn’t too good with this technique. It was because this technique required vast amounts of experience. Without a few years of accumulated experience, it would be very difficult to pull off.

Even if he couldn’t pull it off himself, that didn’t mean he was helpless against it. There was no such thing in Glory as an invincible technique. Qiu Fei spun around twice, but still couldn’t locate Soft Mist. During this time, he ate two attacks. After these two attacks, Qiu Fei decisively made a move. Demon Fighter stopped turning around in an attempt to see Soft Mist and used Tyrant’s Destruction as if he knew her location.

Sure enough, Soft Mist was inside Tyrant’s Destruction’s range. Whether this attack was blocked or dodged, Soft Mist would be forced to move away from Demon Fighter. Vanishing Step required the user to be within a certain range. This attack completely dismantled Vanishing Step.

"Not bad. You can find my location after just the second attack." Ye Xiu said again.

After escaping, Qiu Fei was on guard. Sure enough, Soft Mist rushed towards him. Qiu Fei immediately rolled without thinking and let out a Falling Flower Palm. Soft Mist leaped backwards and used Double Stab at the same time. Qiu Fei did not dodge it. He had Demon Fighter use Sky Strike to trade attacks and launch Soft Mist into the air.

Their attacks traded. Soft Mist was knocked into the air. Demon Fighter may have been hit by Double Stab, but Double Stab did not have a brief stun effect like Dragon Tooth. He took the damage and chased after Soft Mist to attack. Suddenly, a blue light flashed in front of him. An ice chaser had smashed into him.

Hit!

Elemental chasers not only dealt more damage than neutral chasers, but they also brought a debuff to the enemy. Ice chasers would slow the target. The probability of the slow and the effects depended on the skill level. Qiu Fei could not tell how many skill points had been put into Soft Mist’s Ice Chaser, but when he checked his character’s debuff status, he saw that the slow had been triggered.　

There’s still enough time!

Qiu Fei measured the distance between Demon Fighter and Soft Mist. He felt like even with the slow, there was still enough time to attack Soft Mist while she was still in hitstun. He immediately attacked, but his spear moved slower than he had expected. His attack unexpectedly missed.

Not good!

Qiu Fei suddenly realized that he had made an error in judgement. Then, he saw Soft Mist turn her body and send over her spear. Like a sharp sword, the spear swung down onto Qiu Fei’s Demon Fighter, nailing him to the ground. Battle Mage skill: Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.

This attack had little startup lag and little ending lag. When the skill was completed, Soft Mist was still in the air! Ye Xiu’s voice floated down: "Did you miscount my combo count?"

Yes!

Qiu Fei had realized it too. This was his mistake. He had miscounted Soft Mist’s combo count.　　

For a Battle Mage, the benefits of a high combo count wasn’t just from Battle Spirit. The damage and effects of a chaser could also be strengthened through a higher combo count. The higher the combo count, the stronger a chaser. The passive buff from a chaser was fixed though. Only a higher skill level would change it. Without knowing the Battle Mage’s combo count, the power of the chaser could not be determined accurately. Qiu Fei had just committed this mistake.

When Soft Mist landed on the ground, Demon Fighter had just gotten up. He immediately charged towards Soft Mist and the two Battle Mages began clashing again.

The spectators watched in awe. It currently looked like Demon Fighter was slightly on the disadvantage, but he wasn’t getting crushed. At every crucial moment, Demon Fighter seemed to be able to counterattack.

At Club Excellent Era’s studio, Li Rui and the other trainees were stunned.

Finally, one of them turned their heads to look at Li Rui. His expression was doubtful and puzzled. He asked, unsure: "Brother Li, isn’t this... a coaching match?"

Chapter 797: Coaching Match

A coaching match was a match focused on teaching. This type of match wasn’t about victory. The coach would purposefully leave openings during the match, prompting the other to make a decision. The coach obviously had be an amazing player, but the trainee also had to have some degree of skill. If a coaching match was fought with an amateur or someone who simply played for fun, they wouldn’t be able to understand the prompts.

Out of the people who knew Glory, those from the training camps of pro teams were most familiar with coaching matches. Occasionally, they would have the opportunity to practice against pro players, and these face-offs would usually be in the form of coaching matches. As for normal players, even if they were skilled enough to participate in a coaching match, they wouldn’t get the chance.

As this match between Soft Mist and Qiu Fei went on, the onlookers had that sort of feeling. This was clearly a coaching match. The pauses to give openings were rather obvious. This sort of tempo would wouldn’t be found in a usual match, only in a coaching match. The first one to voice this, directed his suspicions to Li Rui, the most skilled among them.

Meanwhile, Li Rui was dumbstruck, because he had similar suspicions, but at the same time, he could hardly believe it, so he didn’t say anything.. But when they saw the uncertainty on his face and the same expression reflected on one another, they knew that their conclusions were similar.

To be able to fight a coaching match with Qiu Fei, wasn’t this opponent a bit too terrifying?

Though everyone could guess that Ye Qiu was probably the one fighting, they never realized that Ye Qiu’s strength was so overwhelming.

The Ye Qiu from half a year ago could fight a coaching match with Qiu Fei, and half a year later he still retained the ability to do so...

No one knew more about the diligence Qiu Fei had shown this half year than the members of the training camp. They could envy him, they could be jealous of him, but none of them could ignore the efforts he had made.

Qiu Fei was already very good, and after half a year of nonstop training, he would only be better.

Yet, he could still be pulled into a coaching match.

Was this coaching match not a blow to his pride?

Never mind Qiu Fei who was in the arena, even those on the sidelines felt a bit discouraged. Had half a year of effort not made any difference in the chasm between their skill? These Gods, just how much better were they?

After careful consideration, they each still ended up worrying for themselves.

They suddenly realized, the Gods they met within their clubs were far more imposing than they had thought. Yet in the Alliance, those on par with the Gods weren’t uncommon.

What was a God? Today, these children truly began to understand through the presence of the obvious disparity in skill displayed in front of them. In the arena, the match raged on.

But after having suspicions of the true face of this match, the training camp members could gradually confirm that this really was a coaching match.

But that didn’t mean Qiu Fei knew.

This was something that those who often participated in coaching matches understood. When you knew about the intentions behind it, it would become obvious, but to the participant involved, it may not be so clear.

This victory was one they no longer had hope for.

If the person who dared to pull you into fighting a coaching match played seriously, you had no chance of winning. And for Ye Qiu, he didn’t seem to care about victory either. Rather than prompting good decisions, the coaching match exposed all kinds of flaws and problems Qiu Fei had.

Under Ye Qiu’s guidance, Qiu Fei’s technique was full of holes.

But who here hadn’t fought Qiu Fei before? If it wasn’t for this match, none of them would believe Qiu Fei could end up like this.

This battle had gone on for quite a while, the two characters seemed to be continuously fighting for the upper hand, and the audience kept cheering for Demon Fighter.

However, everyone in the Excellent Era workroom had long since gone quiet. They knew that the entire situation was under Ye Qiu’s complete control. The only reason the battle had dragged on was because Ye Qiu was fighting a coaching match, not seriously trying to win. Many of the openings that Qiu Fei revealed were intentionally ignored.

They couldn’t help but look towards Qiu Fei. He wasn’t still oblivious, was he?

And what they saw on Qiu Fei’s face was intense focus, teeth gritted, he seemed to be giving it his all to win. … He had no idea!

That was something everyone realized immediately.

Despite his efforts, the first one to fall was still Qiu Fei’s Demon Fighter.

A deafening thud drew everyone’s attention. Qiu Fei had slammed his fist against the table. His displeasure with the result was clear as day.

Qiu Fei was, indeed, displeased.

Just a little more!

That’s what he thought.

Yet, at that moment he heard the other speak up. "Save the video and have a good look over it later!"

Just as Qiu Fei wanted to demand an explanation, Soft Mist left the arena.

Qiu Fei, feeling a bit lost, glanced around around himself only to see everyone staring at him with shock. Qiu Fei knew he had lost his cool. No one had seen him behave so uncharacteristically before.

But his desire for victory was strong. He had wanted to use a match of Glory to teach the other a lesson. Unfortunately, he had failed.

"You okay, Qiu Fei?" Someone asked.

Qiu Fei shook his head, he was still going over the last words Ye Qiu had given him.

Demon Fighter was still lying prone in the arena. Qiu Fei saved the match, and then withdrew from the it.

Happy also finally switched players with Steamed Bun Invasion standing ready.

As soon as Qiu Fei saw that it wasn’t Soft Mist, he exited the arena. Chen Yehui started ordering another to take his place, but Qiu Fei’s attention was elsewhere. He opened the recording at once.

Not long after, he was dumbstruck.

Coaching matches were clear the audience, but not to the one playing in the match.

During the match, Qiu Fei gave it his all and fought to win, but eventually lost in the end.

He really had thought so.

But looking at the recording now, he knew that wasn’t what happened.

This was a coaching match, a patient and meticulous coaching match. Even when Ye Qiu was still at Excellent Era, the coaching matches they had fought had never been so thorough.

A full 23 minutes!

To fight one on one for 23 minutes was probably harder than ending it in two minutes.

The execution of such a patient coaching match was performed despite the fact that Qiu Fei had no idea, and gave it his all, trying to win over his opponent.

Seeing the two figures on the screen exchange blow after blow, Qiu Fei was completely stunned.

His flaws, his problems, the things he needed to work on, after Ye Qiu’s departure, how long had it been since these were pointed out to him?

But in just this one match, they were revealed to him scene by scene.

What painstaking care was put into these 23 minutes?

If Ye Qiu had wanted to win, it would’ve taken only 2 minutes.

If he wanted to fight a coaching match just to mock him, he didn’t need to put in so much effort to unveil all of Qiu Fei’s flaws.

If it was someone who had abandoned their team, someone who had used retirement to escape responsibility, would he really put so much care into guiding their juniors?

Qiu Fei couldn’t continue watching the recording anymore. He suddenly stood up.

Everyone looked over in surprise, but Qiu Fei didn’t speak to anyone, swiftly walking out the room.

"Where are you going, Qiu Fei?" By the time Chen Yehui had asked his question, Qiu Fei had already left.

On the computer he had been using, the screen was still frozen on the images of the recording.

"That guy, after realizing it was a coaching match, I bet he couldn’t take it." Someone guessed.

After leaving the workroom, it didn’t take Qiu Fei long to walk out of the club and head directly towards Happy a little ways down on the other side of the road.

He had to know.

Before, he hadn’t looked for answers because he thought there was no need. His faith in the God he respected was immovable, and he believed he could do no wrong. That’s why all the accusations, all the rumors, even from within the club, failed to convince him. To him, none of it was real.

As for Ye Qiu never coming out to explain anything, he didn’t think it was strange. From what he knew of captain Ye Qiu, he only cared about Glory and victory. As for this other nonsense, say what you want, you think the captain cares?

Yes, he never cared.

Our captain was always like that! When he thought of his, Qiu Fei had felt proud.

Which was why when the club officially confirmed some of those rumors, Qiu Fei seethed. Then when the media exposed that Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, and after, he found that Ye Qiu was using Happy’s accounts to stand opposing them in the arena, Qiu Fei’s conflicting emotions were something no one would be able to understand.

Yet now, he had seen the coaching match Ye Qiu fought with him, with that same patience, that same care. He was so thorough, too, using over 20 minutes. For him, it was like being told that this was the last time, everything that could be taught was given to him in this match, because it was possible that there might not be another chance.

Qiu Fei couldn’t sit still anymore, he had to confirm it for himself; he had to know the truth.

Happy Internet Cafe’s free internet usage promotion was still going on, and the place was still crowded with people, but those who came to talk trash even while taking advantage of the free internet were no more.

Team Happy’s skill had been revealed, sarcasm and mockery needed some basis of truth, but this basis the players thought they had were being shattered over and over again by Happy.

Today was a little different.

The undefeatable Soft Mist from Happy finally met her match today.

It was unfortunate that most of the faceslappers had long since left. Having to eat your words every time you tried to mock someone wasn’t appealing, so none of them dared come back, even with the free internet.

Qiu Fei charged into the Internet cafe, but there were people everywhere.

Ye Qiu… where on earth should he go to find him?

Chapter 798: Defeat After Defeat

For the others of Excellent Era, Qiu Fei’s sudden departure left them confused. They exchanged puzzled glances, but none of them really cared much. All those from the training camp were rivals, so Qiu Fei leaving would only make them happier.

On the other hand, Chen Yehui was a bit worried. That guy was much more skilled than the other training camp members. He had taken notice of the few times Qiu Fei let his expressions slip through. Coming from the training camp, he could definitely tell that it was a training match, and that the opponent had to be Ye Qiu.

And Qiu Fei’s strange mood started from when Ye Qiu stepped into the arena.

Perhaps the others hadn’t heard, or just didn’t care, but Chen Yehui noticed: upon stepping into the arena, Ye Qiu had started talking to Qiu Fei.

"I am grateful for your guidance."

Chen Yehui could clearly hear the coldness of that tone. Considering Qiu Fei and Ye Qiu’s relationship, just the tone used was a big hint that something was wrong. Maybe, Qiu Fei had fallen out with Ye Qiu. It wasn’t hard to guess why either. How could there be a shortage of people who were disgruntled with Ye Qiu, what with his recent actions?

Qiu Fei hated Ye Qiu.

When Chen Yehui came to this conclusion, he immediately felt a connection with Qiu Fei. He even wanted to talk trash about Ye Qiu with Qiu Fei.

On the battlefield, the newly arrived Steam Bun Invasion won a match. The training camp member who had been smashed out of the match by a brick was flushed in bewilderment.

The person’s name was Bai Shengxian, people usually called him Little Bai. After a few exchanges with Steamed Bun Invasion, he thought that this guy was the real noob, turning to smile at his companions: "Watch me crush this noob."

That’s right. He had thought that this opponent was very much an amatuer. How could he be skilled with such simple approaches? He was just fast and technical. For a pro-player, this kind of player was nothing but a noob. Bai Shengxian had confidence that he could deal with him swiftly.

He had set himself up, only to find that reality wasn’t so.

Steamed Bun Invasion fought without much thought or depth in a terribly childish way.

But… shouldn’t there be a limit to how childish, how lacking in thought and depth you could be? He had never seen anyone who was so lacking in thought, so lacking in depth, so utterly childish!

Bai Shengxian’s scorn towards his opponent exceeded his own expectations over and over again. That chaotic fighting style wasn’t a style he had witness before in any brawler. Players who were wild and unrefined in style weren’t uncommon, but never before had he seen such a crazy style. What on earth was this mess?

Eventually, Bai Shengxian’s character fell to a brick.

His disbelief and anger made him want to yell at this player, "That’s not how you play Glory!"

That’s right. That was what Bai Shengxian believed. Of everything he knew about in Glory, there was no such style as the one that had been displayed before him. What nonsense was this?

And yet it was just this messy play style that defeated him. He didn’t want to believe it! That must be beginner’s luck. He hadn’t been prepared at all for someone so reckless. Did he really think he could win more than once with such a style?

The match that was foretold to be played according to the regular tournament rules never happened, so Bai Shengxian ignored the rules too, angrily stepping back into the arena. He wanted revenge, he wanted to wash away this humiliation, and he wanted to tell this opponent: that’s not how you play Glory. It’s not that simple.

Yes, Glory wasn’t so simple.

And when Bai Shengxian’s character fell once more, the one who realized this was himself.

He thought he had seen through this opponent, thought that he could easily turn the tides, yet in end he was still the one who fell.

His opponent was as messy and reckless as ever, so much so that it made his intentions completely incomprehensible. Sometimes he would fight with a steady tempo, sometimes he would make amateurish mistakes, and sometimes he would achieve incredibly smart plays. How are you meant to fight such an opponent? Your experience was useless; your predictions were never right. Though it was a one on one fight, Bai Shengxian felt as if he were in a free for all, and suddenly, bang bang, he was hit!

Bai Shengxian still wanted to make a comeback, but he was afraid. He was afraid that not only would he fail in ridding himself of this humiliation, he would then further humiliate himself.

As for the others, they were also carefully studying Steamed Bun Invasion. None of them dared to take him lightly. Not even Li Rui. This guy was utterly strange, completely beyond the comprehension of experts of Glory like them.

They all stared at one another helplessly, not daring to step forwards to fight.

Then came the awkwardness from ignoring the rules.

If everyone had just played by the rules they set in the beginning, wouldn’t Steamed Bun Invasion have just left of his own accord? Yet since no one cared about the rules, he still stayed in the arena despite winning. What were they to do now? It’s not like they could go up and say, we’re too afraid to fight you, please switch out.

If they said that, then even winning the next match wouldn’t win back their face.

Asking them to obey the standard tournament rules would be even worse. After all, they were the ones who violated them first!

Having thought of this, Chen Yehui glared at Li Rui in irritation.

The good thing was that they didn’t make any promises about this. If they won, then they would’ve been happy about getting one over Team Happy, if they lost then they can just retreat quietly. It’s not like this was their first time getting tormented by Ye Qiu. They could take this humiliation.

"What’s wrong? Does no one dare to try anymore?" At times like this, Chen Yehui had to try and prod them a little. He could tell that they had been startled by Steamed Bun Invasion’s incomprehensible style, and without any firm understanding of how to deal with it, none of them wanted to try.

Yet, you couldn’t just give up a match because you had no idea of how to counter your opponent.

Just thinking of it made Chen Yehui furious. If it wasn’t for the fact that it wasn’t appropriate for someone of his standing, he would definitely berate these guys. At such a time, he wished Qiu Fei were here. If it was Qiu Fei, he wouldn’t cower no matter what his opponent’s identity was. With these guys, they would probably surrender the moment Ye Qiu came out.

Chen Yehui’s provocation worked. As soon as the words left his mouth, they all saw it for what it was, but were still unable to remain unaffected out of shame. Li Rui, who was most prone to overconfidence, stood forward.

"Give me another account. I’ll do it," Li Rui said.

Fuck, you can’t even win. All you do is switch accounts! How many Battle Mages do you think I have? Chen Yehui criticized in his head, but only allowed the latter half to be spoken. "There aren’t that many accounts, so don’t waste them!"

There was no lack of mockery in his words, and Li Rui noticed, but had no way of retorting. He was only in the training camp after all, so it wasn’t unexpected that the guild leader wouldn’t think much of him. On the other hand, Li Rui didn’t want to get on this person’s bad side. The guild leader had no say over members of the training camp, but it wouldn’t hard for him to soil Li Rui’s reputation. He was a senior member of the club, after all.

Li Rui quietly accepted Chen Yehui’s remark and returned to the arena after taking another Battle Mage account.

Li Rui’s abilities were above that of the others present. As for Steamed Bun, his chaotic style didn’t make him invincible. After a messy brawl, Li Rui finally managed to deal with Steamed Bun. Li Rui felt no shortage of relief upon winning. Though he won, it wasn’t easy. It would be hard to say how another match would go.

Yet Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t seem to have any plans on letting Li Rui out of a rematch, he stayed standing in the arena despite his loss.

Li Rui knew that without rules this just wouldn’t work. Even if people lost they would just fight again. Among all the repeated defeats and victories, he would have a hard time standing out and their goal of humiliating the other side would never be achieved!

But how should he do this? If he says the loser should be swapped out, wouldn’t he also get forced from the arena? He stayed despite his loss, too!

Just as Li Rui was trying to figure out how to go about this, he suddenly realized something! He had already switched accounts, he wasn’t a loser who refused to come down, he had a new account now. What was there to be afraid of?

As soon as he thought it through, Li Rui sent a message: "If we keep going like this, it’ll be endless! Why don’t we have the loser switch out?"

At this moment, Li Rui had a plan in mind. This was an individual competition. Compared to the group arena, one versus many was much easier to achieve. Unlike now, the winner’s health wouldn’t be replenished in the group arena. He should take this chance with this mismatch of individual and group arena rules to defeat more opponents. That way he would definitely stand out!

Seeing Steamed Bun Invasion step down, Li Rui was overjoyed! Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were rather strong, and victory against them wasn’t certain, but now they’ve both switched out. Who else does Team Happy have? Are there any other experts? Ye Qiu wouldn’t come up would he?

Just as Li Rui was beginning to feel uneasy, someone stepped into the arena. Windward Formation, a Warlock.

Windward Formation hadn’t fought many matches. He wasn’t as well known as Soft Mist, and he wasn’t a Battle Mage. Li Rui was relieved. The match started and very soon, Li Rui wanted to cry.

Defeat!

He lost again!

Just a little more! He was so close to winning, but his luck today had simply been abysmal.

Li Rui didn’t want to lose this chance, he hardened his heart and sought Chen Yehui out once more. "Give me another account…"

The fourth time...

Li Rui had swapped accounts four times now. Never mind Chen Yehui, even the training camp members were feeling a little ashamed on his behalf.

Yet Chen Yehui didn’t refuse him, giving him another account. In the end, he lost by just a bit once more.

"F*ck!" Li Rui was furious, looking back at Chen Yehui. This time Chen Yehui decided to be nice and just tossed him another card.

Once more, he entered the arena. Once more, he lost by just a bit.

Li Rui stared dumbly at his screen. Losing thrice in a row by just a bit. It doesn’t seem possible to say it’s simply bad luck! It’s not like he could have the same sort of luck every time.

"This person’s a little strange. Let me test him out with another account." Li Rui finally had a proper excuse.

By the sixth Battle Mage account, Li Rui had already started to pay close attention. This time he lost again, and again, it was just by a small margin, and now he understood why. This tiny margin meant that if he just put in a bit more effort, if he was just a little luckier he could overcome it. His opponent was intentionally manipulating him, toying with him, mocking him.

This tiny margin was a very much despicable one!

Bang!

Li Rui got up and stormed out. Angry and humiliated, he couldn’t stay any longer.

Chapter 799: Nonsense

Li Rui also ran away.

Chen Yehui brought six gamers from the training camp with him, and two ran away. They didn’t have enough for a five-man team battle.

But was there a need to fight any longer?

Chen Yehui didn’t think so. Those six were outstanding among the training camp in Excellent Era. If they needed six players from the training camp to form a team to represent Excellent Era, he believed that only those six qualified.

And these six failed to get the upper hand on Team Happy.

No, that statement would be too immodest. What upper hand? They were clearly on the losing side. Qiu Fei’s performance was relatively steady and managed to defeat Tang Rou, who was in the spotlight. However, he immediately alarmed Ye Qiu, whose position would unlikely be touched by them.

But apart from that?

Li Rui had a strong sense of self-importance and believed he was outstanding. But he made a joke out of himself by switching six accounts. After being tormented back and forth, he only managed to win against Steamed Bun Invasion once, before he was toyed with by a Warlock called Windward Formation.

As for the other four, only Bai Shengxian managed to have a go, but he also made a fool of himself. He said he would bully the noob, but he ended up being oppressed by the so-called ‘noob’ twice. He lost to the point that he didn’t dare to try again.

The three’s performance was enough to show their level of skill against Happy. Chen Yehui no longer felt the need for the other three to have a go. The more they tried, the more they would lose. Even if they happened to win once in awhile, the difference between their wins and losses weren’t enough to embarrass Team Happy!

If they couldn’t faceslap, what was the point?

Chen Yehui didn’t stop Li Rui from leaving, while the remaining four looked at one another in dismay. They looked at Windward Formation, who was still standing at the arena field. This was a plot Li Rui had set up in order to be in the limelight, but now they had fallen into it. Windward Formation was clearly more skilled than Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. If Li Rui was toyed around with, then they wouldn’t fare any better. Why would they line up to be tormented? Everyone came here to faceslap, if they couldn’t, why would they turn their cheeks to be slapped?

The four didn’t utter a word, neither did Chen Yehui. Windward Formation even started asking for the next person to come up. Then, the door was pushed open and Qiu Fei returned.

Qiu Fei’s didn’t hide the disappointment from his face.

He ran to Happy Internet Cafe, and looked around several times. He thoroughly checked every customer before each computer, but he still couldn’t find the person he was looking for.

Of course he couldn’t find them.

Ye Xiu’s group moved to the rented apartment much earlier on, and Chen Guo was also with them. As for Happy Internet Cafe, after it overcame the obstacles and won their way through all the challenges, the faceslapping group stopped showing up. The customers present in Happy Internet Cafe were those who came for the free internet. Happy no longer had to keep the promise of staying free until the season. Since it was peaceful, Chen Guo didn’t need to supervise it. She could now have fun and hang around with the other group.

Qiu Fei couldn’t find Ye Qiu, so he returned disappointed. Qiu Fei didn’t have his contact info. It used to be effortless to find Ye Qiu in the club, how could he have known such a day would come?

There would be an opportunity somehow.

Qiu Fei didn’t greet anyone when he returned, but only quietly returned to his seat. No one touched his computer, so the screen was fixed on the scene when he last fought with Soft Mist. His Demon Fighter was on the floor, while Soft Mist stood on his side. Although she was a female character different from One Autumn Leaf, the character still looked majestic. She was just like the silhouette he always admired.

Every character carried the player’s spirit within them! Using this to distinguish the player was more accurate than looking at one’s habits!

Qiu Fei suddenly remembered how Ye Qiu used to tell him this. It sounded incredible, but he didn’t really believe it. He was now witnessing it for himself. Even though it was a different character and she stood there without moving, Qiu Fei felt that this was Ye Qiu, the Battle God and One Autumn Leaf.

He was always there. He had never left. He had never changed.

He only cared about winning or losing in Glory; To Qiu Fei, he was always the instructor who gave his all. Even if it was a situation like this, Ye Qiu was still the same, he would guide and help Qiu Fei with a coaching match.

All of Qiu Fei’s doubts were erased at once. He did not need to find Ye Qiu in person to ask for the truth. Ye Qiu had already used his match to explain everything. The player’s spirit could be passed on through the character!

Qiu Fei was filled with enthusiasm and a smile showed up on his face. After he looked around, he realised everyone was staring at him. He knew that everyone would be puzzled after seeing him running back and forth recklessly. But when he scanned past everyone, he failed to find Li Rui.

"Where’s Li Rui?" Qiu Fei asked.

"He left." Someone answered.

"He left?" Qiu Fei was puzzled.

"Alright, let’s call it a day!" Chen Yehui spoke. Even though Qiu Fei returned, there was no need to continue today’s challenge. They had already lost so many matches. What was the point? They couldn’t switch accounts endlessly. Li Rui have already used six Battle Mages. The spectators weren’t stupid. Even if they were fans of Excellent Era and the ratio of Battle Mages were greater, it would have been too much of a coincidence to gather up so many Battle Mages for a challenge at once.

"Then we’ll take our leave." Bai Shengxian could no longer continue. When he heard Chen Yehui’s declaration, he got up, informed everyone, and was ready to escape. It was very embarrassing for him for viewing the opponent as a noob, but end up being tormented for two matches. He could no longer hold it in.

Even though the other three didn’t fight, they didn’t feel regretful at all. If they really went, they might have ended up embarrassing themselves like Li Rui and Bai Shengxian. If such an embarrassing story was spread in the club, it might affect their future! The three also informed others of their leave and left. Qiu Fei didn’t have to need to stay, but he wanted to save the recording of the previous match, so he hastily typed on the computer.

Chen Yehui had already accepted Qiu Fei as a Ye Qiu hater like him, so he came over to watch Qiu Fei upload the document of the recording onto the disk. He smiled and said. "Little Qiu was not bad today."

Qiu Fei turned around and smiled back. He was not Mo Fan, Qiu Fei would respond politely to the befriendment of others. This was unlike Mo Fan, who would always have an emotionless and deadpan face.

"Would you like me to get you a USB drive?" Chen Yehui made a stance that was prepared to ransack the boxes.

"No need, no need. It’s almost done uploading." Qiu Fei said.

"Little Qiu was not bad." Chen Yehui nodded and repeated what he said previously. "You never forget to improve yourself!"

"I’m supposed to." Qiu Fei said.

"When you fought that match, was the opponent Ye Qiu?" Chen Yehui asked.

Qiu Fei nodded, his eyes continued to gaze at the screen’s uploading progress. 36.8%.

"He was sneaking here and there, who knows what sort of trick he’ll pull next time." Chen Yehui said.

Qiu Fei turned his head around. His expression changed.

Chen Yehui thought he had found a friend and continued to speak. "A match is a match, but he deliberately made it into a training match. What was the meaning of it? To insult you?"

Qiu Fei smiled with disapproval. He was about to say something, but Chen Yehui continued with his tirade. "Forming a grass-root team and pulling off all kinds of ridiculous stunts. Is he deliberately trying to irritate us? This guy must have noticed Excellent Era’s drop in performance. Excellent Era current situation must have been a part of his conspiracy. As for him? He left us mid-way."

Chen Yehui continued to speak nonsense because anything malicious against Ye Qiu must be satisfying to hear for Ye Qiu haters! Chen Yehui wanted to befriend Qiu Fei because his skills were pretty good and he would become a helpful supporter of his. Even though Qiu Fei was under Sun Xiang’s oppression, it didn’t mean his future was in total darkness. Whatever happened. He was better than Li Rui and those other guys. Besides, he was a Ye Qiu hater, so it would be fun chatting together!

Qiu Fei looked at the screen, the uploading bar depicted 57.7%. Chen Yehui didn’t see much of a reaction from Qiu Fei, so he continued to search for their resonating point and spoke badly of Ye Qiu. This was something he was good at.

"Let’s talk about you! You originally had a bright future, but he just suddenly left. It forced the club to find Sun Xiang to save us from our current situation. That’s why you’re in such an awkward position. Does he have no sense of responsibility? To give you hope and then destroy it. Is it fun to mock your dreams?" The more Chen Yehui spoke, the more he entered the role. He even thought of his previous self, and his anger immediately got out of hand.

The screen’s uploading bar continued to increase. 80.2%.

"Ye Qiu is so hypocritical. He likes to speak all sort of nonsense like Glory, winning, and teamwork, but what did he do? He dragged us all into the mud and left us like that. Why don’t we hear him talking about winning or teamwork anymore? Hypocrite! Bah!" Chen Yehui spat with disdain. The uploading of the recording happened to reach 100%.

"Oh, it finished uploading. Alright, you can return. Remember to visit when you’re free!" Chen Yehui said, when the uploading finished.

Qiu Fei stood up and turned around. What Chen Yehui saw was not a friendly smile, but a fist. It smashed into Chen Yehui’s face.

Chen Yehui’s surroundings spun and stars appeared before his eyes. He felt as if his brain was smacked out by the force of the punch. His body tipped back and stumbled. When he lost his balance, he crashed and pushed a table out of place while he fell and rolled under it. Chen Yehui didn’t think that Qiu Fei had such strength. They spent their whole day hanging before the computers, so they shouldn’t be well-built. But when the fist came his way, Chen Yehui was beat down under the table and lost his sense of direction. His lips felt as if it were on fire, and his front teeth seemed loose. Between the buzzing noise in his ears, he heard Qiu Fei say: "Nonsense."

Chapter 800: Not Easy to Report

After Qiu Fei finished talking, he turned around and left the game studio. Chen Yehui lay underneath the desk. He didn’t recover for a long time.

What just happened?

Did I just... get punched?

It was an actual slap to the face. It wasn’t some insult thrown online, but a punch to the face. Chen Yehui had trouble wrapping his head around it. This wasn’t the game. Why was there still fighting? Did he somehow transcend worlds?

Chen Yehui wasn’t the only stunned. There were other employees at the game studio! Everyone had seen Qiu Fei punch their senior to the ground. Everyone stared in shock. A minute passed since Qiu Fei left. It was only then did they realize: wasn’t their boss still lying under the table?

He’s not dead right?

Everyone hastily got up. They immediately circled around and then saw their boss get up from underneath the table with difficulty.

Someone close to him supported him up. Chen Yehui was just barely standing. He lifted his head up. The surrounding people stifled a laugh.

The legendary sausage mouth! They had finally seen it themselves with their own eyes. When the mouth swelled up after being hit, it really looked like he had two sausages hanging on his face.

Laughing at this moment wasn’t appropriate though. Everyone tried their hardest to endure it. Those, who couldn’t hang on, gave an excuse saying they needed to get some water or grab a stool to temporarily leave.

Chen Yehui was helped onto a stool. He refused any water poured out for him with a wave of his hands. The studio was quiet. No one said anything. They were all trusted subordinates of Chen Yehui. If not, Chen Yehui wouldn’t have denounced Ye Qiu in front of them, but it was because of this very reason that Chen Yehui was punched in the face by Qiu Fei. This matter wouldn’t be easy to handle.

Even if he reported him, Qiu Fei had only punched him. Although hitting someone wasn’t right, from the club’s perspective, it wasn’t morally wrong in that situation. Chen Yehui wasn’t injured or crippled. His lips had swelled to two sausages now, but it would heal after a few days.

On the other hand, he had talked all sorts of trash about Ye Qiu. From the club’s perspective, this was definitely a grave error.

Even if the higher-ups like the manager and the boss had the same thoughts as Chen Yehui, none of them would voice it like Chen Yehui had.

In reality, the club wasn’t afraid to offend any players. The club was afraid of offending fans. Ye Qiu had contributed greatly to Excellent Era’s success. The club wanted to reduce his influence, but directly denouncing him like Chen Yehui had definitely wasn’t a viable option. Even if Ye Qiu really had been a malignant tumor to the team, when the club kicked him out, they would still praise him and send him off with their blessings. The club would only cross the line if even the fans spurned him too.

Was Ye Qiu that type? Definitely not.

Even though there were many voices of condemnation towards Ye Qiu recently, that was just because of the current situation. The fans had acted on their own. Excellent Era could only reveal their knowledge of the situation to the public. For example, Ye Qiu had formed Team Happy; Ye Qiu was Lord Grim; Ye Qiu had refused their invitation to return. All of this had been true.

The club intended on stirring up trouble, but they could only fan the flames. They revealed actions that the fans wouldn’t understand and support and let the fans decide for themselves. How could they directly slander Ye Qiu and let the fans choose? If they did that, it would result in the opposite of what they desired.

Club Excellent Era’s attitude towards Ye Qiu was like this both internally and externally. Chen Yehui had overstepped his bounds, slandering Ye Qiu in an attempt to win over Qiu Fei. If the club investigated the matter, the club wouldn’t attach much importance to Qiu Fei’s punch, but his unadorned stance towards Ye Qiu.

The higher ups could talk about their true thoughts privately amongst themselves, but if you go out and start blabbering, aren’t you being too unreliable?

Chen Yehui’s brain wasn’t only fixed onto Glory. As someone holding an important position in the club, he had to worry about his career too. Analyzing the pros and cons of a situation was a necessary skill.

He had no way of launching an investigation into the matter because it was his provocation to begin with. He had misjudged Qiu Fei’s attitude and employed such an unreliable method. There wasn’t even enough time for him to cover up the incident. How could he dare to blow up the incident and report it?

He wouldn’t forget that punch though. As the matter stood, he couldn’t take revenge at the moment, but he could grasp at a weakness he found in the future. If not, how could the saying "settle accounts after autumn" exist?

What should he do to pass through this current obstacle?

Would Qiu Fei report him?

Yes, logically speaking, it was also entirely possible.

Qiu Fei truly respected Ye Qiu. As for the club? Even though the higher-ups hated Ye Qiu on the inside, they could only express their respect and gratitude towards him on the surface. As a result, the higher-ups might have the same thoughts as him, but someone who wantonly condemned Ye Qiu would actually be outed as a pest.

But if that happened, Chen Yehui wasn’t worried.

"Little Zhao, tss….." Chen Yehui finally spoke, but it was extremely painful to open his mouth. Apart from the swelling, his lips had been cut in many areas.

"Senior..." Little Zhao was a quick-witted fellow. When he heard his name called, he immediately went over.

"Go chase after him and see where that kid ran off to." Chen Yehui said.

"Chase him and then what?" Little Zhao asked.

"See where he went and then report back to me." Chen Yehui said. It was like he was typing out his words in chat. Every time he spoke, his lips hurt.

"Okay." Little Zhao nodded his head and then ran off.

Not long afterwards, Little Zhao messaged back. Qiu Fei didn’t go anywhere. He went back to the training camp and was using the computer in the practice room.

"He didn’t talk to anyone?" Chen Yehui asked.

"No." Little Zhao replied.

"That’s fine. Come back!" Chen Yehui let out a sigh of relief. It seems like after punching him, Qiu Fei was too lazy to bother with anything else. Teens were still too pure. How could they have as many thoughts as Chen Yehui.

"You punk. You just wait….." Chen Yehui gnashed his teeth. He never liked him and now he deeply hated him. Even so, Chen Yehui didn’t dare to stir up any trouble using this incident. What he needed to consider was how should he explain his swollen lips to others?

Excellent Era had formed a team to slap Happy’s face, but it resulted in Chen Yehui being punched in real life. Not only did he need to erase these results, even in the game, Excellent Era had failed. Chen Yehui would need to at least report this failure to Cui Li.

"I know. I saw it." Cui Li bluntly said. In the end, he added: "The boss saw it too."　　

"Ah?"

"I’m saying the way you organized it had issues! How can you allow people who lost to keep fighting and losing? We can’t achieve the faceslapping result we want. If it weren’t for those losses, defeating Soft Mist after that one match would have been a perfect conclusion." Cui Li said.

Chen Yehui obviously knew what he was talking about. Li Rui lost two matches in a row. Then, Qiu Fei went up and beat Soft Mist under the context that there had been a switch of players. If Soft Mist couldn’t continue fighting, that victory would have been enough. Unfortunately, Soft Mist won against Qiu Fei in the next match, diluting his victory. The face slappers couldn’t use this victory to back up their arguments because it could easily be countered.

"Good for you though. When you needed to follow the rules, you didn’t follow them. When you shouldn’t have followed the rules, you followed them." Cui Li continued.

When he shouldn’t have followed the rules referred to when Li Rui beat Steamed Bun Invasion and then kept switching accounts only to be toyed around with by that Warlock, Windward Formation. All the matches had been extremely close, frustrating Li Rui to death.　　

Li Rui!

Chen Yehui discovered that everything had gone wrong because of Li Rui. Li Rui started the mess by losing to Soft Mist and then switching accounts, refusing to give up. Then, he squandered it again, when he beat Steamed Bun Invasion, demanding the other side to switch players. Then, he switched, switched, and switched again.　　

That b*stard!

Chen Yehui never had a good impression of Li Rui before either. Now he was even more furious. At this moment, Cui Li asked: "Did you arrange for those Battle Mages to keep on coming out on stage again and again?"

Chen Yehui hastily said. Excellent Era had looked unsightly there. 　　

Chen Yehui never had a good impression of Li Rui. Now he was even more furious. At this moment, Cui Li asked: "Did you arrange for those Battle Mages to keep on coming out on stage again and again?"

"No!" Chen Yehui hastily said. Excellent Era had been toyed with. With so many Battle Mages coming out, the crowd could probably guess that it was someone switching between alternate accounts, let alone Cui Li. He and Chen Yehui had picked which trainees to use. Of the six picked, Qiu Fei and Li Rui were the only two Battle Mages.

"It was Li Rui. He kept trying to redeem himself, so he kept on trying again and again." Chen Yehui hastily explained. He didn’t like Li Rui, but if he hit a person who was already down, he would be seen as using Li Rui as a scapegoat. Cui Li’s impression of him might turn bad as a result.

"What a mess. Then what was that in the beginning?" Cui Li asked.

Chen Yehui told the truth. Cui Li listened and was very unsatisfied with Li Rui’s conduct: "That Li Rui is too reckless."

Chen Yehui did not answer.

"Little Qiu is not bad." Cui Li said for the third time today. This time, he wasn’t talking about Qiu Fei’s performance on stage. If there was some special reason for his praise, then it would indicate his acknowledgement of him.

Chen Yehui heard the praise from Cui Li and was startled. He suddenly hated how he hadn’t pushed the blame onto Qiu Fei instead, when he had needed to explain himself.

But when he thought about it again, so many people knew! Confusing black and white would be too arrogant.

Seeing Qiu Fei suddenly be recognized was too unpleasant. He inadvertently touched his lips. F*ck, they’re bleeding again…...

Chapter 801: A New Season

As for Happy, they had no idea what drama was happening at Excellent Era. However, after identifying Qiu Fei, Ye Qiu was certain he knew where today’s opponents were from. And in these matches facing almost pro-level trainees, neither side had a particular disadvantage.

Nothing needed to be said about Wei Chen, of course. Even though he was older, his experience was enough to let him easily deal with some trainees.

As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, having only started playing Glory upon the launch of the tenth server, being at this level now was a terrifying improvement.

Beating back Excellent Era’s training camp was news that could definitely boost their morale, so of course Ye Qiu wouldn’t keep it to himself. Though Happy’s undefeatable gold wall was finally shattered, their victories still exceeded their losses, so no one could really use their two losses to prove anything.

Instead, through these matches, those with some degree of skill or judgement, finally had a clearer understanding of Team Happy’s abilities. With those who had come only to be crushed, they really estimate Happy’s skill. They could only tell how utterly useless their opponents were.

And now, having gone up against Excellent Era’s training camp members who were close to being pro level, Team Happy had to perform at their best. The true depth of their ability had finally been revealed to players.

There were still many who said that even with such a skill level, wanting to best Excellent Era was a fantasy, but their momentum was greatly reduced.

Compared to Excellent Era, they still fell behind, but they could challenge them. Against normal players, they wouldn’t be met with any resistance whatsoever, so why wouldn’t aim for the Pro League?

More and more people rallied behind Happy. Although, among them, the vast majority just supported Happy to see Excellent Era fall, what with the enemy of my enemy being a friend and all. But, those who truly believed in the team weren’t nonexistent.

On the last day of the free internet event, when Chen Guo came to the Internet cafe to oversee the cleanup, one of the customers suddenly wished them "good luck."

Just one phrase of encouragement.

Whether it was truly from the heart, or if it was because of the free internet, Chen Guo wasn’t sure, but this was enough to warm her heart.

Two weeks! At first, they were besieged with accusations. Ye Qiu’s identity had been exposed, and when the Internet cafe was surrounded by angry fans, Chen Guo had been terrified

Yet today, their efforts had finally earned them a phrase of encouragement. Even though they couldn’t make out this person’s true thoughts, this was the first praise they had gained from normal players. This was something they had obtained through these two weeks of fighting against the overwhelming pressure put on them.

Facing continuous mockery, they struck back fiercely with each victory.

Although the taunting and mocking would continue, these simple words of support gave Chen Guo the courage to charge on.

August 31st. Happy’s free Internet event came to a stop and the new season of the Glory Pro League was eminent. The actual matches themselves wouldn’t kick-off until Saturday on September 6th, but the transfer period would be over at exactly 0:00 on the first of September.

The titans of the league that remained under the scrutiny of players surprisingly didn’t make any moves as the transfer period came to a close. Not Team Blue Rain, which had lost Yu Feng, nor Tiny Herb which had lost two All-Star level players. After Tiny Herb bought 301 Degrees’ Xu Bin, everyone was waiting for these two teams to replenish their strength with new blood. Who would’ve thought that upon the close of the transfer period, neither team made any sort of announcement about transferring players. For both teams, they only made minimal adjustments to their line-up, but what everyone wanted to see was the transfer of a God!

Among everything that had happened during the summer transfer period, the one team that gained the most attention was Tyranny. Ling Jinyan’s transfer, and Zhang Jiale’s return in addition to Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie who were already present, Tyranny’s line-up was beyond striking. Tacky titles like the Elite Four were thrown about, and the voices of support for Tyranny to win the championships were the loudest.

As for the reigning champions, Samsara, they held the tradition of the champion team, not making any major adjustments to their line-up and keeping their main roster the same. But the purchase of Flying Drops from Tiny Herb would definitely strengthen them.

Even with this, not many people believed in the abilities of the defending champions. Especially for those older players with experience, they knew what would happen if the ace made a mistake in these types of teams. Although Zhou Zekai’s flawless performance gave many people confidence about the coming season, on the official poll for who people thought the next champion would be, Samsara was second to Tyranny.

Blue Rain and Tiny Herb were expected to be third and fourth, respectively. Both teams had lost all-star level players and did not do much to strengthen their line-up. Their projected strength had fallen. Their placing on the poll revealed how much everyone expected of these two teams.

Yet the two teams that couldn’t be ignored were Wind Howl and Hundred Blossoms.

Both the transfers in and out for these teams stood out during the summer transfer period. If they stood out, then they would naturally gain much attention. Looking at their resulting line-ups, they seemed very solid. Wind Howl had the impeccable combination of new generation’s number one brawler, Tang Hao and the top brawler account, Three Hits. In addition, there was also Best Rookie Zhao Yuzhe, who would definitely be useful for the new season. And last up not least was the All Star Fang Rui, who was very familiar with this team. The new season was something to look forward to.

Although Hundred Blossoms let go of both Tang Hao and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, they obtained Yu Feng, allowing for the return of the former number one Berserker account, Falling Scattered Flowers, and provoking nostalgia in those who still recalled the scenes of the old times. Because of this topic, Hundred Blossoms managed to attain a good projected placing. But if one thought about it, they only had one All Star, Yu Feng. Team Void’s Ghostblade duo, and Misty Rain’s Chu Yunxiu and Li Hua, somehow both lost to Hundred Blossoms in the projected placings. It could be seen from this that these projection polls were a bit like the All Star votings, lacking in professionalism and authority. These places weren’t reflective of ability, but rather the attention and hopes players had in them.

On September 1st, team rosters were set. Whether it was the transfer of a bigshot, the switching or replacing of average pro players or rookies from the training camp coming in, they all had to be registered by the first of September. On this day, the team line-up was officially set.

In the last week, Loulan Slash and the others from Heavenly Swords had become much less active on the game.

They were finally members of a pro team, so they had to do some special preparations. And all their effort made in gaining the attention of the masses for the first half of the season bore fruit. Their team, despite being completely new to the league, had a protected ranking of 10. This was the highest any new team had ever gotten.

Along with Heavenly Swords, the other team to enter the league was Team Time, not an unfamiliar face. Team Time was eliminated in the seventh season, but managed to fight their way back into the Pro League through beating their fellow eliminated team, Team Wind Sweep, in season eight’s Challenger League.

With all the rosters set, the Pro League soon announced the match schedule for the new season. From now, the teams would begin discussing tactics. At the same time, the Challenger League for the new season wasn’t any slower. On September 1st, the applications for the Challenger League were officially over. The number of teams competing totalled 14218, over 1000 more than last year. Naturally, this was used by the league as a sign of growth to help advertise themselves.

These 14218 teams would come head to head after being randomly assigned opponents, and after all sorts of different adjustments, there would only be 40 left. These 40 would be the participants of the offline matches and upon making it here, there would be an adjustment to the tournament rules away from single elimination. To make certain that only the best teams would be left, the teams would be split into groups for the next round of eliminations.

In the past, the Challenger League wouldn’t get much attention. Though the teams eliminated from the Pro League would have some fans, they were, in the end, weak teams wouldn’t get that much notice.

Yet this year was a little different. First of all, Excellent Era with three All Stars had somehow became a part of it, and then there was the recently infamous Team Happy.

The first opponents of these teams got some attention, especially Team Happy’s opponent. Since Excellent Era was more or less the most terrifying team in this time’s Challenger League.No matter who the opponent was, looking into them was just a tradition, who would need to care about the opposing side for Excellent Era?

But people did very much care about Happy’s opponent. It was just that most people hoped they would very strong.

With Happy managing to make anyone who doubted or mocked them eat their own words, these people would obviously want Happy to meet their match in the challenger’s league and get eliminated quickly. This way they could have some cathartic relief.

But there were really too many teams called Happy, just trying to find them was a task that would make you cry. But they were persistent to the end, managing to find the Team Happy they were looking for. A glance at Happy’s opponent, Team Global Insomnia.

The world hadn’t gotten insomnia, but those who were hoping for Happy to fall did. What a flippant name, not at all serious. Just by this you could tell that they weren’t anything impressive. Never mind then, let’s just see how the next round goes!

Chapter 802: Challenger League Round 1

Worldwide Insomnia.

After seeing the name of their opponents, everyone in Team Happy was speechless for a long time. A short pause later, Ye Xiu said: "I think our name Team Happy is very very good."

Everyone nodded their heads fervently. To everyone present, an imposing name like Worldwide Insomnia made it hard for them to take things seriously.

Chen Guo searched up this team and looked at their team members. Their classes were all listed out. Public information on teams would only report classes. Anything else you wanted to know would have to be found through the course of the Challenger League. Finding information at the beginning was unrealistic. There were over ten thousand teams. How could you pay attention to them all? Usually, teams would fix onto their own opponents and examine their tactics and strength.

Of course, only teams, which cared about winning the whole thing, would plan meticulously. Teams, which just participated for fun, didn’t need to have such foresight.

After Chen Guo finished looking over the classes of the team members on Worldwide Insomnia, she looked up their final opponents, Team Excellent Era.

Excellent Era may be a powerhouse, but after being relegated, they had no special privilege as a participant in the Challenger League. Of course, because of their fame, the Alliance didn’t mind using them for marketing. But from a tournament format, Excellent Era was just one of the 14,218 teams.

When Chen Guo searched for Excellent Era, she almost fell off her chair.

Too terrible.

Chen Guo stared at the various team names, sighing while laughing.

"Team Universally Unrivaled Relegated Excellent Era", "Excellent Era, I’ve Been Your Rival Since the Day I Was Born", "Excellent Era’s Challenger League Future Is Good"... team names mocking Excellent Era could be found everywhere. These teams definitely weren’t here to seriously participate in the Challenger League. Their entire purpose here was to slander Excellent Era’s name. Powerhouse! Team Excellent Era might have numerous fans, but they did not lack haters either. This type of sharp and unkind conduct invigorated Chen Guo’s spirit of hatred towards Excellent Era.

She actually clicked on these teams and took a look. These were clearly randomly put together teams. When she finally found the real Team Excellent Era, she checked the publicly-released information on the members of Team Excellent Era.

"Hm? Excellent Era has two Battle Mages!" Chen Guo was incomparably familiar with Team Excellent Era’s team composition. However, the familiar names she recognized no longer gave her the same feeling as before. Among these characters, there was an unfamiliar Battle Mage, Combat Form.

"Who’s this?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu. No matter how familiar she was with Excellent Era, she couldn’t be more familiar with it than Ye Xiu. Su Mucheng had returned to her team already, so Chen Guo couldn’t ask her.

"Combat Form….." Ye Xiu saw this character and immediately recognized it.

Qiu Fei. This was the Battle Mage that the Club had given to Qiu Fei. As the previous successor to One Autumn Leaf, Qiu Fei would not have been given a weak character. Now, Qiu Fei’s character was among the team roster. Had he been summoned by the team?

This was the Challenger League. Because of the tournament format, Qiu Fei appearing in the team roster didn’t necessarily mean that he had been given a contract. Team Excellent Era may have added the All Star, Xiao Shiqin, to the team, but they also lost three players this summer. Xiao Shiqin was an All Star and God, but he couldn’t replace three regulars, even with his powerful All Star character, Life Extinguisher.

Excellent Era needed to fill in their vacancies, but as a relegated team, their position was awkward. If they picked pro players from the competitive scene, let alone how many pro players had the same confidence as Xiao Shiqin, signing on players for a considerable price for the Challenger League would seem somewhat excessive.

In the trade for Xiao Shiqin, Excellent Era lost two players, but all of the second-string players were there. As second-string players of a powerhouse like Team Excellent Era, weren’t they already more than good enough to crush some Challenger League opponents? Even if this time’s Challenger League had Ye Qiu, Excellent Era still didn’t need to be so cautious.

Excellent Era had carefully studied Team Happy’s strength. In the beginning, they had been overly wary of Qiao Yifan, but they now knew that he wasn’t some secret weapon. He was leftover trash tossed out by Team Tiny Herb. On the other hand, this type of player would be like treasure to a grassroots team like Team Happy.

Then, there was Tang Rou. During this period of time, she had risen to the spotlight, but at the same time, Excellent Era could conduct thorough analysis of her. When she bullied normal players, it was hard to tell the depth of her skill. However, Excellent Era wasn’t an ordinary group. They had Glory specialists for this type of work. In front of these specialists, Tang Rou’s skill was thoroughly examined.

On the other hand, Steamed Bun was a new sight. No form of strategy could be gleaned from his way of fighting, but his reckless fighting brought down his opponents. His technical skill was quite good, but if he could even beat the trainees from the training camp, that alone wouldn’t cut it. His brainless fighting was truly difficult for these systematically trained experts to figure out.

However, as professionals in a famed team, they wouldn’t be stumped by this problem. In short, after serious analysis by Excellent Era, Team Happy didn’t need to be worried about. No one should be an obstacle to Excellent Era in the entire Challenger League. This was the reason for why they did not wave around money to sign players and only used their team’s current resources. The top second-string players would be promoted to the first-string. The top trainees would be promoted to the second-string.

This method was a healthy way to develop a team, especially when they possessed absolute dominance over their opponents. Letting every level of the team grow was important. As a result, Excellent Era did not do anything during the transfer window, letting them avoid any controversy at the same time. If Excellent Era had signed any players, that may have actually been more astonishing.

Under this background, Qiu Fei and his Battle Mage, Combat Form, became a member of the team. Whether or not there would be others was hard to say because the Challenger League allowed team members to be adjusted at any time before the offline competition stage started.

Numerous players anxiously waited for the opening match of the new season, but before that, the Challenger League would start.

Regular league matches were played every Saturday. The Challenger League matches were played every Friday night, so they wouldn’t conflict with the regular league matches. Online competitions were played in the in-game Arena. The game would specially cut out a section in the Arena dedicated to the Challenger League. Every week, the rooms would be automatically arranged. Teams would be given a room number to look for. The match would need to be played on time for the system to record it.

Last season, Samsara won the finals 3-0, ending the finals quickly. As a result, the Alliance wanted to find a new tournament format to use. Usually, the new tournament format would be tested in the Challenger League, but it seemed like the Alliance had yet to come up with a breakthrough over the summer. The elimination format was announced for the Challenger League, which was no different from the past. Both sides would each play each other on their home stage and then the winner was decided based on the total number of points obtained. As for who would play first or second, there was no record to consult, so it was decided by a flip of the coin.

Friday night, the Challenger League’s first round of matches began. Because this year was different than last year, there were more people paying attention to the Challenger League this year. Excellent Era didn’t need to be said. Even though they were against a weak team made up of random players, loyal fans still came to watch, expressing their support for their team. The Excellent Era room was filled with spectators.

At Happy, even though they had been in the spotlight for half a month, when the Challenger League began, they still received less attention than Excellent Era. However, compared to the other grassroot teams, it was simply no comparison. Moreover, Excellent Era wasn’t the only pro team in the Challenger League. The previous season and previous previous season and even the previous previous previous season had relegated teams that had yet to return to the Alliance. But even their rooms, apart from last season’s second relegated, Team Mysterious Fantasy, couldn’t compare to Happy’s. Even though Team Mysterious Fantasy was a truly weak team, as a team that had been in the pro scene, they had still accumulated a number of fans. Despite getting relegated, many loyal fans still hadn’t given up and still had hopes for their team. They also came to express their support, so their room wasn’t any less lively than Happy’s.

In the room, the competing teams flipped a coin and figured out the order of their home and away games. After the home team chose a map, the spectators would just be waiting for the two sides to start fighting. There was a limit to the preparation time. Once the map was chosen, if a team failed to press ready, the team would automatically forfeit the match.

The first round of the Challenger League had many many teams. All sorts of crazy possibilities could happen. Under the system’s impartial and incorruptible decision, there was no mercy. Who knew how many teams would be forced to forfeit this round. But for ambitious teams like Happy, how could they make such a mistake?

On the other hand, their opponents Worldwide Insomnia only had four players show up at their schedule time. The four players were frantically asking each other where the other two players were. One of them said "He said he’d take a nap in the afternoon. Did he oversleep?" The crowd booed.

Aren’t you Worldwide Insomnia? How ironic was it that your team member overslept!　

In the end, the four couldn’t wait for their two other team members any longer. The Challenger League had lax rules thought. Six players must sign up at registration, but in the actual match, it was fine for four players to participate. However, if four players participated, how could they hope to win according to competition rules?

Under the disappointed gazes of the crowd, Happy easily took their first victory.

Chapter 803: Opening Match

Not a bad start!

Chen Guo was ecstatic, but seeing how everyone else seemed so calm, she knew that this sort of easily-won victory didn’t mean much. In comparison to Happy, the ease at which Team Excellent Era achieved their victory was even more absurd.

After they landed such a terrifying match, Team Excellent Era’s opponent didn’t seem to have any plans to back out. Instead, their members all arrived timely and enthusiastically. Yet upon opening fire, their characters seemed to just be dolls; they weren’t really here to PvP, just here to meet their idols. When they went up against One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher, and Dancing Rain, this was especially obvious. Happily losing while taking every chance to try and kowtow to them made the members of Team Excellent Era feel extremely awkward.

The amount of attention gained by the first round of this season’s Challenger League far overtook any other round in history. But compared with the Pro League match the following day, it was nothing to write home about.

On this day, Chen Guo broadcasted the match like usual, but if the week after the free Internet event had anything to say, it was that Happy Internet Cafe’s business had taken a hit. Their demand had fallen by at least a third, especially the regulars. Many of them never came back. The influence Team Excellent Era had in this area was immense.

Out of the 10 ongoing opening matches, Chen Guo chose the one between Team Samsara and Team Heavenly Sword. This was one of the league’s traditions. Among the opening matches, one would definitely be fought between a new team and the defending champions. Team Heavenly Sword and Team Happy had quite a bit of history, so Loulan Slash had been coming to Ye Xiu anxiously to get advice.

Loulan Slash and his team prepared thoroughly for their match. Things like snatching bosses were allocated to others in the guild. They had become like pro players, not appearing much ingame anymore. For this new team, the Alliance also did some introducing and advertising.

Loulan Slash’s team had eleven members in total. Apart from the core five, there were another six. Even though Ye Xiu had been a part of their group for so long, he had never heard of these people, and had no idea were Loulan Slash had found them. But with Loulan Slash and co as the core members, these six people were just backups, so Ye Xiu knew they wouldn’t be very strong.

The match was on Team Samsara’s turf. One of the major changes made for the new season was upgrading all the screens on hand into holographic projectors. Of course, this wasn’t a decision made lightly, but one long planned by the Alliance. All the major teams had made an investment on this in their stadiums, and these first came to use at All Stars on Team Samsara’s stadium.

This perfected technology received very positive feedback, and the plans they had made for so long finally came to fruition this season. Not just at Samsara, but the projections for all the opening matches flickered on.

With an all new method of viewing, the effect on the spirit of the audience was tangible. The lifelike Glory arena was revealed to them, eliciting the passion of everyone in the audience.

The match between the defending champions and the new team wasn’t anything shocking. Team Heavenly Sword lost with a resounding zero to Team Samsara. Not long after the match, Ye Xiu received a column of tearful emojis from the Team Heavenly Sword five.

"Keep trying!" Ye Xiu could only reply with mild encouragement. Because of the difference in skill, along with nerves from their debuting match, Loulan Slash and co couldn’t perform to expectations. But this first match showed Ye Xiu that there was some depth to these players that he didn’t know of before. Their equipment, upon the start of the official matches, had undergone a complete makeover, including several pieces of Silver equipment. Ye Xiu had no idea how they obtained them.

With solid characters and an understanding of their ability through in-game interaction, Ye Xiu judged that Team Heavenly Sword could count as a mid-tier team in the league. He relayed this conclusion to the five, just to give them a boost in morale.

But the opening match that was the most popular wasn’t this match. Chen Guo broadcasted Loulan Slash’s match out of their friendship. Among the opening matches, it was usually the teams that had undergone major adjustments during the summer transfer period that would catch people’s attention. People would be curious as to how good these new line-ups were.

This, of course, didn’t include Team Samsara and Team Heavenly Sword. Team Samsara simply bought an All Star character to fortify their strength. Yet what they did in the end wasn’t to use the grappler Flying Drops directly, but to salvage its equipment and re-equip their own grappler. It was clear that they weren’t aiming for the account in the first place, but the equipment. A character’s ability was mostly determined by their equipment. With Flying Drops’ undressing, this All Star Grappler would most likely fall from fame. Many fans of this account were furious at Samsara for that they did.

It wasn’t as if Samsara hadn’t taken this into consideration. An All Star character could sometimes bring fame. But Flying drops was, ultimately, not a God-level character like One Autumn Leaf or Desert Dust, so Samsara could make the decision to scrap it, taking its place with their own Grappler account. This sort of move to increase the influence of their own accounts revealed Samsara’s ambitious heart.

But that was all Samsara had done. It was not enough to become a hot topic, especially when looking at Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, whose core line-up had gone through some immense changes. It wasn’t very fresh.

After the end of the opening matches, people had some idea of Team Tyranny’s new style.

Zhang Jiale using Hundred Dazzling Blossoms to fight for Team Tyranny was something no one had ever thought could happen even in their dreams, yet now it had become a reality. The flamboyant hundred blossom style was as eye-catching as ever; some were ecstatic, some were melancholy.

And Ling Jinyan, controlling the brawler character Team Tyranny had specially made for him, was a uniting figure in the team. The people that supported these veterans weren’t small in number, with some who was just here just to see what would happen. They hoped that Team Tyranny would meet Team Hundred Blossoms or Team Wind Howl. These matches that had potential for drama were always more interesting.

Zhou Guanyi from Team Tyranny also gained much attention. In the press conference after the match, the reporters were intent on him, asking if he felt pressure when fighting alongside these Gods. But Team Tyranny was prepared for such questions, and Zhou Guanyi’s reply sounded rehearsed. Obviously, their PR department had gone over this with him. Reporters hated this kind of answer the most, but there was nothing they could do about it.

Team Blue Rain and Team Tiny Herb had both lost All Stars, and had not made any moves to fortify their own strength, yet shocked every everyone in their opening matches.

The most important adjustment Team Blue Rain had made in this season was to take the young 14 year old Lu Hanwen from their training camp, using the account Flowing Clouds he used in-game, and put him down as a core member!

Instant fame.

This phrase could be used perfectly on Lu Hanwen. With one victory in the individual competition and an amazing performance in the team competition, everyone witnessed this 14 year old’s technique and skill.

Everyone immediately placed titles like genius to Lu Hanwen’s name, curious and hopeful about his future performance. It was a shame that he didn’t attend the press conference after. It was clear that Team Blue Rain was very protective of this child.

In contrast, Team Tiny Herb’s Gao Yingjie and his Kind Tree’s debut in Team Tiny Herb’s main roster wasn’t as eye-catching. After all, Gao Yingjie had chances to fight in official matches ever since last season’s All Star Weekend. This season, becoming a core member was just the next step. Though his position on the main team was rather conspicuous; he was taking the place of an All Star, after all.

But this situation was the same fo rTeam Blue Rain. Lu Hanwen was also taking the place of the transferred Yu Feng. In comparison to Gao Yingjie whose debut was carefully planned out and revealed, Lu Hanwen came out completely unexpected, making Team Blue Rain’s actions far more surprising.

The other teams that people were keeping an eye on were Team Hundred Blossoms and Team Wind Howl.

Coming to a new team, getting a new character and becoming a team leader, Tang Hao’s performance in their match was admirable. Under his leadership, his other team members fought spectacularly in their opening match. Like Team Samsara, Team Wind Howl also managed to win with a full 10 points, standing currently in joint first place with Samsara, causing their fans to swell with excitement.

In contrast, Team Hundred Blossoms’ opening match was a terrible embarrassment. Their opponent, Team Misty Rain, didn’t make many changes during the summer transfer; their line-up was stable, as was their performance. They took away 8 points from the match, leaving Team Hundred Blossoms with a measly 2 points. The media, of course, blew things out of proportion. Though they just messed up on the opening match, Hundred Blossoms was described as being in peril, and even being compared with Zhang Jiale’s amazing return.

Among all the topics and debates, the Glory Alliance’s ninth season officially began. And immediately a topic exploded among the players, being something everyone had noticed about this season: veterans and newcomers.

The veterans that had rallied under Team Tyranny’s banner for victory.

The very new, but already core team member and youngest ever pro player, Lu Hanwen.

Just in the opening matches, they had caught everyone’s attention, and were already looking to be the main character’s of the coming season.

With the eruption of such a dramatic Pro League opening round, the spectators of the Challenger League, had decreased. The topics surrounding Happy and whatnot were immediately replaced by Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Wind Howl, Hundred Blossom, etc. After all, this was where the real action was happening!

Chapter 804: Endless Topics

As the opening round came to a close, all sorts of news and topics began to trend.

Although Team Tyranny’s four ace player team made them the highest trending team among players, the single pro-gamer who gained the most attention wasn’t Zhang Jiale, Ling Jinyan, Han Wenqing or Zhang Xinjie.

Lu Hanwen.

Known as this season’s most important transfer of Team Blue Rain, Lu Hanwen. With the departure of an All Star, he directly stepped up to take a place on the main roster. The youngest pro player in the history of Glory.

On the day of the match and under Team Blue Rain’s protection, Lu Hanwen had not attended the press conference. But was it that easy to wave off the enthusiasm of these reporters? After the opening matches, each team received an application for a certain team member to be interviewed, and Lu Hanwen’s popularity rocketed.

Was Lu Hanwen’s ability comparable to a God? Not necessarily, but the halo of being 14 gave him a bonus. Being so strong at merely 14, if he continued improving, wouldn’t his ability be terrifying when his skills matured?

Although Team Blue Rain was protecting their young participant, that didn’t mean they were hiding him from public view completely. Their goal was to let him grow in the best conditions. After the opening matches, Team Blue Rain’s PR department gave Lu Hanwen a few pointers on dealing with the media, and finally agreed to letting him be interviewed. However, the interview wasn’t conducted like the press conference where a myriad of reporters would be fighting for a chance to ask questions. Team Blue Rain instead decided to arrange for someone from the influential ESports Home to conduct an exclusive interview. They would let the two find a quiet place to sit and talk, and Team Blue Rain would go over the draft before it became published.

With this arrangement, they wouldn’t have to fear Lu Hanwen saying anything that could negatively affect his future career due to his lack of experience. And being the most influential eSports media, ESports Home wouldn’t go and irresponsibly publish nonsense to catch the eyes of the people.

Not long afterwards Lu Hanwen’s exclusive interview appeared on the Monday’s ESports Home headlines. Through Q & A, they let the normal players better understand this young pro player.

Vibrant, optimistic, diligent!

This was ESports Home’s final opinion of Lu Hanwen. The Exclusive interview naturally concluded with well-wishes for Lu Hanwen. Meanwhile, this made anticipation swell in the hearts of Glory fans. How much could this young pro player achieve?

Of course, there was plenty more to speak of in the next pages of ESports Home.

Such as those teams who had gone through major adjustments, their style and technique in the opening matches was a hot topic as well. And speaking of style, the rare combination of a class overlap appeared in the opening matches of two powerhouses.

Blue Rain, Tiny Herb.

With Troubling Rain and Vaccaria, two aces among their class, there was somehow another same-class character that appeared in their team battles.

Flowing Cloud, Kind Tree. With the same classes as Troubling Rain and Vaccaria, respectively, the two accounts were being played by the rookies of each team.

A dual class combination was very rare. Only Team Void’s Ghostblade duo was currently active in the league. Sobbing Ghost and Carved Ghost were both Ghostblades. But Ghostblades had their own unique playstyle. Phantom Demons and Sword Demons could more or less be seen as two different classes. Team Void’s Ghostblade Duo had Sobbing Ghost as a phantom demon, while Carved Ghost would switch up his skillset every now and then. Through this, they managed to create a variety of play styles.

For Blue Rain and Tiny Herb, Tiny Herb was alright, since Witches had many styles to choose from. But with Wang Jiexi being known as the Magician, his Vaccaria didn’t use any of the typical play styles of Witch players. Instead, he used a style unique to himself. Vaccaria didn’t have particular skills. He didn’t favor particular skills like the mainstream Body Technique or Magic Tool users. Instead, his skill points were placed into all the different skills. With the limit in skill points, Vaccaria’s skill levels were definitely imperfect, but his skill tree make-up was beyond the comprehension of most.

And Kind Tree, who fought at Vaccaria’s side, wasn’t one of the mainstream Body Technique or Magic Tool accounts either, yet he was also different from Vaccaria, or so the opening match seemed to reveal. From the current analysis, he seemed to uphold Wang Jiexi’s Magician playstyle, but his skill tree was tailored to Gao Yingjie’s personal tastes and habits.

Two unique Witches. What kind of combination would they be able to make? Everyone was trembling in anticipation.

As for Blue Rain, Blade Masters didn’t have that much of a variation. Different players would simply pick different combinations of sword types and skills that were to their liking. Troubling Rain wasn’t as unique as Vaccaria, and Flowing Cloud was even more of a typical Blade Master. What sparks these two class overlaps would create had been analyzed by the media for the opening matches, but it wasn’t thorough; they would have to see over time.

As for those like Tyranny, Hundred Blossoms, Wind Howl.... All the teams would gain reviews from the media after the opening matches. Whether the analysis in these reviews were accurate or not wasn’t something certain, but for normal players, they needed someone more professional than them to analyze the matches and tell them what was truly going on.

In comparison, the Challenger League, which had also finished its opening matches, only got a tiny, negligible place on the ESports Home. In this tiny area, half of it was used to emphasize how incredible this time’s Challenger League was. Then, it mentioned which teams used to belong to the Pro League. With Excellent Era as the top priority, they were given a good bit of praise. As for Happy, they were mentioned too. Though it was just a sentence of "the recently infamous Team Happy easily defeated their opponents, a small team of players, in the first round."

Though it was just one sentence, one could tell that ESports Home was keeping a close eye on Happy. Out of 14218 teams, they were the only team to be specifically named in the small article. Even Excellent Era had just been shoved in with the other struggling pro teams, briefly mentioned as "winning with full points".

Even with that, Chen Guo wasn’t happy when she saw the article. With how hilarious their opponents were, who had two players who didn’t even come, they could write much more! However, among these 14218 teams, there wasn’t a lack of crazy names, Worldwide Insomnia was nothing compared to some of the others out there. As for coming with two people missing, this was a situation too common to count in the first round. Two people was actually considered few, for some teams, no one even turned up. And Worldwide Insomnia managed the same in this round. With not a single point in the first round and knowing how strong the opponent was, they simply decided to not turn up at all for the second round. With that, Team Happy had won against their first opponents.

The next day was the second round of the Pro League. The focus point was, of course, the continuation of the first round. Chen Guo originally wanted to go with the popular choice and broadcast Blue Rain’s match with Lu Hanwen being a focus of the new season. But looking at the match schedule, Blue Rain’s opponents were Conquering Clouds, a bottom-tier team. Going against such a team, the match didn’t seem very interesting. Even if Lu Hanwen performed very well, it wouldn’t really mean much.

So Chen Guo looked to the schedule again and saw that Tyranny was going up against Team Royal Style.

Royal Style had Tian Sen and his Peaceful Hermit, a big name in the Glory scene. Tyranny had four ae players.. This match seemed to be more interesting.

Chen Guo’s choice didn’t disappoint. The level of play shown in this match was very high. The four aces performed stably,, crushing Royal Style’s hopes for victory. Though these four only got together during the summer, they seemed as if they had fought as long-time teammates. The tactical sense of veterans was far greater than what the younger generation could achieve, especially since these four were all the cream of the crop. It was like Tyranny didn’t even need an adjustment period and could already function nigh flawlessly.

In this round, all the powerhouses managed to accomplish a satisfactory victory, apart from Hundred Blossoms. They didn’t seem to be able to find their way yet. Going up against the weak team Clear Splendor, they only managed to get three points.

Two rounds completed. Two weeks passed by in a flash.

The goal for pro players was to win matches. Apart from these matches, there was only training and making sure they had the right attitude for these matches. As for Happy? They were much busier. Apart from training everyday, they would still be going around snatching bosses under Ye Xiu’s leadership.

Loulan Slash and the others from Heavenly Sword weren’t here to help anymore, but the other guilds were still the same. Really, all they had lost was Loulan Slash and the other experts. The other guilds didn’t have pro players helping anymore either. Within two weeks, Ye Xiu and his alliance naturally benefitted. Ye Xiu classified and stored the materials they had gained.

Everything seemed to be going well. But after the end of the current week, came Monday and the names of their next opponents. Happy’s opponent: Team Everlasting.

Compared to all those flashy names, a name like Everlasting was very inconspicuous. Yet with a standard name like this, it seemed to tell of the background of the team.

Team Everlasting, a team eliminated from the Pro League in the seventh season.

In the eighth season’s Challenger League, they fell at the finals.

But they didn’t give up. With the new season and a good start, Team Everlasting and Team Happy somehow managed to draw one another.

This result made many people curl their lips.

But after a while, those who wanted to see Happy humiliated cheered.

As for Happy, with Wei Chen representing them, their complexions weren’t so good.

Though they had been eliminated, Team Everlasting was still a team from the Pro League. With the two years spent there, they had some experience. No matter what, they were miles stronger than Worldwide Insomnia.

Chen Guo shot Ye Xiu a worried glance. At times like these, she needed to find confidence from Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu didn’t disappoint her, smiling upon seeing the matchup. "Not Excellent Era, huh? Not bad!"

Chapter 805: A Little Frivolous

Team Everlasting.

Team Everlasting became a pro team when they joined the Pro League in Season 5. They had stayed for three years before being eliminated from the league. For three years, 15th was the best ranking they had achieved, so they had never been an outstanding team.

But when they were placed in the Challenger League, they were enough to triumph over all. The resulting champions of the Challenger League were monopolized by these types of teams every year.

Even though they didn’t have any God in their team, they managed to mingle around in the professional circle for three years, so at least they were qualified pro players. Although there weren’t many Silver equipment for their characters, they had some. They were much stronger than Team Happy, who only had two petty Silver weapons. Furthermore, apart from the Silver equipment, every other equipment was Orange. This was something Happy couldn’t compare with. Team Happy’s characters still had crappy Purple equipment, which weren’t up to standard placed in the pro scene.

It was only because of Excellent Era this year. Otherwise, such team would be the final boss, like how they were in the past. Team Happy was far from lucky finding them only in the second round. Perhaps only people like Ye Xiu would bring up Excellent Era to compare.

However, they couldn’t underestimate Team Everlasting’s strength. This round wouldn’t be easy.

"At least we can get some equipment. Even though we can’t get Silver equipment, we can get Orange equipment somehow." Chen Guo spoke. As for the method, she had already come up with one. There was only one way to collect a full set of equipment in a short time - using money!

Silver equipment might not be purchasable, but Orange equipment was different. This was something that circulated around normal players, so this matter was achievable if one were willing to spend money.

"Mm," Ye Xiu seemed to agree with Chen Guo’s opinion and nodded. "Does anyone have any friends or relatives that could lend us some Orange equipment?"

"Huh?" Chen Guo was stunned. She never thought that they would be borrowing the equipment. Borrowing equipment for a match? Why did it feel extremely dodgy and frivolous?

"Do you have any friends that can lend us some?" Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo.

"I... don’t..." Chen Guo stammered. After thinking about it for a bit,, Chen Guo realised that she didn’t have any. It wasn’t as if she didn’t have any friends, it was because none of her close friends had any Orange equipment. For strong professional teams, Orange equipment was only used to fill in the gaps, but for the majority of players in the game, it was very rare. It couldn’t be helped. They were in two different leagues, so how they viewed things would be different, too.

"I’ll see if Loulan Slash has any!" Ye Xiu said and actually took action. He called for Loulan Slash on QQ. "Comrade Lou, do you have any equipment we can borrow?"

Loulan Slash was now an official pro player, so his name would be revealed to the public. His full name was Lou Guanning. He was both Team Heavenly Sword’s boss and captain. After the first two rounds of the season, Team Heavenly Swords received lots of criticism. People believed that Team Heavenly Swords was merely the toy of a rich person. Normal players only played Glory online. However, the temperament of rich people would be different. They could just spend money to create a team and send themselves into the pro scene to play.

But wouldn’t this method bring humiliation onto themselves? Did they really think money was all powerful?

Many players mocked them in such a manner. This was because judging from the two matches, Team Heavenly Sword’s performance was kind of terrible. They only got one point and was ranked last in the team ranking.

Lou Guanning was frustrated about it! After Ye Xiu’s lesson, they had adjusted their mindset. Their goal was no longer exaggerated and unrealistic. But the current drop in expectations was too great. Putting the ranking aside, it was even hard to gain one point. It just so happened that no one had a clue or idea for a solution.

The five members of Heavenly Swords gathered together for their Monday meeting in order to discuss about how they should digest the pain they received in the past two weeks. After the introduction to the meeting, all five became silent. Lou Guanning had nothing to say himself, so he got bored and logged onto QQ. The moment he logged on, he saw God messaging him.

"Borrowing equipment? What equipment?" Lou Guanning replied with no spirit.

"Pro equipment! Our opponent next round is a bit troublesome." Ye Xiu replied.

"Every opponent we are up against is troublesome." Lou Guanning said absent-mindedly. Evidently, he didn’t think much about Ye Xiu’s words, so he carelessly chatted with Ye Xiu to pass the time.

"I saw your match. The first step is always the hardest!" Ye Xiu said.

"We have made mental preparations, but we never knew it would be this difficult." Lou Guanning replied.

"Your first two opponents were quite strong. That’s a fact." Ye Xiu said.

Team Heavenly Sword’s first opponent was Team Samsara. This had been set up intentionally this season. Sure enough, Team Heavenly Sword was annihilated. As for their second match, they faced off against Team Misty Rain.

Even though Team Misty Rain was never counted as a powerhouse, they were able to eliminate Team Tyranny and become one of the top four last season. It would be easy for them to deal with a team that have just joined the league.

However, Team Heavenly Sword had a good start in the first match. They had won the first round in the individual competition and received their first point ever. This helped increase their momentum and boost their morale. But soon, they were brought back to their original shape and returned to the situation of their first match. They failed to win any of the following nine points.

The victory of winning the first point from the single match was completely forgotten due to their miserable mood. But Ye Xiu just had to bring up that match at this moment. "Didn’t you guys win a round? It shows that it’s not because of your skills, but because you’re not used to it. The feeling of fighting in a professional match is different from fighting with players in the regular arena, right?"

"Different indeed." Lou Guanning admitted.

"Feeling a bit nervous is unavoidable, it will get better when you grow used to it. Everyone experiences this stage." Ye Xiu said.

"Were you nervous when you fought in your first match?" Lou Guanning asked.

"Of course." Ye Xiu said.

"But your performance was still so good." Lou Guanning was pretty clear about Ye Xiu’s record.

"Mm... That was because everybody’s human, so I reckon my opponents were more nervous than me." Ye Xiu said.

"Haha..." Lou Guanning didn’t reply, but actually laughed out loud. The other four immediately gazed at him with puzzlement. Their eyes carried all sorts of blame, expressing how could he possibly laugh at a time like this? He wasn’t focused at all!

"It’s God!" Lou Guanning turned his computer’s screen around for the other four to see their conversation.

The four knew who Lou Guanning meant as "God". Countless of people were called "God" in the professional circle, but for the people in Team Heavenly Swords, if one simply said "God", they definitely meant Ye Qiu.

In the chat, Ye Xiu didn’t say any comforting or encouraging words, he merely pointed out their current problem. Even though he didn’t give them any helpful solutions, they learned that this was something every pro player would have to experience. They were just like everyone else. There were no exceptions. Just because there was no exception, it made it seem as if they didn’t need to feel crestfallen about it.

The mood unexpectedly turned better. Lou Guanning finally realised that Ye Xiu didn’t find him to talk about this matter. He hastily went back to the original topic on his own initiative. "God, you mentioned that you needed to borrow equipment?"

"Pro equipment, as pro as it can be!" Ye Xiu said.

"Are you telling me that you would like to borrow our current Silver equipment?" Lou Guanning asked.

"If I can, I wouldn’t mind!" Ye Xiu said.

Lou Guanning almost planted his face into the table, he was stupefied before replying. "Would the rules allow us to?"

"As far as I know, there are no terms prohibiting it." Ye Xiu said.

"Outside of the transfer window, it is prohibited to transfer characters, but I think equipment can be." Evidently, Lou Guanning had done his research.

"Mm, speaking of this, where did you get your Silver equipment from?" Ye Xiu gossiped.

"I bought it!"

"How secretive." Ye Xiu said.

"Thanks for the compliment."

"Then quickly give it to me to use." Ye Xiu didn’t have any reservations. At the start, he didn’t plan to borrow their Silver equipment. He only thought that if they had any Orange equipment in their guild’s storeage, he could borrow and return it after this match. But Lou Guanning brought up this topic himself, and Ye Xiu thought that the proposal wasn’t bad, so he happily accepted it.

Chen Guo, who watched beside him, was stupefied. Ye Xiu was just borrowing equipment! But now he managed to get Silver equipment, without having any reservations at all! She didn’t know if Team Heavenly Swords would lend them the equipment or not.

Chen Guo was kind of looking forward to it. They wasn’t any competition between the two teams, and their competition dates weren’t the same. It wouldn’t affect Team Heavenly Swords too much if they lended their equipment, unless Team Heavenly Swords was a faceslapping group who felt uncomfortable towards Team Happy and wanted Team Happy to be tormented. But Team Heavenly Swords was not only not a faceslapping group, they were quite close. To lend their equipment at this time... seemed, quite possible?

Chen Guo was a bit excited, she waited with Ye Xiu for the reply while she spoke with excitement. "Hey... If it’s like this, can you find other pro teams to borrow equipment from? You know all of them!"

"I do know them, but not their boss." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo understood at once. Lou Guanning was both the player and boss, so he was able to make the decision. As for other teams, the pro players obviously didn’t have such power, so making such a request would be difficult for them.

In actual fact, wasn’t it the same for Team Heavenly Swords? When Lou Guanning told the other four what Ye Xiu had said, they were at a complete loss. They weren’t mentally prepared for such request! By rights, judging from with their relationship and that there weren’t any conflicts, there wouldn’t be a problem in lending them the equipment. But... why did it feel a little frivolous?

Borrowing equipment to play a match... Did they just make history in the pro scene.

"What classes do you guys have?" Lou Guanning finally started to take practical action.

"Don’t mind about that, just give us everything! Lord Grim could wear what’s left over." Ye Xiu replied.

Lou Guanning’s face was covered in tears at once. Unspecialised was truly great!

Chapter 806: Equipment Finalized

Team Heavenly Swords was indeed wealthy. Relying on money, they were actually able to purchase 20 pieces of Silver equipment. Their five characters equipped them all. Not a single one was hidden, but because of their classes, the equipment was not evenly distributed among each character. In the end, their Berserker Loulan Slash had 5, their Battle Mage Homeward Bound also had 5, their Grappler Night Tide had 4, their Cleric Thousand Falling Leaves had 4, and their Elementalist Ocean Ahead only had 2.

Relatively speaking, 2 or 5 Silver pieces of equipment on a character wasn’t a lot. In Glory, characters could equip a total of 12 pieces of equipment. Loulan Slash and Homeward Bound had the most Silver equipment in the team, but it was still only five. It wasn’t even halfway to a full set.

This type of Silver equipment coverage was considered lacking in the current pro scene. According to last season’s statistics, the average number of Silver equipment on a character was 5.23. Team Heavenly Swords only had a maximum of five on each character, let alone six other characters not having even a single piece.

Team Heavenly Swords wasn’t the only team lacking Silver equipment. In reality, for a new team in the Alliance, obtaining 20 Silver equipment was already very impressive. Silver equipment was not something that could be bought simply with money.

Take Team Heavenly Sword’s 20 Silver equipment. Lou Guanning let Ye Xiu take a look. Ye Xiu knew that these weren’t considered top quality goods in the pro scene.

During the process of creating a Silver equipment, there would be many that would fail to meet expectations. These pieces of equipment would still be used to continue to perfect them. After perfecting them, the earlier unsatisfactory prototypes would be removed. These prototypes might be given to characters in the team that needed equipment or sold to other teams. It depended on how each team wanted to do business.

Ye Xiu did not ask where Team Heavenly Swords obtained these pieces of equipment. Lou Guanning had laid the equipment out for him to see, implying that he agreed to let Ye Xiu borrow them temporarily.

20 Silver equipment.

3 weapons, 12 armor, and 5 accessories.

Ye Xiu checked the stats on each one and got a rough idea of how he should distribute them.

"Apart from the Grappler glove, lend the others to me!" Ye Xiu said.　　

There was a Battle Mage, Cleric, and Grappler weapon.

Team Happy had a Battle Mage and Cleric, so those could not be missed. For the Grappler glove, Steamed Bun’s Brawler could also use it, but gloves didn’t suit Brawlers. Gloves were specialized weapons for Grapplers, so to a Brawler, a Silver glove might not be as good as an Orange claw.

Of the 20 Silver equipment, Ye Xiu wanted to borrow 19 of them. It would be a lie to say that Lou Guanning didn’t hesitate to lend them out, but in the end, he trusted Ye Xiu. As a result, these equipment were lent to Ye Xiu just like that.

But Lou Guanning said that they still needed to use them during practice, so they would give them to Happy on Friday before their match.

"This….. Could you lend them to us a day before to give us time to familiarize ourselves with them?" Ye Xiu negotiated with Lou Guanning. Equipment undoubtedly affected a character’s strength. A character with different equipment would feel different to play on. Thus, it was best to practice using the equipment that would be worn in matches. That was why when a player switched to a new club and received a new character, he needed to get used to the character.

When Happy borrowed these pieces of equipment, the strength of their character’s would increase, but if the player wasn’t used to it and couldn’t play properly, that would be disastrous. Ye Xiu wanted everyone to try out the equipment first. If the equipment wasn’t suitable, it would be better to wear their original equipment. No matter how powerful a character was, a player needed to be able to use their equipment to the fullest potential. If the player couldn’t even utilize their equipment, even a God-level character wouldn’t be of help.

Lou Guanning didn’t need Ye Xiu to explain this type of logic to him. He had already agreed to lend them the equipment. If he insisted on lending the equipment to them at the final moment, he would seem too selfish and insincere. As a result, Lou Guanning happily replied, concluding this matter by saying that it was a must.

After making this decision, Lou Guanning did not wait for Ye Xiu to say anything and asked: "There’s only this many Silver equipment. What about Orange equipment? Do you guys need anything?"

"Yeah... if we could get a full set for each character, we would be most thankful." Ye Xiu said.

"Okay….." Lou Guanning felt a bit speechless. He had lent out Silver equipment though, how could Orange equipment compare to that? Speaking of which, Lou Guanning was a little curious. What made Ye Xiu feel like he needed to borrow equipment?

"Right, who’s your opponent?" Lou Guanning asked.

"Team Everlasting." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh! That’s the team that was relegated two years ago, right?" Loulan Slash had an impression of this team.

"Yeah." Ye Xiu said.

"Good luck!" Lou Guanning’s Team Heavenly Swords had only 1 point. The team sat at the bottom of the Alliance. He couldn’t really be looking down on relegated teams. Even more so when considering the fact that Team Everlasting had survived in the Alliance for three years. Lou Guanning felt like this team might have even more Silver equipment than his own patched together team. He just didn’t know if this team was the same as before after being outside of the Alliance for two years.

"Wasn’t I the one who came here to wish you luck?" Ye Xiu replied back with a smiley face.

"Which classes do you need? I’ll help you take a look." Lou Guanning was quite a hero.

The equipment was settled after a few minutes…...

Relying on the power of money, Team Heavenly Swords was truly quite impressive. They had accumulated numerous pieces of orange equipment. A full set for each player in a team was not a problem. Even if their guild didn’t have any, anyone in their team could have their equipment peeled away! In any case, it was just borrowing.

"Done!" Ye Xiu let out a sigh of relief, after finalizing all of the equipment with Lou Guanning.

"We….. can’t keep borrowing the entire way through, right?" Chen Guo was speechless.

"Yeah, when we face Excellent Era, we’re going to need more. Once we enter the pro scene, we might not even be able to borrow any." Ye Xiu said.

"Then for now, is this enough?" Chen Guo asked.

"Let’s get a read on our opponents first before trying to decide anything!" Ye XIu said and immediately searched for information on Team Everlasting.

As a team that had been in the Alliance for three years, there was plenty of official match recordings to look through. Some of those were a bit outdated though and might not be as valuable now. Fortunately, Team Everlasting had reached the finals of the Challenger League last season. Once the Challenger League reached the later stages and the offline matches started, the Alliance would also do some marketing. Some teams might even be streamed online. A team that had reached the finals would certainly have a lot of data accumulated. Ye Xiu searched around and found quite a lot of information. He began taking a look.

Wei Chen didn’t need to be called over. He had come to Ye Xiu. The two studied the material and quietly discussed it with each other. All of the VODs on Team Everlasting were watched.

After dinner, everyone gathered together. Ye Xiu was planning on saying a few words about Team Everlasting.

The living room in their residence was arranged in the same way as their practice room at Happy Internet Cafe. Everyone was familiar with the orientation. The projector screen rolled down, and clips of Team Everlasting’s matches in the Challenger League began playing.

"These are Team Everlasting’s six main classes: Spellblade, Elementalist, Qi Master, Warlock, Cleric, and Launcher." After what seemed like a short trailer showcasing their classes, Ye Xiu introduced each of the six characters that appeared, which comprised of Team Everlasting’s main roster.

"What are your thoughts on this team composition?" Ye XIu wasn’t going to tell them everything. These rookies needed to learn how to think for themselves. They couldn’t keep relying on Ye Xiu and Wei Chen.

"They don’t have a single completely melee class. All of them have strong long-ranged AoE skills. For a dungeon, this type of team composition is quite good for a One Wave Rush strategy..." An Wenyi replied. He was more familiar with Glory than Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. He had strong observational skills too. He could easily see things as simple as this.　　

Ye Xiu nodded his head: "That’s their team’s specialty. They like clumped-up fights. Last season, the core attacker of their team was this player."

Ye Xiu said. Another clip was played. In this clip, everyone in the team coordinated with the Spellblade to attack.

"Next, these types of map coverage attacks are clearly something that they practice. I’ll let you guys see it for yourself. In a bit, I’ll explain it in more detail. This type of attack is most likely what we’ll need to be ready to face." Ye Xiu said. This time, the opponents were different. A pro team would develop their own unique style. At this moment, undergoing practice specifically to counter it was the most effective for the rookies.

On the projector screen, the battle continued. As Ye Xiu said before, he did not immediately start to analyze it. When this part of the video stopped, he chose a random part in the middle and played it, while asking everyone: "Do you guys have any thoughts?"

"Over here... the core doesn’t seem to be the Spellblade?" Qiao Yifan had the most experience in the competitive scene out of all the youths here. It was just that in Team Tiny Herb, he had a habit of being cautious with everything he said. However, after being with Team Happy for so long, especially playing with everyone every day, he realized how improper a lot of their ways were, so he gradually began having more courage to speak his opinions.

"Who is the core then?" Ye Xiu asked.

Qiao Yifan immediately felt like he had said too much and felt too scared to answer. But seeing how Ye Xiu wasn’t looking at him with reproach, he finally mustered up the courage: "Is it... the Launcher?" He still wasn’t confident.

"Yes, that’s correct." Ye Xiu nodded his head, "The Launcher is leading the attack here. Tactics are flexible to some extent. If a tactic is so rigid that only a single core could execute it, that would be too easy for the opponent to beat."

Just the comment "that’s correct" made QIao Yifan feel excited. Just when he was about to say something more, someone suddenly said: "That Team Samsara. Aren’t they being led by a just a single core?"

Everyone was astonished hearing this voice because it belonged to Mo Fan!

Chapter 807: Team Everlasting

Mo Fan had joined Happy for over a month now, and he was still the same as he was when he came. During this time, only Su Mucheng could cause him to change his attitude. And now that Su Mucheng had already gone back to the Club, Mo Fan just sat in front of a row of laptops, not speaking to anyone. He seemed very isolated.

But here, he had food, water and shelter, computers to game on, and no intentions to leave. With Happy being challenged by all sort of people, and now with the official matches, he hadn’t even participated once.

The Challenger League was critical to Team Happy. For it, An Wenyi hadn’t even checked in with his school yet, and it was already late September. Not soon after Su Mucheng returned to her team, Luo Ji also returned to school. In contrast, An Wenyi remained at Happy, telling them that there wasn’t anything he had to do at school anyways.

Everyone was focused on and high-strung about the Challenger League. Although Luo Ji wasn’t there personally, he knew with his ability that he wouldn’t be of any help, but he was still very concerned with how things were progressing. Only Mo Fan never seemed to care. If it wasn’t for the fact that there was an extra set of cutlery on the table at mealtimes, most people would probably forget that he existed.

And now, the tactics meeting regarding Team Everlasting, in the practice room also known as ex-first floor common room, began. Who would’ve thought that at such a time Mo Fan would speak up, and ask a very much legitimate question. But when on earth did this guy start paying attention to the Pro League? He could even not only name Samsara’s team name, but also their play style!

Chen Guo’s heart soared. She believed that with him being here day after day, he finally was influenced by the atmosphere. Something he originally had no interest in, he was finally starting to take part.

Ye Xiu, like everyone else, was surprised by this turn of events. He glanced at Mo Fan and asked, "You actually know Samsara?" Mo Fan lips thinned, refusing to answer such a useless question.

Ye Xiu smiled and then said, "What Samsara is like, you have to find out from watching their matches, not just through the media.""..."

"By the way, do you know who’s at the core of Samsara?" Ye Xiu then asked.

"Zhou Zekai." Who knew where Mo Fan managed to learn this information?

"And his account?" Ye Xiu continued to ask.

"..." Mo Fan once again stopped speaking. Whether it was because he didn’t know or felt like Ye Xiu’s question was an insult to his IQ, they didn’t know.

"Cloud Piercer." Ye Xiu didn’t care if he knew or not, introducing this character to him anyways. After that, he dismissed the topic and returned to Team Everlasting.

Towards Mo Fan, when he hadn’t wanted to join, Ye Xiu was very persistent. Hunting him down and killing him in game all the time, and even getting Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie to help him, backing the guy into a corner.

Yet when Mo Fan actually came to Happy, he was completely let go of. Ye Xiu barely even talked to him. Most people would just leave out of boredom facing this lack of presence, but Mo Fan was used to this lonely lack of interaction and stayed for all this time. The only thing Ye Xiu did was give him a training plan to help him improve his playing abilities. After doing this training, he was constantly improving.

Apart from that, no one went to care about his will, but being in this environment everyday, Mo Fan witnessed and heard all sorts of things about Glory, He wasn’t someone who was completely isolated from his environment, he had thoughts and ideas, he just didn’t express them.

But there was one thing that Ye Xiu knew for certain he was right about: Mo Fan loved Glory. Though the path he chose in the game diverged from the typical player, it was still a part of this game. The Pro League was also another way to play Glory; it was a way of showing off your skills on a higher stage.

It might seem like Ye Xiu had zero interactions with Mo Fan, but this didn’t mean he wasn’t keeping an eye on him.

Mo Fan’s daily practice was something that he often paid attention to. With the attitude Mo Fan held towards this practice, it could be seen that he definitely wished to improve his skills. With better skills, the online game wouldn’t be able to hold his attention for much longer and becoming interested in the Pro League was inevitable. And now, the idea had been planted in his head, so Mo Fan started paying attention to this topic. He could understand and pose questions to the topics Ye Xiu discussed.

But Ye Xiu didn’t give him a direct answer. Compared to being lectured, fighting for what you wanted was far more interesting, especially for Mo Fan whose interest had just started to appear.

Ye Xiu then introduced Team Everlasting’s techniques and combinations to everyone. After that, he sent everyone the recording for this part.

"There’s not much time left, so work hard, everyone." Ye Xiu said at last. He knew how to counter Team Everlasting’s tactics and combos and explained it to the best of his ability, but how much they understood was all on them. The tides of a match could change in a split second. To understand someone’ tactics was to understand their ideas and adapt to fight back against it, not memorize the form of attacks that you saw.

Having Tang Rou and Steamed Bun accomplish this was a bit too much; their tactical understanding wasn’t that good yet!

After explaining the team battle, something also had to be said about the individuals in the team. The only problem was, were Team Everlasting’s team members the same as the season prior?

From the information they found on the registered accounts, they had two that were different from last year. Clearly, some changes had been made over the summer, but a change in accounts didn’t necessarily mean a change in players. If the player changed, then talking about how to deal with them was a fruitless task.

So in the end, Ye Xiu didn’t talk too much about any of the individual styles of the players, and just analyzed the characters that were still in the team from last year.

Not long after, this pre-match strategy meeting came to an end and the others rushed off to prepare. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, was still looking over Team Everlasting’s match recordings, trying to find anything that he might have missed.

A day passed, only three full days were left until the match on Friday.

Yet on this Tuesday afternoon, Chen Guo received a call from the Happy Internet Cafe. They said that there was someone here to see the boss, something about talking business.

"What business? The Internet cafe isn’t lacking anything right now. Let them leave a business card, if we need anything we’ll find them later!" Chen Guo had thought that they were some sort of salesmen and had no heart to be concerned about that kind of thing.

"They said they’re from Team Everlasting, and that we just had to tell you this name." The employee manning the counter relayed to his boss.

"Team Everlasting?" Chen Guo paused, looking to Ye Xiu and pointing at her phone, "Team Everlasting came knocking."

"What arrogance! Steam Bun, let’s go deal with them!" Ye Xiu hadn’t even had a chance to reply when Wei Chen jumped up. Steamed Bun immediately put down his computer and swiftly charged into his room. After a while, he came out empty-handed and charged into the kitchen to find "them".

"At the Internet cafe?" Ye Xiu ignored the idiots making a ruckus.

"Yeah!"

"I’ll go with you to check it out!" Ye Xiu stood.

"Do you need us to come with you?" Wei Chen stood, too.

"Don’t worry and continue training. We only need me to go and take a look." Ye Xiu said.

"If anything happens, tell us," Wei Chen replied with an air of severity.

"Heheh," Ye Xiu laughed shortly and left with Chen Guo.

Happy Internet Cafe. As soon as the two arrived, an employee immediately came to meet them. There were two visitors in total, and they had been taken to one of the rooms on the second floor under Chen Guo’s command.

Chen Guo asked the employee a few more questions, but didn’t get any important information. The two then went up stairs, and pushed open the door to the room. The people sitting on beanbags, talking, stopped at once and turned their heads to look.

Ye Xiu and Chen Guo hadn’t even looked closely at these people when they simultaneously stood up. The one closer to them greeted them with a smile, directing his words mostly at Chen Guo. "I assume you’re the boss, Ms. Chen? Greetings, I’m the team leader of Team Everlasting, He An."

Team leader referred to the manager of the club, an outdated sort of title. Those who were used to being called such usually had some experience in the Pro League. When He An referred to himself as team leader, anyone could tell he felt superior. It was clear that he wasn’t here to boast about his position, but happy that he could use this title to tell the person standing in front of him: I’m no rookie, I’m an experienced veteran.

Yet this "veteran" was very much a stranger to Ye Xiu. In contrast, it was the person next to him that seemed much more familiar to Ye Xiu. He just couldn’t seem to remember his name. There were over 200 people in the Pro League, and those were just the ones currently active. With all the players who came and went, joining and leaving, the number of people involved was far more than that. How could you expect him to remember all of them? But if he felt like this person was familiar, then it was probably someone that Ye Xiu had personally met. He could guess that this was probably a member of Team Everlasting and they had probably played each over in a pro match before?

Thinking of this, Ye Xiu suddenly remembered. He didn’t know the guy’s name, but he knew his identity, so he smiled and said, "Hey, I recognize you! Aren’t you Team Everlasting’s vice-captain?"

"It’s captain now." It was the team leader who spoke up, taking a closer look at Ye Xiu. Then he looked back at the captain. "You know each other?"

That person’s expression had twisted a little. He understood his team leader’s little problem, but today your boasting of your experience has dug yourself a pit.

"He’s God Ye Qiu." The vice-captain introduced with a hint of exasperation.

That’s right, God Ye Qiu.

Boasting about being experienced in Glory in front of God Ye Qiu, that wasn’t being an old veteran, that was being senile!

Chapter 808: The Feeling of Superiority of a Pro Team

After this introduction, the original cheerful mood had disappeared and Captain He An’s mouth hung wide open. For a moment, he didn’t know what to say. He obviously knew what a huge embarrassment this was.

Fortunately, he had only flaunted with body language and not with words, so it was easier to salvage the situation. He An coughed lightly, adjusted his appearance, and calmly greeted Ye Xiu.

"Hi, have a seat!" Ye Xiu smiled, but didn’t say too much.

Everyone took a seat. Chen Guo spoke first. She didn’t make any excessive small talk and directly went to the point: "What business do you two have with us?"

"Haha." He An laughed. Facing Ye Xiu, he had retracted his previous aura of superiority. But when facing Chen Guo, a trace of disapproval and disdain flashed across his face. He just happened to let the other side see. He clearly didn’t think much of a grassroots owner like Chen Guo.

"God Ye Qiu, are you really part of Team Happy?" This guy actually ignored Chen Guo and directly started talking with Ye Xiu.

What’s up with this guy?!

Chen Guo often had to interact with other people. How could she not be able to discern what he thought of her through his body language? He An’s undisguised contempt made her furious. However, He An was very polite to Ye Xiu. Chen Gou really wanted to flip a table for the other side to think it over, but she could only quietly endure it.

"Yeah." Ye Xiu replied bluntly to the other side’s question.

"What a shame." He An slapped his leg.

"Oh? Why do you say that?" Ye Xiu already knew the answer, but seeing how He An was treating them like bugs, he could guess what He An was going to say.

Sure enough, he said in an arrogant tone: "For someone of your skill, staying in a place like this is truly a pity!"

"Hey, what did you say?" If Chen Guo could still endure it, she wasn’t Chen Guo.

He An just laughed. His expression indicated that someone of his status didn’t need to heed the words of someone of low status. He ignored Chen Guo and said to Ye Xiu: "This season’s Challenger League is different than the past. With a giant like Excellent Era, it really is quite troublesome. In times like these, shouldn’t we consider putting our strength together?"

"Oh? What are you saying?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I’ve been paying attention to your recent performance. There are few players who are quite good. I believe all of them have been coached by you, but please forgive me for speaking bluntly, your players have the skill, but your characters are too lacking, no?"

"Then what are your thoughts?" Ye Xiu asked.

"This is the reason for us coming today. Even though our Team Everlasting isn’t considered a strong team, our resources are still much greater than Happy’s. If our two sides join hands, it would be as if a tiger had grown wings, a win-win situation for both sides. Competitive Glory is like horse racing and auto racing. Having a good rider or a good vehicle isn’t good enough. Both a good rider and a good vehicle must be present. God Ye Qiu, you’re being held back by your characters! Why not join our Team Everlasting? Over here, we can definitely provide resources far surpassing what Happy can provide. If you want to topple Excellent Era, this is a necessary move!"

He An was a talented person. His pitch was excellent in voice and in expression. Even Chen Guo was nervous after listening to it because his words were very logical. Chen Guo could not provide the team with too many resources. Everything required Ye Xiu to manage from the ground up. It would be much more convenient if he directly joined a team.

The format of the Challenger League could not prevent teams from running over to recruit people from the opposing team. Once she thought about the other team’s background as a pro team, Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel lacking in confidence. For a moment, she forgot her anger.

"Ha ha, you’re too right." Ye Xiu nodded his head. His high praise gave Chen Guo a fright. He An was already smiling exuberantly. He gave a glance to his partner, implying: "Look, just what I expected."

But Ye Xiu continued: "But in order for a tiger to grow wings, why not have your Team Everlasting join our Team Happy?"

"Hahaha, of course... yes... hm? God, you’re not joking?" He An quickly responded. Fortunately, he realized what had been said midway and was stumped.

"In either case, a tiger would still be growing wings, no?" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Yes, like a tiger growing wings! Hurry and join our Team Happy!" Chen Guo regained her composure faster than He An. She was actually able to stifle a laugh and speak in a serious tone!

He An’s expression turned ugly. At this point, there was really no point in talking any further. The other side had already expressed his refusal in a mocking manner at that. He An couldn’t understand. With Team Happy’s current circumstances, did he really think the team had much of a future?

"God." He An shouted. His tone became tougher. In his eyes, Team Everlasting was the stronger side. Coming over on their own accord to talk about matters was already a sign of respect. So what if you’re a God? You’ve never heard of the saying, a featherless phoenix is no better than a chicken? Without a powerful character, you’re not a God.

He An felt like he had given the other side an opportunity, but not only did the other side not treasure it, he mocked them. He couldn’t bear it. He shouted solemnly and his tone turned heavy: "I hope that you’ll carefully consider this opportunity. You’d better not regret it."

"Honestly, that’s what I should be saying to you." Ye Xiu replied.　　

"You!" He An was furious. Ye Qiu was worthy of his title as one of the Gods. However, did he really think that his status was enough for Team Everlasting to bow down? Isn’t that too arrogant?

Who would have thought that Ye Xiu would look at him seriously: "I’m not joking. I’m very serious. Carefully consider it!"

"After next week, you’ll be regretting today’s decision." He An continued to say.

"After next week, you can still continue to consider today’s proposal." Ye Xiu laughed.

"We’re leaving!" He An got up and called out to his team’s captain.

This poor captain. Apart from introducing God Ye Qiu to He An, he didn’t seem to be of any use. He had come over to recruit, but he didn’t think it would end so quickly. The captain got up helplessly and followed after He An. From beginning to end, he wasn’t even able to introduce himself.

"Take care! We won’t be seeing you out!" Chen Guo was feeling great! She didn’t forget to give the other side another kick. When He An heard her words, he turned his head around, gave a glare, and humphed. His sense of superiority and contempt was still there. However this time, he had included Ye Xiu into it. He didn’t feel like he had done anything wrong. He felt like Ye Xiu valued himself too highly and actually ignored his win-win proposal.

"You’ll regret it." He An finally threw out. When he said "you’, he always referred to Ye Xiu alone and not anyone else. From start to finish, he never took Chen Guo seriously.

He An and that captain left just like that. Chen Guo let out a sigh of relief and was beaming with joy when she looked at Ye Xiu. She really liked today’s Ye Xiu. It was too unexpected.

"Boss, what’s with that expression?" Ye Xiu felt his blood run cold, seeing Chen Guo’s sweet smile.　　

"You made a fool of that arrogant guy. That was too beautiful!" Chen Guo expressed.

"Oh? I did?" Ye Xiu said.

"You’re still pretending!" Chen Guo gave Ye Xiu a punch.

"No, no. I was being serious." Ye Xiu said.

"Serious about what?" Chen Guo didn’t understand.

"I was really hoping that they would consider joining Team Happy." Ye Xiu said.

"How could that be possible?" Chen Guo cried out.

Yes. Even though that guy’s condescending gaze disgusted Chen Guo, she had to admit that, in the Challenger League, a pro team had the qualifications to be arrogant. He was even quite polite to Ye Xiu in the beginning. It was only when Ye Xiu started mocking him did he become impolite. That type of team join Team Happy? Chen Guo wouldn’t dare to think of it even in her dreams.

"Nothing is impossible." Ye XIu said and headed out.

"Hey hey, what do you mean? Speak clearly!" Chen Guo chased after him.

When they returned to their gaming house, Chen Guo obviously told everyone about their encounter with Team Everlasting.

"So, we definitely can’t lose. If we lose, we’ll be laughed at." Chen Guo tried to boost everyone’s morale.

"If we lose, everything will be over. Who cares if we’re laughed at?" Wei Chen followed up. Chen Guo’s encouragement was clearly a bit amiss. For those participating in the Challenger League, not losing was much more important than not losing face.

"In short, keep working hard everyone." Ye Xiu’s closing statement was very brief.

In the following few days, both teams practiced hard. This week, Ye Xiu and the others didn’t bother fighting for wild bosses. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun also now understood why pro players were so busy preparing for their matches every week. There was too much to prepare if they wanted to win a match.

In the show business, there was the saying "Ten years of practice for one minute on stage". Didn’t this apply to Glory pro players too? Winning and performing was inseparable from hard work and bitter practice.

On Thursday, Loulan Slash delivered the equipment that Ye Xiu had picked. Ye Xiu had purchased a batch of equipment from the in-game market and gaming studios. Everyone’s character improved tremendously. Today’s work would be to familiarize themselves with their upgraded characters.

In the game, the conflict between Team Happy and Team Everlasting produced quite a few waves. Team Everlasting originally had fans. Team Happy was being closely followed. This Challenger League match was given as much attention as a match in the Pro League.

Chapter 809: Riverside Veranda

If not for the colossus Excellent Era, Team Everlasting would have been the peak existence of the Challenger League this season. Meeting them in the second round was definitely not a blessing. However, very few pitied Happy. Instead, an enormous wave of ridicule crashed onto them. The original faceslapping group spread the news, telling their friends to witness their downfall. This time, Happy would definitely lose.

Chen Guo checked the forums everyday, so she saw these discussions. She didn’t tell it to the team though, afraid that it would affect their emotions. Everyone was working hard to familiarize themselves with their new set of equipment. They didn’t have time to be distracted.

That day passed quickly. On Friday night, room 117 in the Glory Arena’s Challenger League area was packed with players. The vast majority of the players, who followed Happy’s journey, saw Happy as the villains. At this moment, they were all supporters of Team Everlasting, which left Team Everlasting’s actual fans somewhat confused.

Everything in the Challenger League was audited automatically by the system. The special area for the Challenger League had its own custom settings for this purpose. 8:00 PM marked the official start of the matches. Before 7:55 PM, both sides needed to finish flipping their coin to determine who was the home team and who was the away team. The home team would also need to choose a map. The two teams would also be required to arrange the order of their team’s lineup. When the time came, the Challenger League would automatically select the chosen teammates and place them onstage. Before that happened, the two teams would not know each other’s lineup. It was the same as in the Pro League.

At 8:00PM, the second round of the Challenger League between Team Happy and Team Everlasting officially began. The first match was Team Everlasting’s home game. As a former pro team, they wouldn’t make a stupid mistake like forgetting to choose a map before the time limit ended.

When the time came, the first two competitors for the individual competition were automatically selected into the competitor’s seat.

For Team Everlasting, their team’s Launcher appeared: Dawn Rifle.

The Launcher wasn’t Team Everlasting’s core, but he was the character used by the team’s captain.

When He An paid a visit that day, He An had come with another visitor. Ye Xiu felt like this visitor seemed familiar, but he couldn’t remember who he was. After some investigation, he figured it out.

Wu Chen. He had been the vice-captain of Team Everlasting during the team’s three years in the Alliance. The character that he used was this Launcher, Dawn Rifle.

In season seven, he was demoted along with the rest of the team. What happened afterwards might only be known by his fans. After all, Wu Chen wasn’t anyone famous.

From the looks of it, Wu Chen had stayed on Team Everlasting and had now become the team’s captain. Usually, the team captain would not be switched when the original team captain was still there. If Wu Chen was promoted to captain, it was likely that Team Everlasting’s original captain, core player, and the owner of the Spellblade Quentinkin, Yu Hongliang was no longer with the team.

The team captain was not always the best player on the team, but rather the most reliable player. Now Wu Chen was undoubtedly Team Everlasting’s most trusted player. By placing him in the first match of the individual competition, Team Everlasting expressed that they wanted to gain the upperhand with a show of strength.

For Team Happy, Steamed Bun was up first. The first person to fight would be under a lot of pressure. Even a strong-willed and determined player would feel this pressure. Someone with a personality like Tang Rou may actually become worse the more they thought about doing better. In comparison, a nutjob like Steamed Bun couldn’t be more suited to this position.

Pressure? Did that word even exist in Steamed Bun’s dictionary?

When the characters stepped onto the stage, the chosen map was announced: Riverside Veranda. The match would begin as soon as the two players pressed start. If any of them didn’t press start, the match would automatically begin after five minutes.

"This map..." Ye Xiu mumbled after seeing this map.

"What’s important to know about it?" Chen Guo hastily asked.

"Steamed Bun." Ye Xiu called out.

"Here." Steamed Bun, who was currently warming up by stretching, replied.

"Be careful not to fall into the water." Ye Xiu said.

"Understood." Steamed Bun nodded his head.

Riverside Veranda was a partly water map. The gap between pro players and normal players was even more pronounced in an aquatic battle. This was because players could simply avoid this kind of situation and choose not to fight in the water, but if pro players acted in the same way, their opponent might utilize that to their advantage.

Truthfully, pro players did not like to fight in the water either, but they had no choice but to practice doing so. Team Everlasting choosing this map was clearly to bully this grassroots team. However, it wasn’t very thorough. A partly water map meaning there was still a portion on land. This type of map required more on-the-moment adaptation.

The match started. The characters were loaded into the stage. Once the countdown ended, the two characters were on opposite corners of the map as usual, except between these two characters was a winding corridor on top of the water.

Steamed Bun couldn’t care about all that. As soon as the match began, his character rushed forward. Wu Chen seemed very calm, moving neither quickly nor slowly.

The individual competition maps wouldn’t be too large. It wasn’t necessary and it was pointless. The two characters neared each other. Steamed Bun Invasion looked ferocious. He held his new Orange weapon, Poison Marsh Point. The poisonous gleam looked horrifying. It was clearly a weapon that increased poison damage. That sharpness looked as if it could tear an opponent to pieces.

Wu Chen still remained calm. While moving, he closely watched his approaching opponent, calculating the distance between them and planning his opening move. The Launcher’s advantage was in having the longest range of any class. As a result, Launchers usually made the first move, especially when facing melee classes. There was almost no possibility of a counterattack. If a melee character could attack back, then the opponent was already too close. That would be very disadvantageous. The hunter might end up becoming the hunted.

Brawlers had a few mid-ranged attacks, but the majority of the skills leaned towards melee attacks. Wu Chen decided not to give his opponent any opportunity to approach him. When he was at about the right distance, he would start attacking.

The distance between them grew closer and closer. His mouse was already targeting Steamed Bun Invasion. For gunners, their mouse would be the direction in which their bullets flew towards.

"That’s about right!" Wu Chen checked the distance. Right when he was about to attack, he suddenly saw Steamed Bun Invasion stop.

With this sudden halt, the attack that Wu Chen had been about to make was now useless. Wu Chen was also astonished.

What sharp eyes!

Wu Chen didn’t think this player from a grassroots team would have such perception. He actually noticed that I was about to attack?

However, he had already readied his gun. He might as well attack. Wu Chen was just about to attack, when he suddenly saw Steamed Bun turn around and run.

As a result, the distance between the two sides became farther and farther away…...

"What is he up to?" Wu Chen was puzzled.

Even if his opponent saw through his intentions, there was no need to run away. If he was running because he saw that he was going to attack, this match might as well not be played. Launchers had longer range. Wouldn’t he get hit first because of a range disadvantage? The opponent of a Launcher should be figuring out how to get closer, not farther away from the Launcher.

If the other side wasn’t going to come, then he would have to go himself.

Wu Chen thought to himself. He continued to move forward, closing the distance between him and Steamed Bun Invasion. At the same time, he didn’t relax his guard towards Steamed Bun Invasion, but the other guy just kept on going round and round. Wu Chen couldn’t guess his opponent’s intent. However, the distance between the two sides was closing. Wu Chen finally made the first attack of the match.

Three Anti-Tank Missiles flew over. While shooting, he swiped his mouse horizontally, so the three missiles lined up, restricting Steamed Bun Invasion’s next movements.

Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t try to dodge. He swung his arms and a brick flew out towards those missiles.

Bang.

The brick exploded into pieces, but so did the missiles. This type of weird interaction wasn’t rare in the game.

As a pro player, Wu Chen wouldn’t just attack once. He already had plans for his follow-ups and sent a barrage of attacks towards Steamed Bun. After Steamed Bun smacked down those missiles with his brick, he didn’t do anything flashy anymore. Facing the opponent’s bombardment, he scurried around like a housefly.

Wu Chen was a bit confused. His opponent didn’t look like he planned on fighting back! Was his bombardment really so fierce that he was completely overwhelming him?

However, as the team captain, this thought only briefly crossed his mind. If he didn’t even have a clear understanding of his own strength, how could he be the most reliable on the team?

It wasn’t that he was strong, but the other side was too weak. That Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t even get through this level of firepower….. He didn’t seem as impressive as before!

Could it be... the previous Steamed Bun Invasion was actually Ye Qiu playing and this is the real one? But that shouldn’t be the case. If that had been a trick, it wouldn’t make sense for Ye Qiu to be so upright facing a difficult opponent like Team Everlasting.

Wu Chen was doubtful, but he didn’t dare to relax for a second. As he continued to attack, he continued to watch Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements. Wu Chen suddenly understood, but at that moment, he became confused again.

Because he discovered that the reason that Steamed Bun Invasion had been passive and never rushed towards him was because he couldn’t figure out his way around the corridor!

What’s going on?

Wu Chen was truly puzzled. This corridor was a bit confusing to navigate through, but it wasn’t so complicated that you could get lost. It wasn’t designed to be a maze. Moreover, if you’re lost, you can just jump in the water and then swim to your destination!

"It’s all your fault..." Chen Guo glared at Ye Xiu, "You told him not to go into the water."　　

"It’s over. D*mn..." Ye Xiu felt sorry too.

Chapter 810: One Hit One Kill

Due to an embarrassing reason, the first individual match concluded with an undignified loss for Steamed Bun. During the match, he wasn’t able to close in on his opponent, and lost without landing a single hit. This result immediately ignited the passions of the spectors. They had been waiting for this day for a long time.

As this passion was expressed, the fans of Everlasting were completely stunned.

Their team leader won beautifully in this first match, and at a time like this, the fans were all cheering for him! And then these people started spamming, but their words were all directed at the opposing side. All sorts of mockery, sarcasm and insults filled up the chat channel. With that imposing manner, a passerby would probably think that Team Everlasting had a major bone to pick with Happy! Unless it was towards an archenemy, fans rarely banded together to attack the opposing side when their side had the advantage. Most fans had reason and composure, and were good sports.

For these spectators who focused their anger on Happy, it wasn’t that they had no composure or manners, it was just that they had been holding in their anger for too long.

"Those noobs from Happy, did you see that? That’s a real pro team, real pro players! Hahahaha!"

"Getting KO’ed like that, you sure have some skill!"

"Yah understand how terrifying pro players are now?"

The reason for Steamed Bun’s loss was quite embarrassing, but for normal players, it wasn’t unheard of. With just the skill they had, normal players couldn’t tell Steamed Bun Invasion merely got lost. A Launchers style was to use firepower to prevent an opponent from getting close. Wu Chen had a solid foundation, and he was very much familiar with these routines and techniques for offense. In the average player’s view, Steamed Bun seemed to be helpless against his assault, but they wouldn’t realize that in reality, Steamed Bun himself met with some problems.

"Wow, pro teams really are strong," Steamed Bun said with some frustration as he took off his headphones, "Picking such a complicated map. They really are strong."

"Mmh," Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more. Choosing to go through the veranda in Riverside Veranda did make the map a little hard to wrap your head around. Steamed Bun didn’t know the way and with Wu Chen’s firepower oppressing him, it was natural that he was unable to perform at his peak. Going into the water wasn’t necessarily a critical point. Steamed Bun wasn’t very familiar with aquatic battles either, so he might have just gotten cornered in the water by Wu Chen. It was Team Everlasting that chose this map, after all.

Everyone came over to comfort Steamed Bun, who was a little bummed out by his loss. Even Mo Fan opened his mouth, seeming to have something to say, but in the end he didn’t speak.

The second individual match started shortly. Team Happy sent out Qiao Yifan and his One Inch Ash. For Team Everlasting, it was a sharpshooter who took the stage, character name Shoot Here.

This sharpshooter wasn’t one of the six characters for Everlasting’s team battles. However, healers like Clerics rarely appeared in individual or group competitions, so there had to be more than just six core members in one team who would fight in the individual or group competition. This was how the Number Seven Ace Backup came into existence.

That was the role that Shoot Here played.

The match started, with Everlasting still choosing Riverside Veranda for the map, and the opponent already began moving towards One Inch Ash, seeming much more eager than Wu Chen in the first match.

Though the spectators didn’t know what had gone wrong with Steamed Bun, but Wu Chen had realized. After relaying this to his teammates, they were all struck dumb.

Although this wasn’t a pro match, if it was a team that wished to enter the Pro League, then their attitude towards the Challenger’s League would probably be even more serious than the Pro League itself. In the Pro League, losing a match wouldn’t have too much of an effect on the final score, but in the Challenger’s League, one mistake could mean another year lost for the team.

Under these circumstances, they actually sent up a newbie who didn’t even know the map. Was this disdain, or did they just have no one else to send?

Speaking of, the reason Everlasting chose this map was just so they could get an advantage on how inexperienced their opponents were, compared to them, but getting lost was a bit overkill. The map gave them an advantage they hadn’t expected, which gave them these new thoughts.

The player who was sent up in the second match didn’t want to waste his time with this strange team, so he actively charged forth, but Qiao Yifan was very decisive as well. One Inch Ash turned and jumped into the water with a splash.

Riverside Veranda’s water wasn’t very deep, but after the spindrift from One Inch Ash’s jump dissolved, the water was calm without a ripple.

This… either meant that One Inch Ash wasn’t moving, or if he was, then it could only mean one thing: he was a professional!

Unless he were a pro player, it was rare that a player could master how to move under the water without causing fluctuations in the water’s surface under such circumstances. Learning how to sneak underwater was something only pro players would learn how to do!

One Inch Ash was Qiao Yifan

It was likely that only Team Excellent Era knew this information due to the coincidence that occurred at the time when Tao Xuan had come over to Team Happy with Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin. Apart from them, not even Qiao Yifan’s original Team Tiny Herb knew where he had gone after his contract expired.

If not even Team Tiny Herb knew, then how on earth could Team Everlasting know that their opponents had a member from a champion team? Though he was an inconsequential member of the team, Qiao Yifan had been under their strict training all this time. He changed his class, but a technique like playing underwater wasn’t affected by a change in class. With Qiao Yifan’s diligence, his execution of this skill was flawless.

The current One Inch Ash was slowly walking underwater, preparing to close in on his target silently.

Seeing how his opponent knew how to sneak around underwater, the player from Everlasting knew that this wasn’t a weak enemy and didn’t dare to make decisions lightly. He slowed to a stop, carefully watching the area where Qiao Yifan had disappeared into.

There were no ripples on the water’s surface, but the water in this map was quite shallow. If a character was walking along the bottom, they couldn’t hide their silhouette.

But, if you wanted to find their silhouette, you couldn’t do it at this angle from a distance. Everlasting’s player carefully watched the water as he moved his character, Shoot Here, towards it. His impatience had long since evaporated, so he was walking rather slowly.

As he was watching the water for any movement, he was also taking note of how much time had passed. A character couldn’t stay under the surface infinitely, they had to come up for air too. However, on this map and for such a professional player, he probably wouldn’t be seen even when coming up for air. Under the Veranda, there was plenty of space for a character to come up without being found out.

As expected, Team Everlasting’s player knew that time was up, but he didn’t see One Inch Ash coming out of the water.

Where was this guy hiding?

Team Everlasting’s player became a little impatient. This map was meant to give him the advantage, but now it was being used against him, putting him in a passive position. This turning of the tides caught him off guard.

Should he go into the water, too?

It wasn’t as if he didn’t think of this before, but he wasn’t very good at aquatic battles either. He wasn’t a pro player who had truly experienced pro matches, but a person who joined after Everlasting had been eliminated and most of their players walked out. People like him naturally lacked confidence in this area. Seeing how familiar One Inch Ash seemed to be when sneaking around underwater, he didn’t dare go down himself.

Let’s try it out first!

Team Everlasting’s player thought for a moment before deciding to probe for his opponent. Shoot Here raised his guns and started shooting randomly at the water in front of him.

Normal attacks didn’t cost mana, so he could be unrestrained with how he shot. The calm of the water’s surface was broken, and foam erupted all over the place, spraying the veranda with water.

But this wasn’t a scene Team Everlasting’s player would pay attention to. His eyes never left the areas he was shooting at. If he hit, or was dodged, there was be visible movement.

There!

Among the ripples the bullets made, Team Everlasting’s player found an abnormal surge. He unhesitantly unloaded all his skills in that direction while swiftly approaching. He needed an angle where he could clearly see the opponent’s figure in order to further his advantage. Sharpshooters had an advantage in range. Cornering a target in the water was much easier than on land.

Shoot Here’s movements were light and easy, traversing the veranda with familiarity. He had finally locked onto his opponent. His attacks didn’t seem to give his opponent too much trouble, but being able to lock onto the approximate whereabouts of his opponent, he believed, he would soon be able to see them.

Pop!

Suddenly, with a quiet noise Shoot Here’s movements stopped involuntarily. A ray of blue-white light flashed. Everlasting’s player realized something and turned his view in shock. He immediately saw the Ice Soul that had been refracted from under the water, and continued to refract with the movement of the water.

Ice Boundary!

It was the Ghostblade’s Ice Boundary that had been placed in the water, but it could reach all across the veranda. Team Everlasting’s player was so focused on his target that he hadn’t thought he would walk into such a trap.

Ice Boundary’s damage and control effects had only just begun. Everlasting’s player could see the light shining off the sword in the hands of an underwater figure.

Sword Soul, Plague Soul, Blood Soul...

Ghost Souls were called out one after another, who knew how many Ghost Boundaries were stacked there? Shoot Here’s body had been possessed by so many Ghost Souls that he had become an encyclopedia of negative status effects.

The water surface suddenly split open, and One Inch Ash leaped out. The Blade of Calamity in his hand shone with a dark purple light, encircled by blade qi made from Ghost Souls, and struck out towards Shoot Here.

One Hit One Kill!

Chapter 811: Character Advantage

It was just one attack, so it obviously wouldn’t instantly kill Shoot Here, but Qiao Yifan’s position established a huge advantage for him. Facing a Ghostblade in a duel, no pro player would allow themselves be affected by so many ghost boundaries at the same time. Qiao Yifan cleverly used this map to lure his opponent into a trap, instantly deciding victory.

Shoot Here tried his best, but in the second round of the individual competition, Qiao Yifan swiftly won.

This shift in tides was too quick…...

The face slappers were still absorbed in the previous round’s victory and looking down on Team Happy disdainfully. When the second round began, their contempt was still concentrated on One Inch Ash, but before they could fully adjust themselves, the tides of battle shifted and One Inch Ash took down his opponent. Everyone was left speechless.

The spectators were speechless. Team Everlasting also felt like their face had been slapped.

They had chosen this map in order to bully their green opponents. Who would have thought that their opponents would be the one to use this map to bully them? This loss not only resulted in a loss of points, but a loss of face too!

The system didn’t care about anyone’s feelings. Once the match concluded, the third round of the individual competition immediately began.

The map chosen for this third round was still Riverside Corridor.

Team Everlasting had clearly done their research on this map. Using the same map for every round in the individual competition clearly showed their intent to eradicate Team Happy for good. Their decision came with belittlement. Team Everlasting thought that Team Happy wouldn’t be able to utilize the map’s characteristics in just two or three rounds.

But after the second round, the players on Team Everlasting were no longer calm, but it was too late to regret it now. The maps could not be changed midway.

The third person to come out from Team Everlasting was their team’s Warlock: Leopold.

"Be careful." The player for the Warlock Leopold was warned repeatedly.

Team Everlasting had acknowledged Team Happy’s skill level from the start. From their action of going over to their front steps to talk, the degree of their acknowledgement wasn’t low. They felt like the players on Team Happy would be an addition to their strength. Their attention hadn’t been fixed on just God Ye Qiu.

During the period of time when Team Happy accepted challenges, Soft Mist appeared the most, then Steamed Bun Invasion, then Windward Formation.

Team Everlasting looked highly upon all three of them. With Team Happy as their opponents, they also attached the most importance to these three. They had even come up with plans to counter them. This was just their attitude towards competition though. While Team Everlasting recognized the strength of these three players, and were not afraid. If they really were afraid, He An would not have acted so lofty when he came to Happy.

Team Everlasting had meticulously chosen their maps and their player order. In terms of strategy, Team Everlasting took Team Happy quite seriously.

But in the individual competition, it was already 1-1. Their victory was against Steamed Bun Invasion, who they had been wary of, but their loss was against One Inch Ash, who they had ignored.

Did Team Happy have anyone else like One Inch Ash? Team Everlasting suddenly felt at a loss. How could they dare to be careless in the third round?

Leopold stood at the competitor spot. At the same, Team Happy’s next competitor appeared as well.

Another Warlock. Windward Formation.

The third round would be a contest between two characters of the same class, putting an even greater emphasis on the player’s skill.

Team Everlasting released a sigh of relief when they saw their opponent. Windward Formation wasn’t unknown, at least. Moreover, in a battle between two characters of the same class, apart from the player’s skill level, the character’s strength would also be a significant deciding factor.

Team Everlasting was very confident here.

It was already extraordinary for an Internet cafe grassroots team to have players of such caliber. How strong could their characters be? Could their equipment be better than ours? Could their characters have more skill points than ours?

Team Everlasting smiled. Their warning to be careful didn’t seem necessary now.

The spectators didn’t know about Team Everlasting’s confidence. After being slapped in the face, they appeared even more cautious than Team Everlasting. Their contempt towards Team Happy continued, but before the outcome was determined, they couldn’t spit out anymore slander.

The match soon started.　　

Despite being confident, Team Everlasting’s player still showed caution. On the contrary, on Team Happy’s side, Windward Formation looked very carefree, heading straight for Leopold.

The faceslappers really wanted to say something. Their hands hovered over their keyboards, but none of them typed out anything.　　

Team Everlasting’s Warlock took no notice. He continued with his original plan. Suddenly, he felt the sky darken above him. He looked up and saw dark clouds covering him.

Chaotic Rain!

He was startled. Leopold escaped outside of its range, while looking in that direction. Sure enough, it was a spell casted by Windward Formation.

"This….. Impossible..." The Warlock player looked at where he had just escaped from. Rain poured down from those dark clouds.

The attack had come, but he had been caught completely off guard because in his eyes, the two sides weren’t even in range yet!

When he looked at Windward Formation, he confirmed that Windward Formation had been outside of his attack range.

But Windward Formation had already cast a spell. Does that mean his cast range is three units more than mine?

Cast range was an extremely valuable stat for mages. A greater cast range meant more distance. More distance meant more time to take the initiative, but in terms of cast range, his Leopold actually lost to Windward Formation? Didn’t that mean Leopold’s equipment was inferior to Windward Formation’s?

Impossible!

Team Everlasting’s Warlock player was dumbfounded. He didn’t want to believe it. The equipment on these grassroot characters was actually better than the equipment that they had refined since their beginnings in the pro scene?

The distance was a bit far, so he couldn’t see Windward Formation’s equipment. After Windward Formation used Chaotic Rain, he followed up with another attack. The corridor was narrow, so after a few consecutive curses, Leopold had nowhere left to run. Windward Formation had formed a Curse Arrow too. At this moment, if he didn’t want to receive damage, he only one had choice: fight back!

Team Everlasting’s Warlock hastily made a move. Leopold also formed a Curse Arrow. This skill could be charged. The longer the charge time, the stronger it became. Windward Formation didn’t seem to want to waste time though. He charged it for a bit and fired it. Team Everlasting’s Warlock timed it well and determined that his charge time wasn’t any shorter than Windward Formation’s before firing his own arrow.

The two Curse Arrows collided, passing through the corridor and landed in the water. That dark energy seemed to be splitting space itself. The resulting collision made it impossible for Team Everlasting’s Warlock to see Windward Formation. A thought flashed through his mind and he immediately cast a new skill.

Warlock skill: Death’s Door!

Leopold’s cast range didn’t allow for him to directly attack Windward Formation. However, Death’s Door had its own attack range of 18 units, so he didn’t need to place it directly on top of his opponent. Taking advantage of the chaotic explosion formed by the two Curse Arrows, he started casting this powerful skill to attack his opponent, but because of the difference in cast range and because of his position in the corner, he would only be able to take a beating, unable to return fire.

This high-level skill was complex and had a long cast time. After Team Everlasting’s player finished the appropriate actions, Leopold waved his staff and prepared the curse. Suddenly, he heard a bang. In front of him, a black revolving door came out from a tear in space. Dark energy spread as it revolved and grabbed Leopold.

At this distance, it was too late to dodge. Leopold’s own Death’s Door was interrupted. He was grabbed by the dark energy and pulled into the door. The door engulfed him and Leopold’s image turned faint. Death’s Door did instant burst damage. Not just Team Everlasting’s Warlock, but when everyone in Team Everlasting saw his health, their faces turned pale.

That damage was way too high!

How many skill points did that Windward Formation put into Death’s Door?

The value in Death’s Door didn’t lie in its high damage. For pro players, its AoE crowd control effects were more favorable. Even though there was only one target at this moment, the crowd control still existed. After being sucked into the door, Leopold could not be controlled. The collision between the two Curse Arrows had ended. The energy collision dissipated as Windward Formation continued to wave his staff.

Corrosion, Soul Strike, Soul Slice, Engulf, Surrender Life…...

Curses and attacks were released one after the other. Ever since Leopold had been grabbed by Death’s Door, the damage received never ceased. When the effects of Death’s Door ended, Leopold fell into the water.

Splash!

Chapter 812: Map Choice Joke

The water’s surface never returned to its calm state.

Windward Formation’s attacks didn’t stop once, chasing Leopold into the water. The water would have some effect on both characters and skills, and the water battle training for pro-plays was to help familiarize them with these effects.

Team Everlasting’s Warlock was hoping that he might get an opportunity to turn the tides upon falling into the water. He could use the experience he had with water battles to escape from the opponent’s attacks, but he soon realized that his opponent’s grasp of this was no worse than his own, no… it should be that it was even better.

So falling into the water turned out to be a misfortune for Team Everlasting. With the movement speed he had currently, he didn’t know if he would be able to escape from Windward Formation’s attack range.

In the second round, Team Everlasting’s Sharpshooter tried to find One Inch Ash and corner him in the water, but because he fell into an ambush of Ghost Boundaries from One Inch Ash, he never managed to carry out his plan. Yet in this round, such a plan was completed by Wei Chen

Team Everlasting’s Leopold didn’t get another chance to return to the veranda, being continuously suppressed in the water by Windward Formation. When he eventually returned to the surface, it was in the form of a corpse...

Happy claimed victory once more in the third round.

The spectating faceslappers’ speechlessness was evident. With this loss by Team Everlasting, they took quite a huge blow.

This round was lost even more clearly than the second.

In the last round, they could say that the Sharpshooter had accidentally fell into his opponent’s ambush, but for this round, the two Warlocks fought head to head. Happy’s victory showed off their player’s experience and their advantage in equipment.

Because Leopold hadn’t gotten a chance to close in on Windward Formation enough to check his equipment, Team Everlasting still had no idea what Windward Formation had equipped.

But from his increased cast range , it could be seen that Windward Formation had better equipment than Leopold. If they had equipment that could increase cast range by three body units, they would’ve given it to Leopold from the start.

They didn’t have it, but Happy had. That was an advantage in equipment.

Their home game advantage had long since been scrapped in the second round.

Their belief in the superiority of their characters had taken a harsh blow in the third round, but this exchange only revealed how terrifying Windward Formation’s cast range was. His true advantage was something they had yet to experience.

Windward Formation’s 4920 skill points would be terrifying if put in the Pro League, but in Team Happy, this was a rather low number. Low enough that Wei Chen hesitated if he should use a different account or not.

"Don’t lose hope now!" On Team Everlasting’s side, someone broke the silence of the training room. The one who spoke was He An, their team leader. At the same time, he was also a part of the team.

Wu Chen was their captain, true, but in their team there was also He An. And he was team leader, having power over the captain. In the Glory circle, team leader was an antique title, now known as club manager. This was a position that truly had power over the team. For Captains, they actually only had the right to give advice, but most teams treasured the advice of their captain, making it seem as if the captain had the power to make decisions. However, it wasn’t like that. If the manager decided to ignore the captain’s advice entirely, that was perfectly ok.

With one of the team members having such a position, Wu Chen’s position as captain was a little awkward and his power within the team was limited. At a time like this, Wu Chen hadn’t even spoken, being the captain, yet He An took the role of leader to comfort everyone. This was because of his two positions.

"The situation was just out of our expectations, that’s all. These inconsequential characters can only be hidden to temporarily give them an advantage once in the arena." He An spoke so, but in reality, Happy had thoroughly shocked him, too. He obviously couldn’t express his surprise either. He could only describe the situation as if these surprises were just some insignificant attempts to pull the advantage to their side. This way, his team members would be able to relax a little.

He An’s words did as they intended to. Team Everlasting’s members relaxed upon hearing them. Next up was the group competition. There was only a small pause between it and the individual competition, but their line-up had long since been decided and couldn’t be changed. At the moment, the two players about to battle were both impatient to get on with it.

In the stands, the faceslappers weren’t sure what to think. They had so much hope in Team Everlasting, but they somehow lost two matches in the individual competition. This made them want to rage at Team Everlasting. However, it was just an individual competition. There was still the group and team competitions. Maybe… they should stay and watch a little longer...

The arrogant faceslappers were silenced by Happy’s two victories. The public chat became much more normal as well. It was mostly the true fans of Team Everlasting giving them some encouragement.

The group arena competition finally began, and the first participant of each team entered the stage.

Team Happy, Battle Mage Soft Mist.

Team Everlasting, Qi Master Heavenly Rage.

As of late, Soft Mist was definitely the most well known member of Happy and also the one the faceslappers hated the most. The experts they had hope in all fell beneath Soft Mist’s spear. And when the one person who could defeat Soft Mist appeared, she won back the match quickly. With victories and losses on both sides, they couldn’t really say anything about that one defeat.

But here, in the Challenger League, there were rules to these matches. If she lost this match, then they didn’t have to worry about her winning it back, because she had no chance to do that here. Everyone could use this chance to say whatever they wished.

Thinking of this, the silent faceslappers became excited once more. Slowly, different voices rose from the crowd, all giving encouragement toTeam Everlasting’s Heavenly Rage. For a moment, it seemed like Heavenly Rage was a celebrity player, receiving the hopes of all the spectators.

Entering the competitor’s areas, loading the competition map. When the map was revealed, even the audience felt faint.

It was still Riverside Veranda...

It was hard for the faceslappers to hold in their mockery. Since they wanted to see Team Happy humiliated, they were supporting Team Everlasting right now, but don’t forget, not everyone was here to see Team Happy humiliated. In the audience, there were a neutral few who were just here out of curiosity, or even those who held hope in Team Happy. Though they weren’t many, seeing Team Everlasting’s never changing choice of Riverside Veranda, why wouldn’t they speak up against it?

Taunting came from the crowd, Team Everlasting’s choice was an embarrassment. There was nothing wrong with their original idea. Since there wouldn’t be an overlap of characters in the individual and group competitions, they wanted to use the field advantage to its fullest. Though this map choice was a little utilitarian, they couldn’t afford to be careless in the Challenger League.

Unfortunately, despite choosing this map, Team Everlasting still lost two round during the individual competition. And in these two rounds, their losses were in part due to the map choice. Now, this choice of map was more like a joke. The audience’s taunts were vicious, but they didn’t understand that Team Everlasting hadn’t thought it would turn out like this. It was too late now.

Luckily, these taunts couldn’t affect the characters who had entered the arena. From the start of the match, the characters fighting couldn’t see the public chat and the private chats between characters would also be forbidden. This was made so that the players in the arena wouldn’t get any outside help, with the audience having a bird’s eye view and all.

But there was no one there to enforce this, with this online match in the Challenger League. If there was anyone giving the players information offline, no one would know. They couldn’t even stop the dirty move of people getting others to play for them. With the rules announced, they hoped that people would act responsibly and follow them. If it was actually found that you weren’t following the rules, then naturally that wouldn’t be good for you. And even if you never got caught, you couldn’t use these tricks throughout the entire league. You would get exposed as soon as you got to the offline matches. So there wouldn’t be too much of an effect on the final results.

The Alliance couldn’t really do anything about it. With the current situation, they could only let it happen in these first rounds.

In regards to this, Team Happy was very responsible. In the first match when Steamed Bun got lost, no one went up to help. Even for victory, everyone made sure it was a fair match; that was what it meant to be a good sport.

As the countdown fell, the group competition officially started.

With how often Soft Mist appeared before, the faceslappers were very familiar with this character, to the point where they knew very piece of equipment she wore.

But when Soft Mist entered the arena, the audience realized that they couldn’t recognize her at all.

Was this that Soft Mist?

Her equipment had changed so much!

The audience had noticed this change with Steamed Bun and Windward Formation, too, but they only had a vague impression of these two characters, nothing like their understanding of Soft Mist. Now as Soft Mist stepped in, everyone immediately noticed that she was different from before.

Team Everlasting had researched their opponents, but they didn’t count on familiarity to judge the change in the character. They could tell from one look that Steamed Bun Invasion’s equipment had changed, and so had Windward Formation’s. It was just that Windward Formation’s victory made them realize it wasn’t as they thought; it was more terrifying.

Though He An had said it was just a small trick to surprise them, Team Everlasting’s members couldn’t help but feel uneasy when seeing that Soft Mist had also undergone a massive change.

Soft Mist’s equipment wouldn’t suddenly become very powerful, would it?

Their worries were accurate. Out of all of them, Soft Mist’s equipment had changed the most. Now, she was wearing five pieces of Silver equipment. In the Pro League, this was nothing, but on this grassroots character, it was something most wouldn’t dream to think about.

Chapter 813: Air of a Professional

Battle Mage Soft Mist vs Qi Master Heavenly Rage. The first round of the group arena finally began.

As Team Happy’s most infamous character, how could Team Everlasting’s Qi Master not be wary of Soft Mist? Especially after seeing the new set of equipment on Soft Mist. The shadow of Leopold’s loss coiled around him.

However, Heavenly Rage’s opening move was very courageous. Although Qi Masters were Fighters, their close combat skills weren’t actually that outstanding. A Qi Master’s skill kit consisted mostly of mid-range attacks, but they didn’t have as long of a range as gunners. In any case, Qi Masters effectively had a longer range than Battle Mages. The first to make the first move should be the Qi Master.

Many of the Qi Master skills were AoE attacks, which were especially a threat on Riverside Veranda, which had land and water. The land portion consisted of the veranda, so the space was already quite limited. For a class with lots of AoE like Qi Masters, it was easy to force the opponent into the water.

Team Everlasting’s main classes generally had this advantage. It was just that in the individual competition, the Launcher and Warlock weren’t able to show this advantage.

The Qi Master was wary of Soft Mist. He didn’t dare give Soft Mist room to maneuver freely. As soon as Soft Mist stepped into his attack range, he launched his offense.

Heavenly Rage rolled his palms and a qi bullet shot out. Soft Mist easily dodged it. Heavenly Rage had already jumped into the air and pushed out with his two hands: AoE attack, Sky Piercing Strike!

A powerful stream of qi burst out from Heavenly Rage’s hands towards the veranda. The AoE coverage was extremely large. If Soft Mist continued to advance, the attack would certainly hit her. If she retreated backwards, she might just be able to escape, but to make this judgement, it would require her to have a very clear understanding of Heavenly Rage’s first attack. How could the purpose of a simple Qi Bullet just be to deal some damage?

Of course not.

That attack was only to restrict his opponent. It wasn’t to restrict Soft Mist’s movements, but to distract the player controlling Soft Mist. The purpose of the Qi Bullet was to hinder Tang Rou from noticing his Sky Piercing Strike. By the time she noticed this attack, it would be too late for her to dodge.

This was fairly simple trick. Even normal players understood that in PvP, it was best to keep the opponent in your line of sight so that you could observe the opponent’s movements.　

However, this Qi Bullet wasn’t enough to fluster Tang Rou and cause her to look away from her opponent’s movements. To put it plainly, this attack was a way for the Qi Master to probe out her skill.

To his surprise, such a shallow method was actually going to work!

Soft Mist seemed to misjudge the AoE coverage of the skill and continued to rush forward. In this case, Sky Piercing Strike would undoubtedly hit Soft Mist.

Pulling off such a simple maneuver caught him unprepared. His original plan was to follow up with another attack, after Soft Mist avoided this one, but the opponent was actually going to be hit, so he had to change up his plans.

Sky Piercing Strike covered that stretch of the veranda. The surrounding water rippled intensely from the shockwave.

After being hit by this attack, Soft Mist immediately rolled. She rolled so quickly and unexpectedly that Heavenly Rage’s following two attacks actually missed.

Soft Mist leaped up and stepped onto the railing on the edges of the veranda. She jumped again directly over the water and landed on the stretch on the other side.

In the blink of an eye, Soft Mist and Heavenly Rage now stood on the same stretch of the veranda!

The Qi Master was startled. Soft Mist didn’t misjudge that Sky Piercing Strike. Rather, she intentionally didn’t dodge it. She used the shock wave from the attack to give her a speed boost. Her roll then put her at a distance, where she could jump over the water and stand in the same line as Heavenly Rage.

The Qi Master didn’t dare let Soft Mist get close. Qi rippled from Heavenly Rage, who gathered that qi into a fist. He punched and the qi transformed into a dragon.

Qi Master skill: Dragon Wave.

The dragon could be controlled by the player. After sending out the qi dragon, the player could freely change its direction. Apart from attacking the opponent, it could be used to hit the user or a teammate. When it hit the user or the teammate, Dragon Wave wouldn’t deal damage. Instead, it would give a buff that increased the target’s fighting strength.

Right now, the Qi Master wasn’t planning on eating this qi dragon for himself. He threw it directly at Soft Mist.

Soft Mist lifted her spear, which glinted with cold light. Dust swept off her feet as she headed straight for Heavenly Rage.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist didn’t dodge. She actually decided to contest with Dragon Wave head on.

That’s completely unreasonable…...

Team Everlasting’s Qi Master thought to himself at this moment.

Not dodging Dragon Wave was too crazy. Dragon Wave did not only deal damage. When it hit the opponent, it would also weaken the opponent’s attack power and attack speed!

Yes, the instant that Dragon Wave struck Soft Mist, the debuff was applied. However, Dragon Breaks the Ranks continued to head towards him.

Heavenly Rage immediately sprinted away.

After being hit by Dragon Wave, the might and speed of Dragon Breaks the Ranks fell significantly. Heavenly Rage immediately jumped twice just outside of its range. At this moment,, Soft Mist didn’t stop attack. Her spear suddenly grew in length, transforming into a dragon that pounced towards Heavenly Rage.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

After Dragon Breaks the Ranks, she connected it with another high-level skill, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. There didn’t seem to be a pause at all. What type of hand speed was that? How did she time that? The instant Dragon Breaks the Ranks completed, she had to also complete the actions required for Rising Dragon Soars the Sky in order to connect those two attacks seamlessly. If she completed the actions slightly late, it would have come out later. If she was slightly early, the attack wouldn’t come out, unless she cancelled Dragon Breaks the Rank first　　

"Not bad!"

Even Ye Xiu was impressed by it. He obviously wasn’t surprised at the difficulty of the maneuver. Rather, it was clear progress for Tang Rou. Ye Xiu never had any doubts about Tang Rou’s hand speed. Her biggest obstacle was turning her absolute hand speed into effective hand speed as well as working on her precision and timing.

Soft Mist had just obtained a complete new set of equipment. Her stats were vastly different, and she only had a day to familiarize herself with it. And after being hit by Dragon Wave, her stats changed again, yet Tang Rou was still able to grasp the timing and pull this combo off. If this wasn’t just luck, then Tang Rou’s sensitivity towards her character and mastery over her class had reached new heights.

At such a distance, even with the debuff from Dragon Wave, Heavenly Rage could not dodge this attack.

Just when everyone could already picture the explosion from Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, the attack suddenly stopped.

Force cancel!

Only Tang Rou could stop the skill.

After being devoured by Rising Dragon Soars the Sky and left in the air, even Heavenly Rage had a hard time believing it, when he saw Soft Mist retract her spear.

"What’s going on?" Chen Guo was dumbfounded. She thought Soft Mist had made an error. However, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had perfectly hit her opponent. What could she be doing to accidentally cancel her attack?

She had been too worried. She looked over at Ye Xiu, who was still smiling. His expression was filled with happiness.

Rising Dragon was canceled, but Soft Mist didn’t stop attacking. Under Dragon Wave’s debuff, Soft Mist stepped forward. She struck out with Sky Strike to knock Heavenly Rage even higher into the air. Then, Tyrant’s Destruction, Double Stab, Sky Strike, Chasers…..

Chen Guo finally understood.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had a long ending lag. For Soft Mist, she wouldn’t be able to connect any other attacks after using it. As a result, she abandoned Rising Dragon and cancelled it. Even though she would lose a large portion of the damage from it, she could still utilize this skill’s grab effect to restrict Heavenly Rage. The following combo clearly allowed her to deal more damage than the loss from Rising Dragon. Moreover, she also maintained her advantage after using the combo, while getting rid of the Dragon Wave debuff. If she had completed Rising Dragon, it would have certainly felt good, but she would not have been able to do anything more. Her battle with Heavenly Rage would reset, but she would also have the debuff from Dragon Wave.

In just an instant, Tang Rou instantly determined that it was better not to finish Rising Dragon and cancelled the skill. Chen Guo realized that Tang Rou was becoming more and more like a pro player. Her decision-making had already surpassed her understanding.

Amazing…..

Seeing Tang Rou, Chen Guo couldn’t help but be envious. She also wanted to be god at Glory. Unfortunately for her, that wasn’t a possibility. She could only place her hopes and dreams onto the team. Seeing Tang Rou’s growth, she could also appreciate Ye Xiu’s joy.　　

We have to win!

Chen Guo clenched her fists. She really wanted to see these people and their characters stand on stage. No...she wanted to see them as champions!

Chapter 814: Team Everlasting's Ace

The improvement of Tang Rou’s technical ability and her judgement of making a tradeoff between the damage from a powerful move and the opportunity to gain the upperhand all displayed the air of a professional. Never mind Team Everlasting, even Ye Xiu was surprised at Tang Rou’s decision making.

The players’ moods had changed by now. Soft Mist was as resolute as ever, but Team Everlasting’s Heavenly Rage was starting to feel the pressure.

A high end move like Vanishing Step wasn’t something that Tang Rou could use, but even with a normal Juggle, Team Everlasting’s Qi Master failed to regain the advantage twice!

After their belief in having field and character advantage was shattered, their belief in their player superiority had finally been shattered as well.

Eventually, Heavenly Rage managed to grasp the third chance to escape from the Juggle!

But he was still in a disadvantageous position. Soft Mist’s attacks were unrelenting, not giving Heavenly Rage a chance to struggle free.

In the exchange, the health of both sides were continuously decreasing, but it was obvious that Heavenly Rage’s health was falling faster. He managed to find a few chances to counterattack and deal some damage to Soft Mist, but it wasn’t much. His counterattacks had no effect on the overall situation, and that was probably why his opponent wasn’t very concerned about them.

Team Everlasting’s player became more and more impatient, unable to calm himself as the battle progressed. Eventually, he left an opening that Tang Rou mercilessly exploited, using a combo that blasted him against one of the pillars of the veranda.

Absolute advantage!

But she didn’t let her guard down. Soft Mist’s fierce offense never wavered throughout the battle, even when her victory was certain, she didn’t show a hint of faltering.

Heavenly Rage finally fell.

Defeat wasn’t a result that they couldn’t accept. The problem was that Soft Mist had only lost less than a fourth of her health in this match. There seemed to be an unbridgeable gap between the two players...

Was it really unbridgeable?

Not necessarily. Skill was an intangible concept, unlike health which could be calculated. The difference in health of the two didn’t necessarily represent the difference in skill, but it revealed the difference in performance during the match.

This difference silenced all the spectating faceslappers once more. They had no chance to unleash their mockery ever since the second individual competition. Holding it in for so long was painful. And now, Soft Mist was gearing up to face her second opponent, Team Everlasting’s elementalist, in the group arena with more than three quarters of her health left. If she lost this match, how would they be able to mock her? They had to think carefully about what to say! After all, she had already beaten one opponent, losing to the second wasn’t uncommon.

Yet, before they could think of how to mock her, the situation on the battlefield was already becoming clear. Soft Mist somehow still had the advantage.

She wouldn’t win again, would she?

Everyone looked on with shock.

Team Everlasting had sent out an Elementalist, which Soft Mist had already managed to close in on. Compared to Qi Masters, Elementalists were garbage at close combat. Now, his health was draining away like someone had pulled the plug on it. When he finally managed to shake her loose, his health was already at the same level as Soft Mist’s! He had entered the arena with a twenty five percent health advantage and now that advantage had vanished.

Though he managed to escape from an undesirable situation, he didn’t get any chance to rest. Soft Mist charged fiercely towards him. Two mage classes with very different styles clashed. First the Elementalist would kite the Battle Mage around, chipping at her health, then the Battle Mage would close in and tear through the Elementalist with her close combat advantage.

But this time, the Elementalist didn’t manage to find another chance to escape from her grasp. Erupting with a final round of vicious attacks, Soft Mist defeated the Elementalist with a fifth of her health to spare, and geared up to face Team Everlasting’s third player.

The spectators had nothing to say, but those who had hope and supported Happy started to cheer wildly.

At first, they wouldn’t dare discard their composure for this. Though they thought Team Happy was interesting, and wanted to see what they could do, they were like the faceslappers, not believing that Team Happy truly had the power to go up against Team Excellent Era.

This was undebatable. Never mind outsiders, even those within Team Happy, Ye Xiu and Wei Chen and the others, they admitted it. If they really faced off against Team Excellent Era the way they were now, their chances were extremely low.

These people also had some misgivings about Team Happy’s strength and hadn’t formed much of an attachment to Team Happy, so they had to be careful with their support. They wouldn’t publically yell and cheer about it, because there were a bunch of spectators just waiting to see Happy humiliated! This small section of supporters lacked confidence and couldn’t tie themselves to Happy’s name. They didn’t want their support to be treated like a joke if Team Happy actually lost.

But now, Soft Mist had consecutively beat down two people and entered the third match with one fifth of her health remaining. This sort of advantage was very hard to turn around. Seeing a definite victory for Team Happy, these supporters finally dared to express their passion and energy, cheering encouragements for Team Happy.

This support was even more disgusting than eating a fly to the faceslappers, but they had no way of retorting. Team Everlasting’s last player would have to beat Tang Rou and then win against another two consecutive matches in order to take back the group competition. There was no need to elaborate on how hard that would be.

Team Everlasting’s mood was even worse.

"What the hell is this!!" He An, who remained calm upon losing two individual competitions, could no longer stay quiet after two people were beaten by Soft Mist.

He could accept one defeat, but having one player beat two of theirs was a major loss that he couldn’t take.

The Qi Master and Elementalist that lost these two rounds hung their heads in shame, feeling disheartened. Hearing He An’s words, the Qi Master raised his head, opening his mouth to speak, but then heard He An continuing. "Is this Soft Mist really that strong?"

The Elementalist player also raised his head, but stayed silent after exchanging a glance with the Qi Master player.

He An didn’t continue to speak because he had to prepare for battle.

Team Everlasting’s core character, Spellblade Go Forth, was currently He An’s character.

That meant He An’s position in the team wasn’t just as an ordinary team member, but as Team Everlasting’s ace.

With his character now in the arena, He An didn’t have the time to lecture the two players who had been defeated. He had to go back and turn the tides, as the ace player.

One versus three?

He An sneered. It was probable that the only one who believed that Team Everlasting could win back the group arena was himself! Because the tide of the match was now in his complete control and he had utter confidence in himself. The superiority he displayed at that time wasn’t baseless. Speaking of strength, he, the player who was also the manager, was the best in the current Team Everlasting. As their core player, his character naturally possessed the best equipment as well.

Go Forth had eight pieces of silver equipment. Team Everlasting only had 32 pieces of silver equipment in total, and ten characters. Among them, their ace Go Forth possessed one fourth of their silver equipment. Maybe it was because of this treatment that this character became the ace, or maybe it was because this character became the ace that it received such treatment. Either way, it was a positive loop. Go Forth was Team Everlasting’s strongest character, and they had never abandoned this core character even after being eliminated from the Pro League.

His character was immensely powerful and he had confidence in himself. One versus three? That was exactly what He An thought to do.

Go Forth appeared in one of the corners of Riverside Veranda. Three, two, one, match begin.

Despite having only a fifth of her health left, Soft Mist was as direct as ever. As soon as the countdown was over, she was already streaking down the path she took in both the previous rounds. As for Go Forth, he immediately turned and jumped into the water upon the fall of the countdown.

Home game advantage?

Character advantage?

Player superiority?

All of Team Everlasting’s advantages seemed to have been shattered by Happy, but now He An was planning to reinstate them and show everyone that Happy was nothing but cannon fodder compared to Team Everlasting.

Being different from the others, He An’s choice of action made Tang Rou’s charge lose meaning. With the current distance between them, she had no idea where He An’s Go Forth was. She could only slow down, carefully keeping an eye on her surroundings as she advanced.

Tang Rou didn’t impatiently try to find her opponent; she had to make sure her character was safe first.

But having scoured half the map, Tang Rou still didn’t find her target. If it wasn’t for the omniscient view the spectators had, this sort of running and hiding would be boring, but with their omniscient view, the spectators knew that Go Forth was settled under a part of the veranda. If Tang Rou only kept notice of the water’s surface while on the veranda, she wouldn’t be able to find him unless she entered the water as well.

Tang Rou didn’t seem to have such plans. Soft Mist was still moving along the veranda, but step by step, she entered Go Forth’s attack range.

He An was patient and didn’t press on the moment Soft Mist came into range.

A little closer… just a little closer...

Seeing the distance between them become more appropriate, the Sllver weapon in Go Forth’s hand, Aqua Lightning Lightsaber, began to flash.

The Spellblade’s signature move, Wave Formation, activate!

Chapter 815: The Careful He An

Electric Wave Formation!

The skill activated silently and by the time Tang Rou noticed, the Electric Wave Formation’s ball of lightning had already formed. The area within 15 units of it was filled with sparks. When the skill was activated, Soft Mist was electrocuted once. It was unavoidable. Tang Rou hastily had her character step out of range. With only a fifth of her health left, she didn’t dare delay. Soft Mist attempted to charge out of the Electric Wave Formation through the shortest route.

But who knew that this was exactly what He An wanted. From where Go Forth was settled, he could see half of Soft Mist’s figure, but this was more than enough. The second Formation was sent out, but this time it was an Ice Wave Formation. The two Formations overlapped, trapping Soft Mist within them.

Seeing this, Tang Rou realized that her opponent had been prepared for this and could see Soft Mist’s movements. No matter how she tried to escape, she would probably be incapable of shaking him off. Making a decision, she jumped up resolutely and dived for the water next to the veranda.

Tang Rou displayed her usual brave decisiveness. By jumping into the water, she immediately saw Go Forth, who had settled under the veranda. Without a moment’s hesitation, she charged forth with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

The flow of water split into two around Soft Mist. In the water, the charge speed of Dragon Breaks the Ranks was greatly reduced, but the drag force from the water affected everything. Even though attacks were slowed, dodging was also slowed. He An was prepared for this as well. With a swing of Aqua Lightning lightsaber, a strike of Chilling Sword Pulse was sent out. Shards of ice shot off from the blade, as if dispersed by the flow of the water, but anyone who understood the settings in Glory would know that water did have some effect on the power of skills, especially for fire, which was at a major disadvantage in water. On the other hand, ice type damage wasn’t just unaffected by the water, but was actually strengthened by it. This Chilling Sword Pulse looked like it had been scattered by the water, but actually it’s range had been silently expanded.

It didn’t look like much, but it’s power was immense!

The reinforced Chilling Sword Pulse met the charging Soft Mist and swept over her.

A hit!

Soft Mist’s movement speed was slowed even further by Chilling Sword Pulse. He An’s Go Forth had already left his original position, already preparing a new attack to unleash on the approaching Soft Mist.

Of course, Tang Rou knew that the situation wasn’t looking good for her, but didn’t cancel Dragon Breaks the Ranks. With the distance between her and Go Forth, there weren’t any attack that she could hit. If she stopped now, she still had to close in on Go Forth. That wasn’t as efficient as if she just used this Dragon Breaks the Ranks as a way to increase her movement speed.

Tang Rou’s choice was obviously made out of having no other choice. She was at a major disadvantage, and He An had this situation entirely under his own control. If it wasn’t for having another two opponents to face later on, He An would have just charged forwards to go head to head with Soft Mist and diminish what remaining health she possessed. Here, He An chose a safer method, deciding not to face Soft Mist head on, keeping his distance and slowly dragging it out.

This was the worst kind of style for Tang Rou. Soft Mist only had a fifth of her health starting out in this round, and then she had been ambushed too. She was already at red blood, how could she afford to drag this out? On the other hand, if they went head to head, she might not win, but she could at least take out some of her opponent’s life.

Unfortunately, He An was very cunning, not giving her such a chance. Slowly chipping away at Soft Mist’s health in the water, he used the Spellblade’s slight advantage in attack range to chip her to death.

"Heheh, that’s wasn’t so bad!" After he won, He An turned to joke with the other members of Team Everlasting. The continuous losses had reduced Team Everlasting’s morale to ice. And for this victory, no matter how he went to describe it, he had only won against an opponent with one fifth of her health left. There wasn’t enough meaning to it. That’s why He An had to appear as if it took him nothing to do. The more it seemed like an easy victory, the better it would boost morale.

It was unfortunate that after defeating this opponent who only had a fifth of her health, Happy still had two players who hadn’t gone up yet. Being at such a disadvantage, Team Everlasting couldn’t avoid feeling uneasy.

The Challenger’s League was far too cruel. It was possible that a single loss here could cut this year short for Team Everlasting. Who could relax with He An’s reassurance when thinking of this?

This was all He An could accomplish for now. He needed a real and valuable victory to bring hope back to his teammates.

The second round of the group arena started shortly. Team Happy’s second player was the Launcher Chasing Haze.

No matter who it was, He An didn’t dare to let down his guard. As soon as the countdown three, two, one, was over, his Go Forth turned and dived into the water once more.

Launchers had an absolute attack range advantage. When facing head to head, the Launcher always attacked first. By the time you got into attacking range, you would have already received quite some damage. If your charge wasn’t successful, the damage you took would be more than just a little.

If this was an individual competition, He An wouldn’t be afraid of charging forward, but they were fighting the group competition right now. After Chasing Haze, there was still another opponent that he had to fight. So, like last time with Soft Mist, he decided to use a careful method.

How could He An guess that his opponent was actually much more nervous than he was.

In the first three seconds of the match, Chen Guo was close to entering a space where she couldn’t even tell where her fingers where. Her mind was entirely blank. There were things moving in front of her eyes, but her brain seemed unable to receive these signals sent by her eyes.

Chen Guo was completely unprepared.

Ye Xiu actually pushed her into the line-up; he had never discussed this with her beforehand.

And to think that Chen Guo was unhappy that Ye Xiu saw her as a stopgap for the number of members in their team. Now that she was sent to the battlefield as an official player, Chen Guo realized she would rather be a stopgap. The pressure of being in the arena far overwhelmed her expectations. Thinking of what the results of this match could mean for them made Chen Guo terrified.

In her mind, she couldn’t possibly win. The opponent was a pro player, the character was the ace of a pro team! As for her? Even with the Heavenly Domain challenge she had help from Tang Rou to pass. From this angle, she wasn’t even as good as Concealed Light! Concealed Light had at least completed the Heavenly Domain Challenge on his own!

Nervous, she was so nervous. From the beginning of the match, she hadn’t had a moment of calm. When she came back to herself, she realized the match had started and her opponent was nowhere to be seen. This made her even more nervous.

"Ah! When did the match start, where’d he go?" Chen Guo yelped in surprise like she would when playing the typical in-game arena matches.

Everyone looked at her with serious expressions, but no one answered.

Chen Guo snapped back to reality. This was a competition; it might be online and there might be no one watching them, but this was a real Alliance organized competition.

Chen Guo tried to calm herself down. She couldn’t see the opponent, but of course he couldn’t be outside of the map. He must’ve gone underwater again. This was how this guy dealt with Tang Rou in the last round. The memory was fresh in her mind, and she even thought scornfully about the opponent’s dirty tricks. However He An couldn’t hear her, so all she did was make Qiao Yifan feel awkward. He An’s plan in the last round was rather akin to how he had won his individual match.

Chen Guo didn’t get the chance to make anymore scornful comments, seeing how the character for the second round was just revealed to be her Chasing Haze.

"Surprise!"

Seeing the smile on Ye Xiu’s face, Chen Guo was frustrated. Was this really the time to joke around? Letting her into the arena, was that really a responsible thing to do?

But before she could yell, Ye Xiu’s smile disappeared, saying to her, "Good luck! Even if you lose, it’s ok; you have me at your back!"

"You…" Chen Guo was still quite displeased, but she couldn’t say anything. The line-up couldn’t be changed, after all. She rushed to take up the position. Yet as soon as it started, she was besieged by her nerves. Even telling herself that Ye Xiu was there to hold fort didn’t work.

Now, Chen Guo had finally gotten into her competitive mood. It was just that He An’s Go Forth had dived into the water, leaving her helpless. With her skill, she didn’t dare jump into the water to fight him. She could only wander the veranda, occasionally firing a few shots into the water, hoping to find a hint of Go Forth.

He An still didn’t let Go Forth close in and found an appropriate position to hide and watch Chasing Haze’s movements on the veranda.

He An still hadn’t figured out the depth of Happy’s skill, so he planned to observe the opponent before making any moves. He would be able to figure out his opponent’s vague skill level from seeing what moves his opponent made.

Yet as Chen Guo started to shoot at the water, it seemed like a fair choice to make, but Chen Guo’s blasts were completely chaotic. Like in the second individual match, Team Everlasting’s Sharpshooter attempted to force Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash from the water, but his attacks had a method to it. He had made estimations on One Inch Ash’s position, range and distance, but for Chen Guo? It was just wherever Chasing Haze walked, she would blast, no calculations, no judgements...

Is she pretending to be dumb to bait me?

He An was very much on guard; even when seeing Chen Guo’s clumsy technique, he didn’t make a move.

He observed for a while longer, until Chasing Haze had walked more or less on top of his Go Forth. She still fired a shot to the left, a shot to the right and moved on. He An finally confirmed that this person wasn’t playing dumb, she was actually dumb!

So, after Chasing Haze walked by, He An attacked at once. Multiple Wave Formations were thrown out and Chasing Haze looked wildly around before finally finding Go Forth’s position, but her lack of technique had already been witnessed by He An; he wasn’t afraid at all to have Go Forth jump out of the water to exchange blows with Chasing Haze.

The situation was extremely one-sided. When Chasing Haze fell, He An’s Go Forth had only lost a sliver of his life. That meant he had managed to get to the deciding match in near perfect shape.

The audience was bubbling with excitement, and so were Team Everlasting’s players.

Chapter 816: Too Naive

Reverse sweep!

At this moment, whether it was in the spectator chat or Team Everlasting’s practice room, these two words were mentioned the most. The second-most mentioned words added an adjective to it: super reverse sweep.

In a 1v3 situation, He An actually managed to beat two opponents in a row and entered the final deciding match with nearly full health. Such a turnaround filled the audience with anticipation.

Team Everlasting had been half-dead. As the second opponent was triumphed over, each and every player’s morale started to revive. When He An nearly obtained a perfect victory over Chasing Haze, silence filled the practice room for two seconds, before the players erupted into cheers.

Everyone was standing around He An, pushing and shoving each other. If they didn’t know that one more match still needed to be played, they might have started lifting He An up into the air.

He An obviously had to show confidence and give off a feeling of superiority at this moment. Apart from that, the victory already said everything. Their current situation said everything. He didn’t need to give any words of encouragement. The players of Team Everlasting had already come back to life. Next up, if he could win this deciding match, Team Everlasting’s morale would be at its peak for the team competition.

Morale cannot be underestimated.

Morale represented the player’s mental state. Having high morale made it easier for the player to play to the best of his or her ability. After all, a player was a person, not a robot. A player’s mental state decided how well a player performed.

He An was very satisfied with the morale of the team right now. Moreover, he was certain that after having a huge lead reduced to nothing, Team Happy’s morale must be very low. The two sides were on nearly even ground coming into the deciding match. If it had to be said, in terms of health, He An had lost a bit. However, in terms of the overall situation, He An felt that their Team Everlasting had the advantage. The pressure from a reverse sweep was terrifying. Just look at the countless spectators spamming the chat. Everyone was looking forward to this scene.

He An was too busy to think too much. After a short break, the deciding match began. On Team Happy’s side, the character that should have originally been paid attention to the most, but had been hiding the entire time appeared: Lord Grim.

He An wasn’t surprised about this arrangement. Lord Grim had always been seen as Team Happy’s core. This was undoubtedly Ye Qiu’s character. Even though the media reported that the person, who registered Lord Grim, wasn’t Ye Qiu. However, when He An paid a visit to Happy Internet Cafe, he personally saw Ye Qiu at Happy. If the player behind Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, who could he be?

The Challenger League had this type of loophole. He An could only look at things from a worst-case scenario standpoint. He thought his confidence was unbreakable, but when he thought about having to face Ye Qiu, the king of a past era, the innovator of countless techniques, and the Glory Textbook, He An suddenly felt the sweat dripping his two hands.　　

He An grabbed the towel on the table and dried his two hands.

There was no time for him to adjust his mental state. The stage came into view. Three, two, one, and the match began. He An put down the towel and took a deep breath.

No matter who his opponent, victory was his only path. It was only path for Team Everlasting too.

Team Everlasting had failed to pass through the Challenger League last year. A year without the Pro League naturally led to losses. Another year of losses would be needed again. The team’s ace player, He An, also had to be the club’s manager. It was evidence of Team Everlasting being in difficult financial straits. If they couldn’t return to the Pro League this year, the team might not last for another year. Let alone being able to support high salaries for the players, anyone worthy of a high salary would not continue playing for Team Everlasting. The team would need to sell characters, equipment, and materials to survive. In that case, the team would definitely weaken, making it even harder to get through the Challenger League. Many relegated teams fell into this vicious cycle until they disbanded.

I can’t lose!

He An reminded himself once again.

He had originally considered himself invincible, but after thinking that Lord Grim might be Ye Qiu, his confidence wavered. He couldn’t help but remind himself.

The spectator chat was as lively as ever. The face slappers resurrected just like Team Everlasting. This scene was simply too exciting. Team Happy had a huge lead, but they lost it all. Moreover, Team Everlasting’s character had barely lost any health. He had the momentum from winning two matches in a row and had high morale, but Team Happy? They were probably too nervous to even move.

The crowd jeered loudly. However, their remarks could no longer be seen by the two sides playing.

My opponent is Ye Qiu…..

Unable to get rid of this thought, He An was unable to play boldly. He repeated his old strategy and started by directly entering the water.

He slowly swam towards a section and found a hiding spot. It was obviously different from the hiding spots from the other two matches. He An once again began observing his opponent.

But he couldn’t find him…..

With the water and the veranda, his line of sight was naturally limited. Within this limited space, He An couldn’t find any traces of his opponent. He patiently waited for awhile, but still didn’t see Lord Grim. He finally felt like something wasn’t right…..

If Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, then... he shouldn’t be afraid of a battle in the water, so he might have gone into the water too. Could he be moving closer to me?　

He An thought and hastily dove into the water. After looking 360 degrees around him, he still didn’t see anything.

Where is he?

He An suddenly panicked. This situation was completely outside of his expectations. Could he just be standing at his original position? He An had his character switch positions. From a new perspective, he looked at Lord Grim’s starting position. No, Lord Grim hadn’t remained there. He had moved, but He An didn’t know where.

Two choices.

Take the initiative to search for Lord Grim, or continue hiding there and wait for Lord Grim to find him.

After a moment of hesitation, He An decided to choose the safer option and quietly hid there, waiting for Lord Grim to enter his attack range, but considering his opponent’s skill, he didn’t dare look only in one direction. Above the water, under the water, front, back, left, right, he didn’t stop looking around.

Even so, He An still didn’t see Lord Grim. His heart was beating madly. What’s going on?

Above the water, under the water, front, back, left, right…...　　

He kept scouting around. He was starting to get tired. He suddenly began to regret choosing this map. Wasn’t he causing himself trouble? If he had chosen a simpler map, he wouldn’t be in this type of situation.

He An was sighing with sorrow, when he suddenly caught himself.

I’m actually complaining about the map!

This would mean that this map was giving him trouble, putting him at a disadvantage. The map might have already been taken advantage of by the opponent.

He An’s reaction was quick. Under this situation, he needed to switch strategies. He had already fallen into his opponent’s trap! Even though neither side could see each other, this was an attack in and of itself. The attack wasn’t physical, but mental. He An was currently feeling troubled, making him the one affected by the attack.

He An swam underneath the veranda. He was just about to go back onto the veranda before making his next step, when he suddenly heard a shout: "He’s on top!!"

He An was startled. His character immediately turned. He saw Lord Grim’s spear come down with a Circle Swing. Like a fish being hooked, he was dragged out.

The shout had obviously come from a Team Everlasting player. They were in spectator mode and could look at the match from any perspective. He An’s trouble and confusion could clearly be seen by them.

Lord Grim kept moving, but not completely underwater or on the veranda. He did both, making it difficult to understand his intent.

Then, everyone discovered that Lord Grim was coming and closer to He An, while He An was looking around without a clue.

He An didn’t seem to be faking it. Everyone now understood that Lord Grim’s strange pathing was to hide in He An’s blind spots.

Could he have guessed his hiding place? Or was he also going to blind spots for all possible hiding spots? They couldn’t tell, but they knew that Lord Grim had quietly snuck up above He An. On the other hand, He An was still looking below the water, above the water, and searching around left and right…..

The crowd had already started shouting it out, but He An couldn’t see any of it.

The players on Team Everlasting could obviously warn him, but they maintained their competitive integrity. They were bitterly conflicted.

Finally, He An naively swam out from below that veranda, not knowing that his opponent was already waiting for him with his spear out. Someone on Team Everlasting abandoned his competitive integrity and gave a warning.

But it was too late.

Dodging an attack from land while in the water wasn’t an easy task. Even more so against someone as skilled as Ye Xiu. He An was dragged onto the veranda. Lord Grim stepped down and shot him in the head a few times. Sharpshooter skill: Punisher.

"The same map. The same strategy. How naive." In the match public chat, a message from Lord Grim appeared.

Chapter 817: Never Before Seen Combo

How could He An have the time to start trash talking with Ye Xiu? Once the Punisher ended, he hastily took the chance to make Go Forth roll, but Lord Grim’s movements were as quick as ever, striking down with a Berserker’s Collapsing Mountain. The curled up Go Forth was instantly struck flat to the ground.

Dodging wasn’t enough!

Knowing that Lord Grim was a critical member of the opposing team, Team Everlasting would naturally do their research on the unspecialized class. Unspecialized characters only had low level skills. Compared to high level skills, they had lower damage, but they activated quickly, had little ending lag, and low cooldown times. And to think an unspecialized character had 120 of these skills; there were too much variations for combinations. Even more importantly, the tactics for unspecialized characters in the Glory circle were unknown. Unspecialized characters had long been eliminated. Who would go and and research what combinations could be performed with the low level skills of all 24 classes? Even though Team Everlasting put effort into researching, they didn’t have that sort of time. They hadn’t managed to make much progress yet!

Lord Grim had approached He An without notice. He had gained the upper hand with a successful sneak attack, but this wasn’t enough to grasp victory. Whether he could keep this advantage in the following fight depended on the skill of the players.

But now, Go Forth had been beaten into the ground; was there really any need to consider their skill levels any further? He An now had a basic understanding of this unknown unspecialized. He couldn’t make accurate judgements because he lacked experience, so dodging wasn’t enough. What about parrying?

He An glued his gaze on Lord Grim’s attacking hand, preparing to parry. Then Lord Grim raised his strange weapon and… made a circle with it. He An didn’t have the time to figure out what attack was being made. Seeing how the weapon started to swing, he hurriedly struck out with his sword in a parry, but Lord Grim’s weapon drew a circle in the air and then made no more moves.

He An paused in surprise. His parry was only half finished! Now that his opponent wasn’t pressing forward anymore, then… should he turn his parry into an attack? As the thought passed through his mind, Go Forth involuntarily slipped backwards and then his feet left the ground.

This is!

He An was shocked, and then he realized that the circle Lord Grim drew was an Elemental Power.

The Elementalist’s knock-up skill.

He An wanted to cry. This was the problem with facing an unspecialized. Even if you tried to prepare yourself, even if their skill had been activated, your brain might not be able to catch up. Did He An not recognize this Elementalist’s knock-up skill? Of course not. The point was that the unspecialized skill tree wasn’t something he was used to. Against any of the other classes, He An would be able to subconsciously list out all of their skills. This was a habit of any experienced pro player and didn’t require any extra effort on their part, but now, facing an unspecialized, it was something he had to consciously do, reducing his reaction speed by a little. But just this little bit had a decisive effect. Having been caught by Elemental Power, Go Forth was now airborne. Lord Grim slid over, his Thousand Chance Umbrella swinging up as a spear and reinforcing the effects of Elemental Power with a Sky Strike. Go Forth was knocked even higher. Then, the spear shrunk back, and the point of the umbrella opened up to reveal the dark holes of the muzzle of his gun. Bullets swept out and across without hesitation.

The Launcher’s Gatling Gun technique pushed Go Forth even higher than he already was, making him spin uncontrollably in mid-air.

This really didn’t do much damage...

Seeing Go Forth’s health fall, He An had this sort of experience.

Though Lord Grim borrowed quite a few pieces of equipment from Heavenly Swords, Go Forth’s equipment was still better. And the equipment that DPS depended most on, Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, was still in the midst of leveling up.

Calm down! Unspecialized characters don’t deal very high damage, I can still find plenty of chances.

He An hurriedly reassured himself. His palms were all sweaty by now, but how could he have the time to go and wipe them? Not a single one was wasted with Gatling Gun’s hail of bullets, all hitting Go Forth. Finally free from his uncontrollable spin, Go Forth started to freefall. Lord Grim had already taken steps to charge over. He An hastily adjusted Go Forth’s position, preparing to sneak in an attack before anything could happen and hopefully turn the situation around.

But, he raised his sword, where was his target? He looked around. Lord Grim had somehow taken that moment to disappear...

"Under you!!!" Uncaring for the rules and having already broken them once, the members of Team Everlasting didn’t hesitate to help He An again. Lord Grim was currently right under Go Forth, waiting for him to fall!

Under him? He An quickly looked that was, but he still couldn’t see anything. He An then had a realization.

Vanishing Step, this was Vanishing Step! Nevermind He An, even All Stars wouldn’t dare say they could perform such a high skilled technique so well without a certain amount of experience and awareness.

Ye Qiu, this guy must be Ye Qiu!

He An felt unbalanced. If his opponent really was Ye Qiu, then that was cheating! They should lose the right to participate; their character should be sealed, but the problem was, could he prove it? With just Vanishing Step, he couldn’t prove anything. This move did have incredible technical difficulty, but it was one that every pro player was working toward. Even He An would attempt to accomplish Vanishing Step when he managed to knock-up an opponent. It was just that he wouldn’t always be able to perform it accurately, but he could occasionally succeed.

Ye Qiu could definitely perform Vanishing Step, but it wasn’t an if-and-only-if situation where whoever could perform Vanishing Step was definitely Ye Qiu.

He An was frustrated at his opponent finding someone to fight on their behalf, but had forgotten that his teammates gave him outside help, which also violated the rules.

He An knew that picking at these details would do nothing to help him. There was a way to deal with Vanishing Step, but for such a terrifyingly powerful technique, it would naturally be difficult to deal with. If it was easy to deal with, then the practicality of such a technically demanding move would be questioned.

He An had no confidence that he could deal with this move directly. Eventually, Go Forth unsheathed his sword and swung out with a Falling Light Blade. He An couldn’t determine Lord Grim’s exact position, so this use Falling Light Blade seemed rather dumb, like he was struggling mindlessly, trying to escape, but since Falling Light Blade created a small shockwave upon hitting the ground, he might get lucky and deal some damage.

Everyone else could see that with this Falling Light Blade from Go Forth, he really did "go forth". Coming down at this angle, his back became perfectly exposed to Lord Grim.

As for Lord Grim? He had his palm raised for quite a while. It wasn’t posing, but charging up a Falling Flower Palm.

Charging would naturally give the attack more power. Having exposed his back so perfectly, how could Lord Grim miss Go Forth? Lord Grim’s Falling Flower Palm struck the center of Go Forth’s back. Go Forth’s Falling Light Blade hadn’t even managed to touch the ground yet when he was blown flying, his body stretching out and lunging forwards.

When activating Falling Flower Palm, you could choose to stand still or slip forward. As Lord Grim sent out his Falling Flower Palm, he slid forwards to catch up. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had long since turned from a spear into a gun by the time he struck with his palm. Boom boom boom, three rockets were launched, preparing to push Go Forth even further.

Wasn’t this attack equal to sending Go Forth out of attack range and helping him escape? Just when people started thinking that, Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella swung out, neck and neck with the rockets. With another slide at his feet, Lord Grim’s spear stabbed into Go Forth’s body at the same time that the first rocket exploded behind him.

Circle Swing.

The technique that had fished Go Forth out from the water’s cooldown was up. Everyone had thought Go Forth would get blasted flying, but now he was pulled back with a stab. With the smoke that had yet to disperse from Go Forth’s body, he was slammed into the ground again.

Nevermind normal players, even the experienced pros in Team Everlasting were struck dumb with this combo. Falling Flower Palm, Anti-Tank Missiles and then a Circle Swing to pull them back. This was definitely not a combo that a normal class could perform, but it wasn’t something that just any Unspecialized player could do either. Linking Anti-Tank Missiles after Falling Flower Palm wasn’t hard, but then you had to somehow pull your target back with a Circle Swing! That required an extreme understanding of each skill.

The smoke from the explosion had yet to disperse from Go Forth’s body!

Though he was continuously being attacked, his health hadn’t even gone down by a tenth because of the difference in equipment and skills. This gave the audience hope in him, wishing that he would still be able to turn the tides.

He An wanted to do that, too, and quickly got up from where he had been smashed to the floor. But then a foot came crashing down from the sky, treading him back into the ground, and then several shots were fired at Go Forth’s head.

Punisher… the cooldown for that skill was finished, too.

Everybody became speechless. When Go Forth was fished out of the water, it was with a combo of Circle Swing and Punisher. Now, this scene repeated itself. Was he going to cycle through sending Go Forth into the air, onto the ground, Circle Swing and Punisher infinitely?

The audience was a little too worried. Glory wasn’t something you could win by simply cycling through a sequence. He An had already fallen prey to this routine once. After getting up, he would exceptionally wary.

He had to give it everything!

He An had realized that just getting up wasn’t possible. If he wanted to get up, he had to link it with an attack. This time when he jumped up, he took note of Lord Grim’s position and struck as he rolled. A Wave Wheel Slasher sped towards Lord Grim.

Chapter 818: Red Blood!

Wave Wheel Slash was a Spellblade grab skill. The Spellblade controlled the fluctuations from the sword to seal the opponent. Grabs could not be blocked. Trying to block it was equivalent to trapping yourself in your opponent’s move.

He An hadn’t hoped for this attack to hit Lord Grim. He just wanted to interrupt his opponent’s combo, so he could readjust his position.

He raised his sword above his head, but hit nothing. Go Forth still completed his roll into a crouching position, but... where was Lord Grim?

"Above you….." The same dishonest Team Everlasting player once again warned him. He An hastily adjusted Go Forth’s viewpoint, while also looking up himself.

Pow! Pow! Pow!

Striker skill: Eagle Stamp.

Lord Grim had been standing on top of his sword. He stamped three times and jumped to the side, escaping from Go Forth’s view again and leaving footprints on Go Forth’s face.

The Team Everlasting players were also speechless.

They could also tell that He An was already flustered. He An heard the warning and actually lifted his own head. That was obviously an instinctive reaction, but it shouldn’t be one for a pro player. A pro player should have thought that the warning was for an enemy attack and find some way to respond.

But He An actually looked up towards the ceiling. He was clearly lost.

He An was a mess, but Ye Xiu wasn’t. After Eagle Step, Lord Grim didn’t wait to land on the ground. Instead, he unsheathed his sword and descended with Falling Light Blade. It was quick follow-up from Eagle Stamp, but He An finally reacted and hastily rolled to the side to dodge. Halfway through his roll, Go Forth crashed into the veranda railing. The narrow veranda didn’t give him enough room to complete a full roll. When Falling Light Blade descended, Lord Grim was also blocked by the railing, but the shockwave still sent Go Forth tumbling into a corner. He An immediately tried to tech it, but he was blocked by the railing again. He couldn’t roll and get up. He became like a ball, bouncing around in the corner…..

The other Team Everlasting players shut their eyes.

They couldn’t watch anymore... losing’s fine, but could you at least lose in a less childish manner? What are you doing? Looking up into the sky, crashing into the wall, and then repeatedly rubbing against the wall, did your brain short circuit?

He An’s situation couldn’t be described as cutting a sorry figure. It was practically a comedy at this point, but after thinking about it carefully, Lord Grim didn’t seem like he was intentionally toying with He An. Forcing the opponent into the veranda meant he was taking advantage of the veranda’s narrow terrain to restrict his opponent’s movements. He An ignored this point and went blindly towards the railing, before ending up in this situation.

The face slappers and Team Everlasting fans were depressed. Those standing on Team Happy’s side found it hilarious on the other hand.

After being blocked by the railing, He An’s tech failed. Lord Grim chased after his trapped opponent and attacked fiercely.

There’s no way out!

He An looked left and right. There was only one choice. Seeing an opening, he immediately jumped. It was difficult for him to jump through, so he had to crouch in midair. It didn’t stop him from turning around at the same time. Finally, he decided to jump off the railing and into water.

Splash! Go Forth dove into the water. Another splash. Lord Grim didn’t hesitate and pursued closely after him. When Lord Grim got into the water, he gave Go Forth a kick too.

He An had been chased so closely. Go Forth failed to show any signs of hope, but because they were in the water, all of their movements were slower, so Go Forth’s health dropped slower.

Go Forth struggled in the water. The spectators all closed their eyes…..

This was a battle in the water? It was more like a fish meeting a great white shark and running for his life. When everyone saw Go Forth, they felt like it was because Lord Grim wasn’t giving him any choice but to run.

That wasn’t true. He An couldn’t find any openings among Lord Grim’s attacks, so he tried to create some distance between them. By winning space, he would win time to attack. Unfortunately, he kept on failing. Lord Grim stayed stuck to him, but because he stayed on the defensive, his actions just seemed like he was trying to run for his life.

Left, no good. Right, no good. Up, no good. Down, no good…...

Battling in the water allowed much more space to move in than battling on land. However, no matter what He An tried, Lord Grim would always stop him. The damage dealt by Lord Grim wasn’t much, but a lot of attacks hit him. Go Forth’s health gradually fell until it was about to hit red blood.

Players weren’t bosses. When a character’s health hit red blood, it wouldn’t become Enraged. Red blood would actually increase the pressure on the player even more. Berserkers were the only exception. As their health fell, their battle strength would increase. From time to time, Berserkers would make a comeback when they hit red blood.

He An wasn’t thinking about this. His Go Forth wasn’t a Berserker. His health continued to fall due to Lord Grim’s attacks. He was about to hit red blood, but his situation hadn’t changed in the slightest. From He An’s point of view, unspecialized attacks were completely unpredictable. He was trying his hardest to predict the next move out of all the possible low-level skills available, but it was to no avail. His processing ability wasn’t fast enough. He really couldn’t do anything.

He An had never felt so powerless before.

He was Team Everlasting’s ace player and core. His position as the Club manager wasn’t just for show either. He had played Glory for many years now. He had deep knowledge and experience of the game, but the reality was that he didn’t have any experience in the pro scene. After Team Everlasting was relegated two seasons ago, the team scouted him out and added him to the team, replacing Team Everlasting’s former captain, Hong Liang, who had left the team. He became Team Everlasting’s new Spellblade core.

The Spellblade character Sidingken used to be the team’s strongest character, but in order to relieve the pressure from being relegated, Sidingken was sold. This was the tragedy of small teams. All sorts of predicaments awaited for them as soon as they were relegated. Team Everlasting had three years to build up their foundation though. After Sidingken was sold, they quickly created Go Forth for He An.

He An was filled with ambition. He always felt like he was just lacking an opportunity. He considered himself a classic example of having talent, but no opportunity. Being favored by a relegated team had been an opportunity he had been waiting for. Through his knowledge and experience, he even earned himself the position of club manager. Team Everlasting had indeed found a very capable talent.

He An had been looking forward to Team Everlasting returning to the scene. He wanted everyone in Glory to know that a treasure had been ignored by everyone all along! It was his time to shine.

Unfortunately, the team lost in the finals of the Challenger League last season. Before they could walk out from the shadows of their loss, another bomb exploded, shattering the hearts of everyone who wanted to make it through the Challenger League into the pro scene.

Glory Pro League Season 8, Team Excellent Era had been miraculously relegated, becoming their opponents next season in the Challenger League.

This piece of news made everyone preparing for next season’s Challenger League fall into despair. Unrest arose among the various teams. Too many people weren’t willing to waste their time in the Challenger League because in their eyes, it was pointless. This year’s champions would be Team Excellent Era. Competing in the Challenger League this year would mean needing to compete in next year’s Challenger League as well. That would be two years. How many two years did an eSports career have? Many were willing to search for other paths to tread on rather than waste their lives here. Because in their eyes, no matter how distant their other paths were, there was at least hope, but there was not even a sliver of hope against Excellent Era.

Team Everlasting lost a few players because of this reason. He An stayed though. Wu Chen, who became Team Everlasting’s captain last season, also stayed. The team finally found a few other players to join. There were still a few players willing to give the Challenger League a try. After all, getting the first step into the pro scene was not an easy task for the vast majority of players.

Team Everlasting set sail. They didn’t have any confidence against Excellent Era, but they could still hope for a miracle.

But now, they had only reached the second step of their journey, and they were put into such an embarrassing situation already. Hopes, dreams, awaited miracles.... Everything suddenly came crashing down on He An the moment he hit red blood.

He wasn’t willing to lose in this way!

With this sudden realization, He An’s hands suddenly turned nimble and his mind cleared. How well a player performed on stage was affected by the player’s mental state. This was the so-called player condition. At this moment, He An awakened and displayed his peak performance.

Block, Wave Slash Wheel, Ice Wave Sword!

Three skills in a row. Defense, control, counterattack. He An stringed together this sequence of moves. Ice Wave Formation sent out a wave of ice. In the water, the attack spread even further as it wrapped around Lord Grim. He An’s movements were extremely quick. Go Forth had already started his next move and was in the middle of casting Electric Wave Formation.

Bang bang bang!

Lord Grim fired three Anti-Tank Missiles in different directions.

The first and second missile moved to the left and right, spurring on the waves. Only a pro player proficient in water battles would notice that these waves would affect the movement path of Ice Wave Sword. These two missiles rocked the waves, reducing Ice Wave Sword’s speed, while also pushing Lord Grim away. The third missile headed in the reverse direction.

Using this skill, Lord Grim brilliantly dodged this sudden Ice Wave Sword.

Electric Wave Formation!

But He An finished his cast too. A ball of electricity formed in the water.

Chapter 819: Low Morale

Lord Grim was inside Electric Wave Formation’s range. With the water slowing him down, this attack didn’t look like it could be dodged, but who would have thought that at this moment, Lord Grim raised the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella above his head. Ka ka ka. The umbrella contracted and the ribs merged together. Then, the ribs opened up and spun rapidly.

Mechanic skill: Rotor Wings. On land, it allowed the user to fly like a dragonfly. In the water, it was like a propeller. The spinning force pulled Lord Grim backwards and also created billowing waves, affecting Electric Wave Formation. Lord Grim easily escaped from Electric Wave Formation like a torpedo. In the blink of an eye, he was in front of Go Forth.

Even though He An was in high spirits, he wasn’t prepared for something so unexpected. Being in good condition, his reaction speed was fast. However, Ye Xiu was even faster. As soon as Lord Grim was within reach of Go Forth, he turned his body and grabbed Go Forth.

Grappler skill: Toss.

Go Forth was thrown over the shoulder straight out of the water. Lord Grim followed after him and floated up, right when Go Forth was falling down. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear form and then arced up into a Sky Strike. Ding! Go Forth was actually able to block it. He An’s condition was vastly different from before.

This block negated Sky Strike’s damage and knock-up effect. Go Forth swung his sword downwards towards Lord Grim with a Falling Light Blade.

Bang!

The surface of the water exploded. Lord Grim wasn’t able to dodge the Falling Light Blade in time, but he had managed to to throw out a grenade. Lord Grim was hit by the sword, and Go Forth was hit by the grenade. The two characters were blasted away from each other, but the two both tried to follow with another attack. Go Forth used Earthquake Sword on the surface of the water. Lord Grim fired Anti-Tank Missiles towards Go Forth.

Hit! The two characters were both hit again.

Who received more damage from these exchanges didn’t matter. Go Forth was already at red blood. This exchange of blows was certainly disadvantageous for him. Moreover, after the trade, He An wanted to cough blood. Not only was that trade not worth it, Lord Grim was currently healing himself!

What am I supposed to do!

He An felt the urge to throw his mouse and smash his keyboard to bits. It hadn’t been easy finding an opportunity to deal some damage to his opponent, but his opponent could even heal himself! Even though it wouldn’t be more effective than a heal from a Cleric or a paladin, Go Forth only had a sliver of health left. If they kept trading, he wouldn’t win! It’s not like he was against some random noob.

In reality, Lord Grim had plenty of health left and didn’t need to heal. Ye Xiu still decided to give himself a heal. His purpose for doing so was worthy of looking into. This heal was clearly a low blow to He An’s morale.

For the following battle, Ye Xiu completely relied on trading health for health, which was what He An was most afraid of. After fighting each other for awhile, Lord Grim cast another heal on himself…...

He An let out a long sigh. This was killing without spilling blood! Even if he released a powerful high-level skill, the damage done wouldn’t compare to the mental damage done by each heal that was cast. He An had lost all hope. He just didn’t want to surrender. The winner of this match was already obvious. He An’s brief burst of energy failed to result in anything. The Team Everlasting players were among the spectators, who became alive for a brief moment, but once that moment ended, the group arena ended in Team Everlasting’s loss.

Out of the individual competition and the group arena, Team Everlasting was only able to win one point in their home game. This situation was enough to make the glasses of many fall off and break. If they couldn’t win this team competition, Team Everlasting’s situation would be incomparably difficult. Team Happy would only need to win 2 points in their home game.

Team Everlasting’s practice room fell silent. The morale that He An ignited with his two victories in a row vanished with this single loss.

Seeing everyone’s expressions, He An felt a thread of fear in his heart. He suddenly noticed that he had missed something in the group arena match that just concluded.

This loss alone causing the morale of the entire team to plummet to the bottom was a bit too excessive. Although that victory was important, He An had to face three opponents in a row. Successfully achieving a reverse sweep was extremely difficult. A success would definitely boost their morale, but a loss was something that everyone had already been prepared for, so it should be mostly acceptable.

He An hadn’t considered this situation though.

After awakening the team’s morale with those two victories, he should have struck the iron while it was hot in the third round. That did not mean he needed to win. As long as he could show vigor, even if he lost, the morale obtained from the previous two matches wouldn’t plummet all the way back down.

Both the process and the results of the third round were important. He An had ignored this point. Like the previous two rounds, he continued to use the same strategy to win. This approach failed to work. The image of Go Forth looking as if he were a little fish trying to run from a great white shark.

Even though He An was able to display a glimmer of hope in the last few moments, that glimmer had been too brief. Lord Grim quickly switched to a trade-blood-for-blood strategy….. At that time, He An had already lost all hope. His mental state was reflected in his playing. His teammates could see it too.

Morale... He An had lost it all through his string of performances. This was his mistake. Seeing his teammates downcast, he realized that he had been too late to notice. He couldn’t provide any evidence. Just saying a few words wouldn’t be enough to stir up everyone’s spirits either. He An felt his head hurt. The team’s morale had fallen even further. He had already said what encouraging words he could say. At this moment, he could only hope that everyone realized the importance of the team competition!

"Everyone, cheer up!" He An was still melancholy. He didn’t think Wu Chen would speak. Wu Chen was Team Everlasting’s true captain. However, because of He An’s existence as the ace player and manager, the team captain’s authority became very awkward. Even so, Wu Chen’s feelings towards Team Everlasting was deeper than anyone else’s. He was the only one left who had stayed with Team Everlasting since its creation. He had been together with Team Everlasting through the Pro League, through relegations, and through the Challenger League. From start to finish, he was the only one, who never gave up on the team.

The next team competition would likely decide Team Everlasting’s existence. At this moment, although he was only the captain nominally, he still stood out to speak.

Team Everlasting was used to He An leading the team. When they suddenly heard Wu Chen come out at a crucial moment, they were surprised, but they soon remembered. Wu Chen was Team Everlasting’s captain. Moreover, their only point came from him, even if it was mainly because his opponent had gotten lost.

"At this point, we’re at the ends of our rope. If we cannot win the following team competition, we’ll be very disadvantaged in the next round. Everyone probably already knows that Team Happy isn’t as easy to defeat as we had imagined. We must fully utilize what we have. Don’t we have the home team advantage in the following team competition too? Our practice everyday has been for this very moment." Wu Chen didn’t shout, worry, or say anything encouraging. He calmly described their situation.

"Correct!" He An discovered that Wu Chen’s calm explanation had accomplished its desired effect. He didn’t want to miss this opportunity and added, "Don’t forget. We’re going to be challenging Team Excellent Era. How can Happy compare to Excellent Era?"

With this comparison, Team Happy not being anything was easily accepted by everyone. Everyone suddenly felt like their situation wasn’t as frightening as they thought.

"In the team competition, let’s show Happy our strength!" He An shouted powerfully. Even though the other players didn’t become as excited, they at least no longer looked dead like before.

The break time after the group arena quickly passed. Team Everlasting came out with their usual main force for the team competition.

Spellblade, Launcher, Warlock, Qi Master, and Cleric. Their reserve member was an Elementalist.

On Team Happy’s side, their team lineup also appeared on stage.

Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands. Their reserve member was Wei Chen’s Windward Formation.

The lineup on both sides wasn’t anything unexpected.

The face slappers among the crowd were quiet. They didn’t know what to say. They discovered that Team Everlasting’s match didn’t seem to be any different from the ones, when Team Happy had been openly accepting challenges. They could only cheer for Team Happy’s opponents, but their opponents would end up getting beat, causing them to lose face. After experiencing the same thing again and again, the face slappers had learned to be cautious. However, Team Everlasting had originated from the pro scene and dominated Steamed Bun Invasion in their first fight. Their expectations rose, but they still fell into the trap! Their shouting and cheers had been traded for swollen cheeks just like before.

This time, the face slappers weren’t going to speak first. They should at least wait until Team Everlasting had a clear advantage, right?

Team competition. 3, 2, 1, start!

Chapter 820: They’re Actually in the Lead?

The Team Competition between Team Happy and Team Everlasting was finally about to commence. Everlasting still had the choice of map and for the time in the match it wasn’t River Veranda.

Flagged Flame Springs.

In the training yard under the setting sun, multicolored banners fluttered in the wind. These flags weren’t just there for decor, each one was a singpost. Where there was a flag, there was either the eye of a spring or a pit of fire. These areas weren’t areas that you could step lightly. Because of these flags, there was a lot more to consider when fighting on this map. Those who hadn’t undergone special training for it would be in trouble. The reason for picking this map was because Team Everlasting wanted to continue using their opponent’s inexperience to their advantage.

In the public chat, Team Everlasting’s true fans were still persistently cheering for their team.

Those who came to shame Happy still had hope, but decided to act a lot more inconspicuously. Some had even left the room.

There were people leaving, but there were also people entering. The room numbers for the Challenger League were made public, and you could easily find the number for each team in the match schedule.

No one took notice of the few characters who had just entered the room, and these characters didn’t do anything to draw attention either. They entered the spectator stands and glanced at the current points. What they saw shocked them.

Club Excellent Era, meeting room.

Just after watching Team Excellent Era crush their opponents 9.5 to nil, Excellent Era’s CEO Tao Xuan and manager Cui Li directed their characters from the room they were in into Happy and Everlasting’s room.

When they saw who Happy had drawn, they had laughed. They wouldn’t deny that with Ye Qiu in Happy, the team would be strong, but with just the second round of the Challenger League they managed to draw a former Pro League team. Look’s like they didn’t have Fortune’s favor.

Tao Xuan wasn’t obsessed with personally dealing with Ye Qiu and Happy. So long as Happy was eliminated, no matter how it happened or who did it, he would automatically feel better. Now, Happy had been abandoned by fortune, Tao Xuan felt like this was a great thing.

But being the head of the club and the manager, Tao Xuan and Cui Li still stayed with their own team, as per their obligations, though they knew Excellent Era would have no trouble.

As soon as the match ended, the two congratulated their team members and went to see how Happy would be made a joke.

As the Challenger League official arena, there would naturally be something to keep score. The two used Cui Li’s character to go into the room and look at the current score. The two shook their heads, blinking in surprise.

4.5 to 1.

Team Happy 4.5, Team Everlasting 1.

They hadn’t misread it or seen it in reverse. Team Happy was in the lead with an absolute advantage. If they won the following team competition, then they would only need to get two points in the next round to assure their victory.

Tao Xuan and Cui Li exchanged glances and the match on the screen started. Cui Li immediately switched his omniscient view to Team Happy’s character, and suddenly shouted out in surprise, "That’s not possible!"

"What?" Tao Xuan had been distracted by his own thoughts, but quickly returned to reality at Cui Li’s hollering. Hastily looking at what Cui Li was pointing at onscreen, he froze in shock as well.

What made them so shocked was the equipment that Team Happy had equipped.

The quality of the equipment wasn’t something that would scare the two heads of Excellent Era. But the problem was that Team Happy should be very poor and lacking in materials, so where on earth did they get all these pieces of equipment from, especially the Silver ones?

For the omniscient view given to spectators, they didn’t need to close in on a character to see their equipment. They could see just by clicking on the character they wanted to view. The properties of Silver equipment were hidden, but the Silver letters couldn’t be anything but real. Of course, there was garbage among Silver equipment, but bringing them to the battlefield meant it was the real deal.

"One, two, three…" Cui Li clicked into the five characters on Happy’s side, starting to count the equipment. His tone changed as the number increased, all the way until seventeen, before it finally stopped. For a pro team, it wasn’t much, but since this was Happy, it was enough to stun Tao Xuan and Cui Li.

Having finished counting, Cui Li turned to look at his boss, seeing the incomprehension and disbelief he felt reflected on Tao Xuan’s face.

How long had it been since Team Happy had started working towards this? They actually had managed to procure seventeen pieces of Silver equipment already? Truly a stunning number.

Tao Xuan and Cui Li were intimately familiar with how pro teams worked. Suddenly procuring seventeen pieces of Silver equipment wasn’t easy. The two paused to process this. The two sides had already started fighting, but neither of them cared.

"Call Chen Yehui and get him over here," Tao Xuan suddenly ordered.

Being a manager that understood his boss, Cui Li was very much competent. Hearing this order, he immediately realized his boss’ intentions. He quickly got his phone and dialed Chen Yehui’s number, giving him the orders that his boss had yet to speak as well.

Chen Yehui was also watching Happy’s match! But unlike Tao Xuan and Cui Li, he hadn’t gone to Excellent Era’s match to show his regard for the team. From the beginning, he was in Happy and Everlasting’s room, spectating. Standing among the faceslappers, Chen Yehui was moved by how many people seemed to understand his feelings.

Who would’ve guessed that his emotions would get shoved right back into his face with the other people who understood him. Their cheering for Happy to lose hadn’t appeared again since the first round.

Chen Yehui had long since clicked on Happy’s characters to see their stats, and naturally received quite a shock. He hadn’t heard a sound or whisper of all this Silver equipment, but being a part of the in-game guild, Chen Yehui also fought to steal bosses and knew how well Lord Grim’s little alliance was doing.

But, even though they managed to steal so many bosses, they had to split the profits between five parties. With this, each party’s profits weren’t very impressive. With just what they had gained recently, it was enough to procure all this Silver equipment?

Chen Yehui was shaking his head as he looked through the materials. Then, he received a call from Cui Li who asked him to bring the reports on what wild bosses they had managed to steal.

Hearing this, Chen Yehui knew what this was all about. This was exactly what he was looking for. After hastily finding everything that he needed, he sped over to Club Excellent Era’s meeting room.

Club Excellent Era’s training room.

Though it was an online match, they were a team and they had to be conscious of that, so they couldn’t let just anyone grab a laptop and go to their own corner of their building to play. For matches, pro players had to be together.

But this was just a Challenger League match with a team that was far as can be from professional, so Excellent Era didn’t have to be too serious about it. Victory wasn’t something to make them happy, it was expected.

As soon as their match was over, the members of Team Excellent Era all left the training room. There wasn’t much that they needed to go over for this match, but after returning to their own rooms, everyone opened up their laptops and logged into Glory, grabbing an account and speeding off to the room they knew to go to in the Challenger League arena as if they had planned it together.

4.5 to 1?

Team Happy was in the lead?

Everyone was shocked, and even a little uneasy.

Team Happy… didn’t seem to be that weak of an opponent.

Among this unease, there was also someone who was very happy. Su Mucheng used her account to gracefully type out a "You can do it, Happy!" in the public chat.

Just five inconspicuous words, but this was the first direct sound of support that Happy had gained. Those who were on Happy’s side were mostly just here to see others humiliated and didn’t have any real feelings for Happy. Even if they yelled out encouragements for Happy, it was just to make some others disgusted.

And now, the sudden encouragement given by Su Mucheng’s character was very eye catching. Those who just came here to witness the walk of shame were all passionate people. With Su Mucheng’s words, the spectating faceslappers suddenly became reckless.

Not waiting for them to retort, Su Mucheng’s character quickly fired a "Happy for the win!"

Following the two sentences, they appeared again and again interchangingly. Su Mucheng hadn’t even used the hand speed that she was currently showing off in the match just now. The entire chat window was instantly flooded with her encouragements.

"Unacceptable!!!" The spectating faceslappers couldn’t hold it in anymore, starting to counter with their own retorts, but Su Mucheng had long since shifted her attention onto the match. She closed the public chat channel. There wouldn’t be anything important to see there anyways. The interactions between the players was shown in another window in the match.

But after scrutinizing the situation of the battle, Su Mucheng wasn’t as cheerful as before. On the other hand, the other members of Excellent Era breathed out sighs of relief. Though they didn’t know how Happy had gained such a lead, they didn’t seem to be that scary in the team competition?

In the meeting room, Tao Xuan and Cui Li calmed upon realizing the situation in the match. Chen Yehui had rushed to the meeting room in a hurry with the documents, but after stepping inside he heard his boss greet him with a calm, "You’re here?" Chen Yehui was a little lost, unsure where to put down the documents.

Cui Li reached out and took the documents after Chen Yehui sent him a questioning gaze and started to flip through. Chen Yehui didn’t have anything else to do, so he turned his attention to the competition being played on the projector.

Though they didn’t have the technical skills of pro players, they did spend their time in the pro circle so they had the judgement of pro players. It wasn’t long before Chen Yehui understood who had the upper hand in the match, instantly understanding why his boss seemed to be in good spirits.

Chapter 821: Terrain Features

"Team Everlasting is doing pretty well!" Chen Yehui pretended to blurt out, but he had actually thought long and carefully before attempting to start a conversation with this sentence.

"They are doing well." Tao Xuan nodded. In reality, after Team Everlasting had been eliminated from the Pro League and undergone several adjustments in players, their ability was far from being able to impress Excellent Era’s boss, but since Team Everlasting was helping them deal with an annoying problem, they weren’t as strict with their judgements. Seeing that Happy was at a disadvantage, they all praised Everlasting’s performance.

"Ai... It’s too bad!" Chen Yehui noticed a critical part, drawing out his words and expressing his pity.

Tao Xuan could no longer keep ignoring him with his attempts at making his presence known. He didn’t call Chen Yehui here to watch the match, after all.

"Ye Qiu seems to have been doing well in the Heavenly Domain recently?" Tao Xuan distractedly asked as he watched the match. Even though this was an arbitrary question that he didn’t seem to care for much, it revealed Tao Xuan’s attitude to the situation. Ye Qiu! He had only mentioned Ye Qiu, not Team Happy. It was clear that the threat of Happy came entirely from Ye Qiu. The only thing he was concerned about was Ye Qiu’s presence. Ye Qiu’s very existence represented everything.

"Well… it’s like this!" Chen Yehui took a moment to formulate a response. "If it was just Ye Qiu causing trouble, what he has managed to accomplish would be very impressive, but he utilized the power of four guilds along with his own. A total of five different guilds working together. So when they manage to steal a boss, they have to split their gains. If we look at it from that angle, their profits are just that."

"What do you mean, ‘just that’?" Tao Xuan was a little annoyed at the use of such vague phrasing, but the way the match was going was satisfying, so he didn’t get onto Chen Yehui’s case, and just glanced at him, hinting that he wanted an explanation.

"Since they haven’t become a strong competitor for very long, and weren’t always very stable, there’s no way to make an accurate estimate. If we talk about their current profits, then they get about what the top guilds get after splitting their spoils between all five parties, but we don’t know how stable they’ll be in the future," Chen Yehui hurried explained.

"Then what about our profits as of late?" Tao Xuan asked.

This was the question Chen Yehui was most afraid of because Excellent Dynasty’s profit wasn’t a pretty sight. If they were a small to mid sized guild then it would make sense, but they were a guild with glorious history. Alhough their team had been kicked out from the Pro League earlier this year, Excellent Era had no problems in continuing to function. If they could transfer over an All Star like Xiao Shiqing when they were eliminated, then there shouldn’t be any negative effects on their guild. Yet, it was just coincidentally at this time that Excellent Dynasty was struggling with fighting for bosses. The good thing was that they weren’t the only guild struggling. Chen Yehui quickly relayed what had been happening during the summer holidays, how many pro players started interfering in the fight for bosses along with Ye Qiu active role...

Tao Xuan was speechless after hearing this. He couldn’t help but think of the very first few years of the Alliance. Back then, there was no such thing as a holiday for pro players. The Alliance wasn’t 20 teams like it was now, and the competitive season was much shorter as well, making the holidays a lot longer, but once the holidays started, almost all the pro players would rush to the online game, fighting to gain materials and equipment for their teams. In the beginning, Silver equipment was rare and everyone used Orange equipment as their go-to choice for matches.

Excellent Era’s era of three consecutive championships was in part thanks to the foundations built through fighting for this equipment. The captain who had once spared no effort or expense for Excellent Era was now the most painful thorn in Tao Xuan’s side.

Thinking about this, Tao Xuan became distracted by his upsets. Chen Yehui seemed to say something, but he didn’t hear. However Cui Li went along with him, bringing over the documents that Chen Yehui had given him. Tao Xuan picked them up and quickly flipped through them, not seeming to have a care in the world. "Let’s watch the match first! I don’t think this round will be easy for him."

Him, not them. Team Happy. From the beginning Tao Xuan only took notice of that one person.

"Team Everlasting seems very familiar with this map." Cui Li added his opinion of the current topic. "Using the the banners to cover their positions and movements, though they’re at different places, they have cohesion between them. With a range of AoE attacks, they can cover their opponent with firepower and successfully surround them."

"Actually, they could be a little more daring. They could even switch their Cleric with their sixth member, adding another DPS. Happy’s members are currently unable to focus due to the topographical features of the map," Chen Yehui entered the discussion.

"I think that’s exactly what they’re planning on doing." Cui Li looked towards the screen. With an omniscient view, they could see Team Everlasting’s cleric moving under the cover the banners provided in the support zone, and the Cleric was switched out for the sixth member, the Elementalist. Like Chen Yehui had said, while having the upper hand, they could give up their healing and add a DPS to maximize the damage they would be able to deal to their opponents.

Five DPSers, all good with AoE attacks, Team Everlasting’s firepower coverage was instantly top notch. As the attacks flew, some would definitely hit the banners, triggering the terrain effects. This way, there would be more and more springs and fire pits on the map. After these areas were uncovered, they wouldn’t become hidden again. This would make it easier to tell where you could and couldn’t step.

Team Happy was struggling under such a situation and had lost any semblance of teamwork. Each character was fighting to take cover for themselves. Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim also had to be responsible for healing, having to send over a heal from time to time, but an Unspecialized’s healing was incomparable to the healing of a class that specialized in healing. The trade off in MP for healing wasn’t an affordable one for the Unspecialized class.

"This Cleric isn’t very good." Chen Yehui concluded. He couldn’t help but feel satisfied at how Ye Xiu was being forced to make up for his teammate’s shortcomings.

"He’s healing wherever Ye Qiu is. What use is he with such poor judgement?" Chen Yehui said with a smile.

Who would’ve thought that Tao Xuan and Cui Li’s expressions would change as soon as the words left his mouth.

He healed wherever Ye Qiu healed.

Even the dumbest healer wouldn’t need someone to guide him step by step. Pulling a player like that into the core position of a team wasn’t possible unless Ye Qiu’s brain had short circuited.

So there was only one possibility, and that was that their actions were intentional. Ye Qiu had planned for the healer to heal at his tempo.

This Cleric was, indeed, not the best, but he wasn’t as bad as they originally thought. Were Ye Qiu’s actions the most effective way of supporting their team?

Thinking of this, the three started to take notice Cold Hands’ healing.

Positioning, healing targets, it was all following what Lord Grim did, but his choice of skill was, in the end, up to him. Maybe Ye Qiu could give him tips, but the team chat was clear of Lord Grim’s words.

He could be verbally giving instructions...

Their thoughts involuntarily drifted to this. There was no one keeping an eye on everyone in an online match. Sitting together, they could treat it just as they treated the online game, yelling out hints and discussing plans.

The reason why they thought of this was because this Cleric’s healing method was flawless. The choice of skill, timing, it all maximized the healing output. All the input had been converted to effective healing, not missing or wasting anything.

This Cleric was very good at calculating, or rather… extremely careful and precise.

This was the feeling that the three heads of the club had.

This support could definitely draw out the match, but what was the point of prolonging it? Just to keep struggling futilely?

None of the three believed that, because that person was in the arena.

Maybe other grassroots would be unfamiliar with this map, but how was that possible for him? Though there were many, many maps in Glory and even the most experienced players couldn’t know all of them like the back of their hands, it wasn’t every map that had very unique characteristics. Through the propagation of terrain effects, with other adjustments made, Glory created so many maps. For veterans, what they were familiar with wasn’t every map, but each setting and the features of the different terrains. With that, even to a map they had never seen before, it wouldn’t feel completely foreign to them. They could always easily figure out the map’s features and how to use them, or at least how to make sure they weren’t disadvantaged.

Had Ye Qiu already found a way to deal with Flame Flagged Springs?

Tao Xuan, Cui Li, and Chen Yehui hoped this wasn’t true, but somehow, in the depths of their hearts, they seemed to already believe that this was inevitable. Was it even possible for that person to lose so badly?

Even if he died, that guy would definitely give his opponent a good scare before succumbing!

Boom!

Wu Chen’s Dawn Gunner guided a howling rocket to its target, making another two areas collapse and creating a mushroom cloud. The mud that fell was quickly submerged by the bubbling spring water. In the other area, it was incinerated by tongues of flames, turning into lava.

Causing another two marked areas to activate wasn’t surprising for the fierce offense Team Everlasting was mounting.

Wu Chen prepared to attack again, but upon taking a good look at his surroundings, he froze.

The ground was full of holes and ditches, with so many water and fire pits uncovered. The terrain was much less even than it had been before, but how come it seemed a lot more open?

Wu Chen was a real pro player with three years of experience in the Pro League. In regards to experience in high-end battles, he had much more than He An.

Something was wrong! The unease buried within Wu Chen suddenly erupted.

Chapter 822: Help Needed

Fire pits and geysers scattered the map. All of them lay bare in front of them. It didn’t affect Team Everlasting in any way. They were adept at identifying the positions and ranges of the geysers by using the flag markers, but this was very helpful for Team Happy. They didn’t need to waste time looking at flags. With the fire pits and geysers exposed, their locations were very obvious. They just had to avoid them.

The terrain effects didn’t completely disappear, but the players didn’t need to spend as much effort paying attention to where they stepped.

An experienced player like Wu Chen could see the importance of this tiny difference. As a result, he was able to instantly decipher his opponent’s intentions. Team Happy was indeed surrounded, but their position was starting to transition from defense to offense. As Team Happy defended against their attacks, they were also using this opportunity to change the terrain, transforming it to something different from the original Flame Flagged Springs.

"Everyone, be careful!" Wu Chen immediately warned in the team chat.

Their team chat could not be seen by the other team, but it could be seen by the spectators. Many of the spectators were puzzled by his warning. Team Everlasting had a huge lead. They had even withdrawn their healer in exchange for another DPSer, boldly bombarding Team Happy with attacks. Why was he suddenly worried?

Let alone the spectators, even Team Everlasting’s own players were confused at Wu Chen’s sudden warning.

"What is it?" Someone asked.

It was quite embarrassing for the team if even the team’s own players didn’t understand, but during the match, they couldn’t care about all that. They needed to understand what Wu Chen meant.

"The map has changed." Wu Chen said.

The spectators were still puzzled, but for Team Everlasting, even if they had no experience in the pro scene, they were still skilled players. After listening to Wu Chen’s reminder, they focused on the issue and also discovered where the problem lied.

Among the spectators, people like Tao Xuan, Cui Li, and Chen Yehui also came to a realization after hearing these words. They had never thought that Ye Qiu would fall so easily. Now from the looks of it, he really did have a countermeasure in mind. It was exactly what they had expected. However... that didn’t make any of them happy. It only annoyed them.

"Keep your distance. Who’s closest to the support zone? Switch out for the Cleric." Wu Chen ordered.

"The closest one... is me….." He An replied gloomily.

"You too." Wu Chen ordered without any ambiguity. The sense of crisis in his heart was growing more and more intense. At this moment, it wasn’t too important if the core player was on the field or not, hurry up and switch in for the Cleric.

He An understood how crucial this was. He wasn’t someone, who only cared about himself and not the team as a whole. Even though he wasn’t happy, he still immediately rushed towards the support zone.

A flag unfurled on his screen, and a player appeared in front of him. He An saw that it was Steamed Bun Invasion. The only point that Team Everlasting had won came from this guy, some noob who got lost on the map.

"F*ck off!"

He An was not in a good mood. Seeing Steamed Bun Invasion blocking his path, he threw an Earthwave Sword directly at him.

Among all the wave swords, Earthwave Sword was the quickest. His sword slashed down and chunks of earth flew wildly towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

But the two sides were rather far from each other. Earthwave Sword had some range, but hoping to hit the opponent in this way was looking down on him too much.

Steamed Bun Invasion stepped to the side and dodged it. He raised his hands and threw sand at Go Forth.

He An had Go Forth turn his head slightly, ready to take this Sand Toss directly. If this skill didn’t have a Blind effect, just the damage alone was nothing to be afraid of.

He turned his head and the sand hit him. He turned his head back... a brick.

He An was confused.

He didn’t even notice that Steamed Bun Invasion had hidden a brick in the sand. He An was a bit glad. If he hadn’t turned his head back quickly, just a little bit slower and that brick would have hit the back of his head, not the front. According to the skill effects, a back attack would have a 100% chance of inducing a Dizzy effect.

But the next second, He An discovered that he had rejoiced too fast.

Because Go Forth still became dizzy.

When a Brick hits a target’s head, there was a 50% chance to induce a dizzy effect. Now that it had triggered, whether or not it hit the back didn’t matter.

Steamed Bun Invasion seized this opportunity and rushed forward. He An could see the duration of the dizzy effect. His hands hovered over his keyboard impatiently.

Good!

The dizzy effect usually lasted three seconds, but the Spirit stat affected status effect durations. Spellblades had a 3.5 Spirit growth, higher than the 2.5 Spirit growth for Brawlers. In addition to the difference in their equipment, the gap between their character’s Spirit levels was even wider. The dizzy effect from Steamed Bun’s brick lasted less than 2 seconds on Go Forth.

Steamed Bun Invasion had just arrived in front of Go Forth, when the dizzy wore off. Go Forth immediately used Wave Wheel Slasher.

"You thought you could make me dizzy for 3 seconds?" The timing of this Wave Wheel Slasher was perfect. Steamed Bun didn’t have time to dodge it. Grab skills could not be blocked. After this successful attack, He An taunted his opponent.

"Then how many seconds should it be?" Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

He An was startled.

What type of response is that?

I’m clearly taunting you! Did this guy think I was chatting with him?　

He An didn’t know how to answer Steamed Bun’s question. Unable to respond with words, he could only respond with actions. After Wave Wheel Slasher ended, Steamed Bun Invasion fell. Go Forth followed up with a Fire Wave Sword. Flames engulfed Steamed Bun Invasion. Fire Wave Sword also had a powerful knockback effect.

He An didn’t forget his goal. He needed to hurry over to the support zone and switch with the Cleric.

"Not bad. You’re pretty good." Steamed Bun Invasion, who had been sent flying by Fire Wave Sword, praised He An mysteriously. His praise was stinging to the ear though. It sounded as if he were playing around with He An.

He An valued the big picture. He ignored him. Go Forth hastily rushed towards his destination, but before he could make a few steps, he saw Steamed Bun Invasion shout in chat: "LOOK AT MY BRICK!"

He An immediately had Go Forth roll. When he looked at the chat again, Steamed Bun Invasion laughed: "Ha ha ha, you’ve been tricked."

He An was furious! He couldn’t bear it anymore and turned around to send over an Ice Wave Sword, but when his character turned around, he suddenly saw a hand reaching out in front of his eyes. The hand clutched Go Forth’s throat, and Ice Wave Sword was interrupted.

So quick?

He An was surprised. He thought Steamed Bun Invasion should still be several units away from him. Who would have thought that the other side had already reached his back. Brawlers didn’t have any sudden dashes or movement skills. When he thought about it again, the problem might have been with his Fire Wave Sword.

Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t been completely hit by Fire Wave Sword. When he was grabbed by Wave Wheel Slasher, he evaded or rolled away from Fire Wave Sword, which would reduce the knockback effect of the skill.

He An had been careless. In the end, he had looked down on Steamed Bun Invasion. After Steamed Bun lost the match because he got lost in the map, He An equated him with an idiot, but now he was being lifted in the air like a little chicken by this idiot.

Strangle. A persistent restriction skill. Because of the Spirit disparity, Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t restrict Go Forth for too long, but this strategy already let He An become aware of his opponent’s intentions. His opponent was stopping him from switching in with the Cleric.

Steamed Bun Invasion might not be the only one who would come to delay him. The other side might have backup come to assist him.

"They’re stopping me from advancing. Find someone else to switch with the Cleric!" He An immediately sent this message in the team chat. He was secretly delighted, when he typed out the message. He obviously didn’t want to be switched out. Now, a perfectly good reason had showed up in front of him. He wasn’t too worried about the other side blocking him. By attracting the attention of the other side, it would make it easier for his teammates to get the Cleric in!

"Support him!" Wu Chen immediately ordered.

"What support? I’ll control them. You guys hurry up and switch with the Cleric!" He An shouted.

"You can’t control them."

He An suddenly became furious. Wu Chen’s reply wasn’t giving him face. What do you mean I can’t? Are you saying I’m not skilled enough?

Strangle didn’t seal the target’s attacks. After being strangled by Steamed Bun Invasion, He An had dealt Steamed Bun Invasion quite some damage. When the strangle ended, he was just about to show his might and let Wu Chen witness how he could control his opponent. Suddenly, numerous skills slammed into his back. While the effects of Strangle lasted, a chain of fierce strikes struck. Steamed Bun Invasion also timed his attack perfectly. Go Forth was sent flying away too. Even rolling twice wasn’t enough to completely neutralize all of the momentum. During these two rolls, the attacks never ceased. He An watched as Go Forth’s health slid down rapidly. At this moment, he was frightened stiff. When the two rolls ended, he looked up.

F*ck, I really can’t control them! Team Happy cared too much about him. All five characters had come running over to attack him. 5v1. He would be killed in the blink of an eye. Even if their team switched the Cleric back in, they would have still be down a player. It would be very disadvantageous for them. The price for having him control the other team would be too great.

"Help!" He An was decisive and immediately called for assistance.

Chapter 823: Backup Ploy

The players in the arena often were unable to understand the overall situation of the match. They had to rely on their own experience and judgement to grasp the bigger picture.

That was what Wu Chen was trying to accomplish. Upon realizing that Team Happy had guided the control of the situation from their hands, he immediately thought to get back their healer; they wouldn’t be as reckless anymore.

Team Everlasting’s biggest flaw at the moment was not having a healer. They understood that, and of course Happy would too. They could tell what classes were on the field by the attacks that flew towards them. So they might have predicted that Everlasting would try to switch a character out for their healer and use that to their advantage.

So, after telling He An to switch out with their healer, his Dawn Gunner sped towards where He An’s Go Forth had been headed.

When He An reported that he had been attacked, Wu Chen’s guess was confirmed, so he told the others to go and support. If their opponent had planned to use the fact that they would switch their healer in, they would mount a full offense, one that He An couldn’t be able to cope with alone. If only he went to help, then it wasn’t certain to work, so he decided to have their team regroup and switch in a healer after beating the enemy back.

Wu Chen’s plans were clear.

But when he saw He An take the initiative to call for backup, he knew instantly that the problem might be worse than he had expected.

He understood He An pretty well. That guy thought highly of himself, feeling that he had the talent, but not been given the opportunity. Then he was uncovered by Everlasting and proved his ability, becoming more and more smug. With his personality, he wouldn’t lower himself to ask for help unless he was really helpless.

"How many?" Wu Chen hastily asked.

"5"

He An didn’t even have the time for punctuation.

When Wu Chen received his message, he was stunned. The entire opposing team had gone after He An; that was way beyond Wu Chen’s expectations.

They were attacking the enemy from all sides so they weren’t clueless about their positions. In the span of a few moments, all five of them managed to charge over, but he was making judgements based on his own awareness and experience. How could the situation be so unbelievable?

Their opponents had been prepared!

Wu Chen obtained this conclusion with his experience.

The advantageous situation they had managed to create from being besieged was far more complex than Wu Chen had thought.

It was no coincidence that He An’s Go Forth was the closest to the support zone. This was something the opponent had planned as they turned their passive situation into an initiative. Their offense was aimed at that exact direction. This had been planned from the very start. Team Everlasting had fallen for their ploy by telling He An’s Go Forth, who was closest to the support zone, to switch out for the Cleric.

As soon as Go Forth rushed towards the support zone, Team Happy could swiftly position themselves to stop him. That was how things came to this point.

"Hold on!"

Wu Chen could only give He An this sentence of encouragement. Other than that, he could only get everyone to go towards the support zone as quickly as possible.

Luckily, Team Everlasting didn’t positions themselves too far from each other during the siege. Backup wouldn’t arrive too late for anyone.

He An managed to endure until his teammates appeared.

"Steady now, don’t be too hasty in attacking. We need to find a chance to switch our Cleric in." Wu Chen was the third to arrive. The two who had arrived first were already fighting alongside Go Forth, tangling with Happy. Three versus five, the situation could only be called dismal. As soon as Wu Chen’s Dawn Gunner arrived, he sent out a few shots with a boom and instantly brought the three out of a terrible situation. The four characters reunited and immediately counterattacked. All their classes had AoE skills, so they held the advantage when fighting in teams. The four attacked together, and their attacks swept over the map, knocking back the five from Team Happy for the moment.

"Nice one!"

When he had been fighting alone, He An had been a mess. Nevermind counterattacking, he had been beaten without being able to even plant his own two feet! Now that his teammates were here, his opponents weren’t able to beat them down with such ease anymore. He An’s morale surged, quickly erupting with a chain of attacks.

Ice, Fire, Light!

Three waves of attacks swept out one after the other. This was the Spellblade’s famous technique, "Three Pulsing Waves".

The public chat channel was instantly filled with cheers for their ace by Team Everlasting’s true fans. Even the spectating faceslappers felt excitement surging with this impressive Three Pulsing Waves. Some couldn’t hold it in any longer, mockingly calling for Happy to surrender as the technique swept out.

It was true that He An had been a mess before, but that was in a five versus one situation. No matter who it was in such a situation, the outcome would be the same! Now, four of Team Everlasting’s members made a tide turning counterattack. What was this? This was the difference in ability! With just four people, they could beat back all five of you! Just wait until their last member arrives; how will you deal with it then?

Since the team command chat channels were made public to the audience, the audience could get the gist of the situation even if they didn’t understand what was happening. Though Happy seemed to have a plan, it now seemed like they were completely unsuccessful! Why? Because Team Everlasting was stronger. Being an ex-pro team, they had more cohesive teamwork and tactics.

The four fought side by side, attack after attack, and not long after, the fifth member of Team Everlasting arrived as well. Everlasting’s true fans and the spectating faceslappers were all at a high, believing that this face-off was going to make their decisive victory. So the encouragements and mockery flew from them. It seemed like they could already start celebrating their victory.

But as for the players on the field?

Wu Chen’s unease had yet to disperse. Maybe it was because he had always been a part of a weaker team and was used to defeat that developed an acute sense of danger in Wu Chen. The situation at hand started to seem fishy to him once more.

"Don’t just focus on attacking, break through and get the Cleric out!" He An exclaimed in the channel. Wu Chen nodded upon seeing it.

Was that it? Wu Chen thought to himself, in this face off, they may have gotten the upper hand, but if they didn’t have a healer, then there was less room to make mistakes. A single opening could cause damage that they couldn’t afford to take. Go Forth didn’t have much health left. In a chaotic battle like this, he might get taken out by a wave of attacks. It was better to get their Cleric here pronto.

"Ch-charge through them!" He An wanted revenge for the mess that he had been put through before. Without a healer, the offense of five AoE DPSers were imposing and ferocious. Any opponent would have a hard time dealing with this with their healer unless they had the ability to instantly upset this offense. Otherwise, everyone’s health would be falling simultaneously with the attacks from five AoE characters. A single healer would have a hard time keeping up. Even if they were skilled enough, the cost was high, so it would be very inefficient.

Under Team Everlasting’s bombardment, Team Happy retreated step by step and reached the support zone first after a little while.

It was at this moment that Wu Chen’s fluctuating sense of danger erupted with a warning. He suddenly realized what the problem was.

"Disperse!" Wu Chen’s abrupt command had both the audience and his own teammates puzzled. Two of them even asked at the same time, "Why?"

"It’s a backup ploy! Quick, go!" Wu Chen yelled.

Backup ploy?

Everyone who had a good grasp of knowledge of Glory only had to hear this noun and look at the situation to realize what was happening. A real backup ploy couldn’t be launched under the current circumstances, but if Team Everlasting didn’t retreat and continued to exchange blows with Team Happy, then that would equal to helping Happy achieve a backup ploy.

With even some of the audience understanding, Team Everlasting wouldn’t be so oblivious, even if they didn’t have much experience.

"Retreat, retreat, retreat, quick!" He An started to yell in their chat as well.

But it seemed like Team Happy had heard it, since Lord Grim suddenly typed a sentence into the public chat: "It’s a little too late to retreat now, isn’t it?"

"Come on, let this senior open a door for you!"

Another sentence followed Lord Grim’s. It was Windward Formation, Team Happy’s sixth player who had been called over through the support zone. Team Happy’s Cleric, Cold Hands, was switched out.

This was a backup ploy.

Using the support zone, the healer and sixth player would switch frequently. Once a rhythm was established, they could increase their firepower without sacrificing healing, like there were six people fighting at once.

But since this scheme needed them to be within a support zone, there was a limit to how it could be used. If one side stood in the support zone and their opponents never approached, then there was no point. So in most maps, a backup ploy’s effects were greatly limited. Only in a few maps where the support zone was placed in a special position, could you corner your opponent and use the backup ploy to crush them.

The current map, Flame Flagged Springs, didn’t have this feature. If Team Everlasting had thought of this before, there wouldn’t have been any harm in just letting Happy retreat, but since they wanted to get their Cleric on the field so badly, they were even more impatient to get to the support zone than Team Happy and forgot the existence of such a ploy. By the time they remembered, Team Happy had already gotten the terrain advantage. They, on the other hand, had been too excited, had charged too fiercely, and were going to pay for it when they retreated.

As Windward Formation spoke, he had already raised his staff. Wisps of dark energy swirled around him. Seeing this, Wu Chen was shocked, hastily making his Dawn Gunner run and shouting, "It’s Death’s Door, interrupt it!"

A Laser Rifle blasted out from the muzzle of Dawn Gunner’s gun, but Lord Grim, who was at Windward Formation’s side, stepped over and opened up the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Laser Rifle had a knock back effect, but these effects would be reduced in the face of a shield. Seeing that the opponent had a shield covering them, Wu Chen quickly turned Dawn Gunner’s gun towards the sky, preparing to release a Stinger, but at that moment, there was a flash and the Laser Rifle he shot came streaking back...

Chapter 824: Are They That Strong?

Reflect Attack!

Wu Chen choked on his surprise. He hadn’t expected that at all. Laser Rifle was a very fast attack and he wasn’t prepared for it, instantly taking a hit from the reflected Laser Rifle. He definitely wouldn’t be able to fire that Stinger.

The others had only tried to interrupt upon hearing Wu Chen’s call, sending their attacks half a beat too slow onto Lord Grim’s open Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. They were all preparing a second attack when their eyes caught a flash of blue light and an icy aura appeared...

Ghostblade skill: Ice Soul Protection Boundary, otherwise known as Ice Boundary.

Team Everlasting’s members were all focused on the Death’s Door Windward Formation had been chanting. With this powerful skill, they couldn’t escape their fate of being controlled. They hadn’t expected Qiao Yi Fan to use One Inch Ash and successful sneak attack them. With the appearance of the ice boundary, the five were all frozen with the sounds of crackling ice. Now the result was set. Don’t even think about escaping, if they didn’t interrupt that technique, they were all ducks sitting at Death’s Door.

Team Everlasting’s players paled as one. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shield was still open and in their way! If they were all frozen, how were they to interrupt it?

The chant for Death’s Door quickly came to an end and it was summoned in front of the five. At such a distance, they would have trouble escaping from Death’s Door, even if they weren’t frozen by the Ice Boundary.

"Fire Wave Formation!" Wu Chen yelled anxiously into the chat.

This was a hint everyone understood. Ice and fire were opposing elements, so if they could activate a fire element Fire Wave Formation, the Ice Boundary would disappear quicker. He An’s Go Forth hadn’t been completely frozen, only slowed, so he could still activate his skills.

But they soon saw a helpless message from He An. "I’m dizzy!"

Go Forth was dizzy again...

Team Happy wasn’t made up of just one or two players!

As Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash sent out an Ice Boundary, Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion had also been silently approaching. He expertly threw a brick and it struck Go Forth perfectly in the back of his head. Everyone else had only been frozen, but poor He An; not only was he slowed, but he was also dizzy thanks to a brick.

The five trapped by the Ice Boundary were helpless in the face of Death’s Door, and the dark energy from within quickly grabbed all them. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had long since charged over as well. All that aggression she had been holding in erupted, swinging her spear and giving the five tangled in dark energy a beating. Her combos were stacking rapidly, causing the golden light from her Battle Spirit to intensify. Her attacks became faster, her damage rose, and the chasers from her skills became larger, flying out and exploding. The mere sight of all the health being blasted away was enough to make anyone’s heart ache.

Lord Grim, Windward Formation….

These two characters charged over as well. With Death’s Door holding them all in, these five had been tormented for quite a while. Wu Chen carefully considered the situation at hand, suddenly noticing that their opponent’s were rushing to deal damage, but this offense wasn’t without clarity. For example, no one was attacking Go Forth anymore. That was because his health was low enough and they had no healing skills. They didn’t need to continue their offense on him, since Death’s Door still had a spectacular ending!

Gradually, Team Everlasting’s five characters were pulled into Death’s Door by its death force, and then Death’s Door suddenly imploded, as if trying to banish the five characters into a parallel world.

Amongst the wildly pulsating death force, the five characters were thrown out by the blast, and He An’s Go Forth lost the remainder of his health in this blast, being the first character to fall in this battle, but the other four had their health chipped away at a steady rhythm by Team Happy’s orderly attacks.

Wu Chen’s Dawn Gunner had the second lowest health. With Death’s Door’s explosion, he hadn’t been taken out, but Lord Grim’s Sky Strike caught the falling Dawn Gunner and sent him towards Steamed Bun Invasion, who jumped up and greeted him with a Strangle.

With a 50% reduced in physical defense, Dawn Gunner didn’t last long under the following assault, becoming the second to get taken out.

The remaining three had their health intentionally reduced. After Dawn Gunner had been dealt with, the Team Happy five turned heel together and instantly surrounded them, taking them out.

Although Team Everlasting seemed to still have three people, their core class and reliable captain had also been wiped out. The battle was over.

The encirclement of the remaining three was done in silence. No one talked in the match chat channels or in the audience public chat. Everyone watched on in silence, sitting in front of their computers.

On this side was a team eliminated from the Pro League, on that side was a grassroots team originating from an Internet cafe. Two teams like this wouldn’t be able to play any kind of high end competition, and wouldn’t gain any fame, but, this team competition was definitely a textbook example.

How to use the map to turn the tides when disadvantaged. That was what this match had shown.

The players weren’t the most skilled.

Their equipment wasn’t the best.

Even the tactics that were used weren’t flawless. If Team Everlasting had been a little more on guard and noticed the backup ploy faster, then they wouldn’t have lost the upper hand and been wiped out in one counterattack.

Unfortunately, there were no "if only"s in tactics. Plus, even if Team Everlasting had managed to guard against the backup ploy, that didn’t mean Team Happy didn’t have any other tricks up their sleeve.

Reality was the only way to judge tactics. And from the results of this match, Team Happy’s tactics were extremely successful.

"Team Happy is so strong!!!"

As Team Happy sent the last last member of Team Everlasting out of the competition, the person who had been publically supporting Team Happy before jumped out again.

After flooding several pages of the chat with a fwoosh, the person left again without waiting for a response.

The spectating faceslappers were depressed! How is that all their efforts came back to slap them in face? What kind of team would it take to eliminate this Team Happy? Even a team that originated from the Pro League like Everlasting wasn’t enough; could they really be a team strong enough to go against Excellent Era?

Thinking of this, more or less everyone shook their heads involuntarily.

A team strong enough to go against Excellent Era? With that sort of equipment! Though they didn’t know where these guys had gotten all of those pieces of silver equipment, just that wasn’t enough to match up with the subs for Team Excellent Era.

Suddenly, it became a trial to try and estimate Team Happy’s strength! The cons of not having a full understanding of the team’s ability was something the faceslappers had experienced over and over again.

From when they thought this team was arrogant and personally tried to shoot them off their high horse, their actions came back to bite them again and again, because they always thought: this should be enough to defeat Team Happy, right?

So when they cheered and jeered about Happy losing, when they were ready to finish an essay on Happy’s defeat, Happy always sent back a solid slap to face, punching the words from their mouths.

It was painful! The faceslappers had been holding this grudge for so long and never got a chance to unleash their anger; the effort of holding it in was killing them.

In comparison, Team Everlasting’s fans were truly depressed.

There was no record of turning things around after losing with a 1 to 8.5 lead while having the home advantage. Was Team Everlasting’s journey this year coming to an end so soon?

Next year? Would there even be a next year for them? They had nothing to do now, not even the Challenger League, so what could they use to keep themselves and the confidence their players and fans had afloat.

There wasn’t a lack of disappointed people tonight.

Team Everlasting’s fans were crushed and disappointed and their players were obviously no better.

Such a large difference in points was enough to make them as lifeless as the dead.

The match was over, and everyone sat in their chairs as if they had been paralyzed. No one spoke, and no one could squeeze out even the smallest of smiles. Though they knew it wasn’t over, there was another round, this result made their morale plummet.

Everyone stayed silent, no one moved and no one spoke until the door was pushed open. They all subconsciously turned to look, only to see the boss of Club Everlasting standing in the doorway sadly.

Club Excellent Era.

"Fuck!"

When Team Everlasting’s five characters had been caught by Death’s Door, Tao Xuan had already hurled the documents to the ground. Then as Team Happy wiped out Team Everlasting one by one, Tao Xuan’s mood had gone from sunny to cloudy, then those clouds darkened with rain, ready to storm at any time.

Especially the end, seeing the public chat flooded with "Team Happy is so strong!!!", it got to his nerves.

"Is Team Happy really that strong?" Tao Xuan spoke darkly.

"With Ye Qiu, their strength is definitely above normal teams," Cui Li forced himself to speak.

"Then is Team Everlasting a normal team?" Tao Xuan asked, pointing at the screen.

Chen Yehui looked at Cui Li with sympathy. This question wouldn’t be easy to answer, but who would’ve thought Cui Li would easily say, "Though Team Everlasting was eliminated the year before last, their ability has declined greatly since they were a part of the Alliance. They sold their core character that year, and their Captain and core players also left. A year later, they lost the Challenger’s League which put them into a terrible situation. Now their team only consists of one player from the original team. All the others were found in a rush, and even their manager is a player. Their strength is far inferior to a real pro team!"

Chen Yehui was surprised by this logical analysis. This was truly a man who deserved to be manager; he had really done his homework!

As Cui Li finished his matter-of-fact speech, he was sweating internally! He hadn’t really done much research on Team Everlasting. It was just that when he saw the tides turn, he did a quick search on his phone and formulated such a speech.

"Actually, this victory might be a good thing. When they really start believing in their own power is when they’ll meet a dead end." Cui Li added on.

Chapter 825: City H Interview Station

Happy won!

This match didn’t receive an incredible amount of attention, but it didn’t receive too little either. But in any case, it was the one match that the media did notice.

After all, one side was currently the talk of the town, while the other side was a former pro team. The strength of both sides was noteworthy. No matter how famous Team Excellent Era was, just fighting against normal players wouldn’t receive much attention.

In the match between Team Happy and Team Everlasting, if Team Everlasting had won, the news reports might have simply written over it with a single stroke, but with Team Happy winning 8.5 to 1, that was certainly something worth writing about.

Esports Home, the most reputable eSports media platform. Glory was currently the most popular eSport right now, so news on Glory would undoubtedly be their most important focus. Eighty percent of their paper, which released twice a week, consisted of Glory related news. Every city with a major Glory team had an eSports news station. A few top teams even had their own special reporters that followed the teams around, establishing a good relationship between them to be that team’s sole interviewer.

City H was Team Excellent Era’s home city. It could even be said that the news station located there was their oldest one. It was also where the first sole interviewer for a team came, but as Team Excellent Era gradually declined, the City H news station declined as well. It had only been busy last season because of Team Excellent Era’s miraculously disgusting record, which had become such a good topic to report on. After being busy all of last season, City H’s Esports Home news station discovered that it was as if they had overdosed.

Because Team Excellent Era had actually been relegated!

That was admittedly a huge topic, but after reporting it, even for a powerhouse like Team Excellent Era, a relegated team wouldn’t receive much attention in a paper dedicated to the Pro League.　　

City H’s news station would become marginalized into an awkward spot.

During the summer, when the various teams were trading players and equipment, the Esports Home also prepared for the new season.

The first step was to adjust the number of employees at City H’s news station.

City H only had Team Excellent Era. After being relegated, it wasn’t necessary for so many dedicated employees to be there. As a result, the employees of City H’s news station were sent out to different areas. Didn’t the Alliance have newly added teams too?

In the end, only two people remained in City H’s news station. If it wasn’t because they were certain that Team Excellent Era would return to the Alliance and their purchase of Xiao Shiqin and Life Extinguisher, City H’s news station might have even closed down.

Leaving just two employees couldn’t be considered much. They were just there to be prepared when the time came. The end of the Challenger League would have some topics to report about. With Team Excellent Era this year, there would be more to talk about than usual, but for the reporters, they had been with Team Excellent Era when they reigned over the Glory scene and were even familiar with the big names of the various teams. Now, they had suddenly dropped to such a position, where they needed to follow the Challenger League. They didn’t feel any better than those relegated players.

Cao Guangcheng was currently responsible for City H’s Esports Home news station. He was also formerly the interviewer who followed Team Excellent Era. During Team Excellent Era’s reign, he had undoubtedly been Esports Home’s most famous reporter. Every year, he would have who knew how many lead stories on the front page.

But in the blink of an eye, he had become a phoenix without feathers. With Team Excellent Era relegated, a famous reporter like him also fell to an awkward spot. He could also do work with other teams, but as the team’s reporter, his network couldn’t be ignored. All of Cao Guangcheng’s relationships lay in Team Excellent Era. If he ran to another team, he might not be able to outcompete his fellow reporters. Cao Guangcheng knew that many were already laughing at him behind his back! After all, there would be no lack of people who had been jealous of his fame for so many years.

In the annual summer Esports Home conference, Cao Guangcheng had heard quite a few insidious greetings, but he could only hold back his anger! The current powerhouses already had their own established team reporters. If he switched teams, he would be sent to a new team. A team with the goal of not getting relegated could only have so much to talk about. When the time came, that team might even get relegated and he would once again fall with them. The cycle would continue and he might never be able to return to his former glory. 　　

Cao Guangcheng had a good understanding of his situation, so when Team Excellent Era was relegated, he didn’t hurry to find another path. After all, this was still Team Excellent Era! Their relegation was considered a miracle. No one doubted that Team Excellent Era would return to the pro scene next year. Moreover, even after being relegated, the team was able to trade for Xiao Shiqin and Life Extinguisher. Such a trade was rarely seen during the summer transfer window.

Cao Guangheng stayed, waiting to return to the Alliance together with Team Excellent Era. However, for this season, his days would be unfortunately leisurely.

Speaking of which, when he was usually busy and had to stay up to finish his report, he would always curse his profession for being so exhausting. Now that he was suddenly idle, he was reminiscing about those busy days. He missed those days so much that he was even losing sleep…...

He had time to sleep, but he couldn’t sleep. Cao Guangcheng felt a little depressed towards this lifestyle that he led.

Saturday morning.

Cao Guangcheng opened his eyes. He looked at the time and subconsciously began wondering if today was Team Excellent Era’s home or away match. After realizing what he was doing, he laughed bitterly. The third round of the Pro League was about to start. He still wasn’t used to Team Excellent Era not being in the Alliance. He didn’t need to follow their team!

Helpless, Cao Guangcheng got up and left his bedroom to go to the bathroom.　　

Their news station was really just them living in City H and being closeby to interview the team on a moment’s notice. The company would provide the reporters with an apartment. Their everyday life consisted of going over to interview the team and then writing a draft. They didn’t need to a specific office location. If you insisted on it, then his his bedroom and living room could be considered his workplace.

When Cao Guangcheng went out of his bedroom, he passed by the living room and saw the other person, Chang Xian, staying in City H with him. He was currently on his laptop, busy typing.

Compared to Cao Guangcheng requesting to stay, Chang Xian had been told to stay. This young man was a new graduate last year. After being hired by Esports Home, he was directly sent to City H’s news station, a location with many Glory fans. Unfortunately, City H’s Team Excellent Era had been relegated and he was set aside as a new hire. This summer, headquarters didn’t change their mind, and he stayed there with Cao Guangcheng. However, Chang Xian didn’t have as many thoughts as Cao Guangcheng. He readily prepared for work with youthful energy. He looked as if he were going to write a long report on the Challenger League. To Cao Guangcheng, it was quite funny.

Challenger League? What’s there to write about?

Cao Guangcheng, who had written news stories on four finals, had trouble lowering himself to following the Challenger League. Because of this he was quite thankful for having a young guy like Chang Xian. He at least had a partner!

Seeing Chang Xian busily working early in the morning, Cao Guangcheng couldn’t help but be curious about what this fellow was writing so busily about. Didn’t a round of the Challenger League just finish yesterday?

Before he could get closer, Chang Xian saw him from the reflection of his monitor and hastily got up to give him a greeting: "Morning, brother Cao! You’re up!"

"Mm, what are you up to?" Cao Guangcheng had noticed that Chang Xian had quite a few web pages opened up as if he were organizing something.

"Oh! Last night in the Challenger League, Team Happy beat Team Everlasting!" Chang Xian excitedly said.

He hasn’t seen the world yet!

Cao Guangcheng muttered to himself, but calmly said: "Really?"

"Brother Cao, don’t you think we should interview Happy? From what I’ve heard, Ye Qiu should be a part of Team Happy, right?" Chang Xian said.

Cao Guangcheng smiled. This brother knows a hundred times more than you about that. I obviously know that Ye Qiu is in Team Happy, but you asking for an interview was a joke. Who was that? Ye Qiu! In the entire Glory scene, he was the media’s number one enemy! He was the only public figure in the Alliance with special privileges. No one in the media could reach him even if they wanted to.

Cao Guangcheng was Team Excellent Era’s reporter, but he had only been able to get an interview with the captain three times!

Three times!

Cao Guangcheng had been with Team Excellent for eight years, yet he had only been able to get a total of three interviews across those eight years. Another team reporter might meet their team’s captain more than that every week. Even more depressing was that those three interviews had been through f*cking QQ…...

Yes, up until now, Cao Guangcheng had never even seen Ye Qiu in person. It was something he had always felt depressed about.

Thinking of this, Cao Guangcheng felt grief and indignation again. Seeing Chang Xian in high spirits, Cao Guangcheng felt like he needed to show this young guy how deep the waters were in this industry. Young people nowadays thought that interviewing Zhou Zekai was difficult! F*ck. Have you guys ever followed the team eight years, never seen the team’s ace player in person, and only got three interviews with him on QQ?

"Little Chang, that’s a good news point. Team Happy is a popular team right now. We can trail them. Let’s go. I’m optimistic about your future!" Cao Guangcheng said.

"Yay!" Chang Xian immediately began packing up his equipment. After packing up, he turned his head to say: "Brother Cao, you’re not going?"

"Oh, I won’t go. You should try going by yourself. Train your ability to work independently! If Team Happy is actually able to go through the entire way, won’t they be your resource? You have to grab onto them well!" Cao Guangcheng said.

"Okay. Then I’ll be heading out, brother Cao." Chang Xian called out.

"Be careful! I’ll be waiting for your draft!" Cao Guangcheng said.

"Okay!" Chang Xian nodded his head enthusiastically.

Chapter 826: Interviewing Happy

The weather wasn’t bad on Friday, and Excellent Era gave their players the day off, allowing them to rest.

This was a tradition that had been around since the beginning of the Pro League. The day after a match was a day for rest, but now that they were participants in the Challenger League, Friday, their original match day, had become a holiday. Those who were used to the Pro League felt a little unused to this change.

It wasn’t just the players, but even the manager, Cui Li, felt a little lost when waking up to a day where he had no match to prepare for.

Uncertain of he should do, Cui Li eventually decided to go for a walk.

Cui Li was something of a workaholic. He was married to noone but his work, so he more or less lived in the club. Stepping out of the club this morning, the first thing that he saw was Happy on the opposite side of the road. Instantly, his mood went from bad to worse.

This really wasn’t a good season! Cui Li couldn’t help but lament. A powerhouse like Excellent Era had to fight in the Challenger League this year. Even if they won, there wasn’t anything to celebrate since it was expected, right?

Therefore, there would be nothing happening this season that Excellent Era could be proud of.

Cui Li stood outside Excellent Era with his hands on his hips, thinking about where he should go. Suddenly, an moped passed by precariously, and came to a stop after some struggle. The rider scratched his head awkwardly and greeted Cui Li, "Morning, manager Cui!"

Cui Li cheered up a bit upon realizing that he recognized the boy on the bike. Chang Xian, an intern from Esports Home that had been sent here to H City just last year. He had come along to many interviews with Excellent Era. Now that a year had gone by, he should be a full member, but his electric bike riding skills still had much to improve! Cui Li silently thanked the fact that he had yet to cross the road, otherwise it was completely possible that he would be under those wheels at this moment.

"Hey hey, Little Chang!" Cui Li laughed as he teased the other, "It seems like, compared to your writing skills, your biking skills are still in need of a lot of improvement!"

Chang Xian scratched his head, smiling in embarassment.

"Where are you heading off to, so early in the morning?" Cui Li asked.

"To do an interview," Chang Xian replied honestly.

Hearing this, Cui Li lit up. As the club manager, what he needed to consider wasn’t just the results of their matches, he had to take care of the functioning of the club as a whole. With Excellent Era out of the main competition, the attention they received this year was at an all time low. Offers for sponsorships and ads were more or less stagnant. They didn’t care about what a glorious history you had, after all. If you weren’t going to be in the public eye this season, then there was no point in making a big investment. Excellent Era’s situation wasn’t too bad, all things considered, since the public still had expectations for them, some sponsors didn’t pull away immediately, but talked with them about future plans. How they would be executed had to wait until Excellent Era returned to the Pro League.

If Excellent Era could gain attention from the media and appear in public eye more, it would definitely benefit them from the economic perspective Cui Li stood in, as the manager. More attention like this could give sponsors more confidence in Excellent Era!

Cui Li’s smile didn’t shift and he prepared to welcome Chang Xian, but Chang Xian had already gotten back onto his bike, waving at Cui Li and saying, "I won’t take up any more of your time, manager Cui, bye!"

Cui Li’s smile froze on his face, hurriedly stifling the words on the tip of his tongue. His confusion slipping onto his face.

This brat wasn’t going to interview Excellent Era? It was lucky that he hadn’t said anything yet, otherwise that would be really awkward.

Cui Li knew that though Glory was the hottest topic in eSports, there were other games as well. Esports Home was a comprehensive esports media, so they also reported happenings in these other games, but since Glory was the main focus, the interview station in City H was placed close to the only club in City H, Excellent Era.

Was Chang Xian going to interview teams from other games? That what Cui Li thought, until Chang Xian’s bike started to move, wobbling. He had a bad feeling. Around here, there were no other pro teams from other games. The electric bike wasn’t that good of a tool for travelling such distances, right? Then if Chang Xian wasn’t going to interview Excellent Era, he was going to ….

As he thought of this, Chang Xian’s bike finally got properly onto the road, turning and heading directly for Happy Internet Cafe.

To interview Happy.

In this moment, Cui Li’s heart was filled with all sorts of emotions that couldn’t be put into words, standing stunned on the side of the road.

Chang Xian rode his electric bike and crossed the road unevenly and then rode onto the pavement. He seemed to want to stop in front of the door of Happy, but his terrible biking skills couldn’t handle even that. The bike came to a sudden stop half inside the Internet cafe….

Cui Li vaguely heard screams coming from the Internet cafe. They must have been startled by an electric bike charging inside.

Then he saw Chang Xian hurriedly jump off the bike, scratching his head again in embarrassment and quickly backing the bike up to be parked properly. Then he rushed into Happy Internet Cafe.

Happy….

Though Cui Li was displeased, he had to admit that defeating Team Everlasting was quite a feat for Happy, and would make people curious about them. Getting interviewed wasn't entirely unexpected, but watching one of the workers from the the team working specifically for Excellent Era go to interview their enemy made Cui Li’s heart twist.

Out of sight out of mind!

Cui Li thought furiously, whirling in the other direction. Though it was out of sight, his thoughts still lingered on it. What kind of article would be written on Happy?

Happy Internet Cafe.

Chang Xian had rode his bike straight into the Internet cafe, almost startling the employee into calling the police. He quickly explained what happened and why he was here. The employee manning the counter hurriedly called his boss after hearing Chang Xian’s words.

Chen Guo now often lived at the rented house in the compound. Last night, they celebrated their victory over the ex-pro team Everlasting, and now in the morning Chen Guo got a call from the Internet cafe. At first she thought something had happened, but actually someone was here to interview them, and they were someone from Esports Home too. Chen Guo was shocked.

"One second," Chen Guo quickly said before turning to tell Ye Xiu to go.

"Esports Home wants to interview us? Not bad, it’s a good chance to raise our fame," Ye Xiu nodded in approval at her words.

"So, we should accept?" Chen Guo asked.

"No reason not to!" Ye Xiu said.

"But what about you?" Chen Guo knew, of course, that Ye Xiu never accepted interviews, not even the mandatory press conferences after matches. The Alliance wouldn’t ban you from playing if you broke these rules, but you would get fined.

But Ye Xiu never cared. If he was fined, then he’d pay the fine and still not go. They came to an understanding in the end. Ye Xiu was more clear about the fines from the Alliance than even his own balance, making sure to pay them every month. The Alliance was didn’t know whether to laugh or cry at this stubborn guy. In the end, the Alliance even felt a bit sorry for fining him all the time, but the rules were there. If they changed them, how would they face those who adhered to them? So in the beginning there was some debate, but in the end it was just so. One side would pay the fines and the other wouldn’t say anything about his actions.

"Me? They wouldn’t know who I am anyways, right?" Ye Xiu said.

"So you’re just going to say you’re Ye Xiu?" Chen Guo questioned.

"Yup!" Ye Xiu nodded.

"Then, you’re going to accept the interview?" Chen Guo asked.

"It doesn’t matter," Ye Xiu smiled, "They won’t write that much anyways."

"Why won’t they write much?" Chen Guo was a bit disappointed.

"Because I don’t have time left!" Ye Xiu said.

"...." Chen Guo hadn’t thought that would be what he meant and didn’t know how to respond. When Ye Xiu avoided the media, it was first because he was afraid his parents would find him after he ran away from home, and force him to go back. Later on, though he didn’t need to hide from his family, it became a habit. Ye Xiu had thought he would be able to use his brother’s ID to play until he had to retire. He never thought that something like this would happen before then.

He regained his identity as Ye Xiu, and when he returned he wasn’t planning on using Ye Qiu’s name any longer. After experiencing all that once, he was too lazy to go over it again.

Chen Guo respected Ye Xiu’s wishes and simply picked up the phone, telling the guy at the Internet cafe to tell the reporter to come over.

"Uh, shouldn’t you ask the others if they’re okay with being interviewed first?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Oh yeah, you’re right!" Chen Guo immediately realized that was something she should probably do after hearing Ye Xiu ask. And, as they exchanged a glance, they knew they were thinking the same thing.

After living in the Internet cafe for so long, Chen Guo had never poked into Tang Rou’s background, but anyone would realize that she definitely wasn’t someone who had to work in an Internet cafe to keep herself afloat. With her beauty, her composure, a few pictures would earn a lot.

Tang Rou’s background definitely wasn’t simple, so maybe she wouldn’t want to be exposed to the public?

Chapter 827: All Rather Impressive

Ye Xiu and Chen Guo had thought of Tang Rou, but reality was very different from their expectations.

Hearing that there would be a reporter coming to interview them, Tang Rou had no intention of avoiding it. Instead, it was An Wenyi who shook his head furiously at the news. Everyone curiously inquired as to why and was struck speechless by his response. This guy hadn’t gone to his school to check in since school had started. It would be fine if he was inconspicuous about it, but if he went and accepted an interview and appeared on news, it allowed his school to know that he had skipped to play games, they would definitely have a hard time accepting that.

"Okay then, do as you wish, Little An. Everyone else should wait here for a while, the reporter is coming soon," Chen Guo ordered before going outside to welcome the reporter.

Not long after, Chen Guo came back, but she was limping as she pushed open the door and came inside. Everyone stared in shock, Tang Rou running up to help her. "What happened?"

"I’m very sorry about that! My biking skills are… Not the best." Not far behind Chen Guo was a young man, scratching his head in embarrassment as he walked in timidly. After getting the address that Team Happy was at from the Internet cafe, he had rushed over.

Chen Guo had, of course, asked after what Chang Xian was like so she could take him up from downstairs. Seeing the electric bike, she more or less knew that this was who she was waiting for. She had been walking into the road to greet him, but didn’t think there could be someone so terrible at biking. Seeing someone walk out, Chang Xian had anxiously yelled out a warning, but even as one of them tried to dodge and the other tried to swerve, Chen Guo had still gotten hit….

"This is Little Chang from Esports Home…." Chen Guo was still in quite a bit of pain! But she still gritted her teeth and introduced Chang Xian to everyone.

"Boss Chen… I’m really sorry, are you sure you’re okay? Should we go to the hospital first?" Chang Xian chattered nervously at the side. Though Chen Guo had been hit by Chang Xian’s bike, they hadn’t wasted any time in introducing themselves to each each other.

"I’m fine, let me introduce you first," Chen Guo said.

"I think you should sit down first!" Tang Rou helped Chen Guo make her way over to the sofa, so Chen Guo went ahead and introduced her first. "This is Tang Rou, the player behind the Battle Mage Soft Mist."

"Ah!" Chang Xian expressed in surprise. He had, of course, done some research before coming to conduct an interview. The more he understood, the more topics he could bring up. And in the match against Everlasting yesterday, she had defeated two players in the group arena. She was definitely the most famous player in Team Happy. Now, she had turned out to be a beautiful woman in real life as well. Did he really need to write anything? Just a few photos were probably enough to create waves.

And Boss Chen was also a beauty! He was pretty sure the Glory circle had yet to have such a beautiful lady as a boss.

He had, of course, also brought his camera to this interview. It was currently held in his hand, but Tang Rou was busy taking care of Chen Guo, who he had unfortunately injured. He wasn’t shameless enough to ask them for a few photos first. By then, Chen Guo was already introducing the next person.

"This is Qiao Yifan," Chen Guo was just introducing them by who she saw first, "Little Qiao was originally from Team Tiny Herb. After his contract expired, he came over. He plays the Ghostblade, One Inch Ash."

"What?!" Chang Xian, who had been waiting for a chance to take pictures of the two attractive ladies, suddenly heard Chen Guo introducing the next person. He was instantly thunderstruck.

Team Tiny Herb! A member from a team that had been two time champions had joined Team Happy? What was this?

Chang Xian stared in shock. Information on One Inch Ash was lrare. He only knew that it was an account for the tenth server and the second under max level character to reach the Heavenly Domain in the tenth server, after Lord Grim. He hadn’t appeared much during the time where Happy was accepting challengers, but in yesterday’s match against Everlasting, he had won them their first point, giving a calm and mature impression. He hadn’t thought this person would be from the Pro League, and Tiny Herb too!

Chang Xian didn’t hide the shock on his face as he gazed at Qiao Yifan. Qiao Yifan became nervous with all the staring. He had been someone without presence in Team Tiny Herb, and wouldn’t had never had the chance to be interviewed. Now, seeing Chang Xian’s shocked gaze, Qiao Yifan was also a little startled. "I… I…" he stuttered for a while before suddenly blurting out, "I’ll go pour some water," and fleeing.

"That’s Wei Chen, maybe you’ve heard of him?" Chen Guo was still making introductions, "He’s currently our Warlock, Windward Formation."

Wei Chen?

Chang Xian considered this name, feeling a little lost. It was completely unfamiliar to him, but Windward Formation was definitely someone who had ability. However this guy…. Chang Xian looked at Wei Chen, taking in the stubble that hinted at his comparatively old age. Wasn’t he a little… too old?

"Hahaha, young people these days wouldn’t have heard of me." Wei Chen, of course, wouldn’t nervously run away like Qiao Yifan. Seeing that Chang Xian didn’t recognize him, he shamelessly started to introduce himself. "The former captain of Team Blue Rain and the original owner of Swoksaar, that’s me."

"Ah!" Hearing this, Chang Xian jumped once again.

He might not know who Wei Chen was, but the captain of Team Blue Rain, the owner of Swoksaar, he understood what these two identities meant. This middle aged man was actually that impressive a character?

"Hahaha, calm down, kid, don’t get so nervous upon hearing someone’s reputation. Look at you, how are you going to interview us like this?" Wei Chen shamelessly started lecturing.

"I… I…" Now it was Chang Xian who was stuttering like Qiao Yifan. It was a good thing that Chen Guo had started introducing the next person already. "This is Bao Rongxing, we all call him Steamed Bun, he’s the Brawler Steamed Bun Invasion."

Chang Xian listened with both ears perked, but didn’t hear anything after "owner". Chang Xian hastily ran over the introduction in his head again. It seemed to be just as he had heard. That’s weird! Something seemed to be lacking! Did this Steamed Bun have no impressive sort of background?

With there being beauties and ex-Team Tiny Herb members and Team Blue Rain captains, Chang Xian immediately expected each of the members of Happy to have some sort of impressive background. Yet Steamed Bun seemed to be a normal person, making Chang Xian a little disoriented. As he gazed at Steamed Bun, he heard Steamed Bun speak. "Good thing that you seem like a honest little reporter, otherwise I would have your leg for injuring the boss."

Holy crap!

Chang Xuan felt his legs turn to jelly. What kind of person was this! What kind of response was that! Seeing Steamed Bun seriously considering his leg, Chang Xian couldn’t take it as a joke. He wouldn’t really lose a leg upon leaving, would he?"

"Don’t mess around, Steamed Bun" Then, a guy with a cigarette in his mouth told Steamed Bun off. Chang Xian looked over and Chen Guo was already introducing him, "This is our captain, Ye Xiu, the player behind Lord Grim."

Ye Xiu!

Chang Xian had listened carefully. It was Xiu not Qiu. And, as a member of Esports Home, he knew for certain that in the registered players for Team Happy, Lord Grim’s player was definitely not Ye Qiu, but many people were suspicious that even if Ye Qiu hadn’t registered, he was still hiding in Team Happy, playing for them, and were therefore suspicious of who was the player behind Lord Grim.

But now, this player was introduced to him just like that, and as the captain, too. Chang Xian suddenly didn’t to dare suspect his identity.

"There’s also a Cleric, Little Cold Hands, but he’s busy today," Chen Guo continued.

Chang Xian nodded, going over the names and faces of each person he had been introduced to so far, but as he counted the people present, he suddenly realized there was one extra. This person kept his distance from everyone else, leaning against the wall stoically and watching on.

This person… was he the legendary god Ye Qiu!?

Chang Xian thought he had definitely managed to make a right guess, but saw how Chen Guo seemed to have no intentions of introducing him, but this was god Ye Qiu! That topic far outstripped anything like beautiful ladies, or Tiny Herb members or Blue Rain captains. In the media circle, nobody had managed to interview him except for Cao Guang. And even for Cao Guang, the interviews had been done over QQ.

Now that God Ye Qiu was in front of him, he couldn’t let go of the opportunity given to him, or else he couldn’t be called a reporter.

Chang Xian gathered his courage and stepped forwards without any prompting.

"Excuse me… are you God Ye Qiu?" Chang Xian greeted this cool guy. In his heart, god Ye Qiu who always refused to be interviewed was definitely someone who was aloof and proud like this.

"No." But the other person coldly denied it.

Chang Xian was waiting for him to speak again when Chen Guo introduced him as well. "This is Mo Fan, Ninja, Deception. He’s still considering whether or not he wants to join."

"Ah?" Chang Xian startled, disappointed upon knowing that this person wasn’t Ye Qiu. If Ye Qiu was really at Happy but didn’t want to come out for an interview, then he probably wouldn’t get a chance today.

Chang Xian turned his focus back to the others as he thought over this, but the name Chen Guo had given him flashed through his mind and he turned suddenly. "You’re Deception?"

Mo Fan glacned at him. He wouldn’t respond to a useless question like that.

"You… Give me back my equipment!!!" Then, Chang Xian said something that made everyone a little taken aback.

Chapter 828: I Once Had a Friend

Chang Xian wasn’t just an eSports reporter. He was also a fan of Glory. His work revolved around Glory. Outside of work, he spent most of his free time on Glory too.

In the Heavenly Domain, Chang Xian had a Striker account. He was a normal player in the game. As a result, he had suffered under the hands of the most infamous scrap picker in Glory, Deception.

When he had prepared for his interview, Chang Xian had seen the name Deception among the registered members in Team Happy, but from the time Team Happy accepted challenges to the recent three matches in the Challenger League, Deception’s character had never appeared a single time. Chang Xian thought that he wasn’t with Team Happy. Who would have thought that Deception really was a part of the team? Suddenly, Chang Xian’s grievances towards Deception exploded. At that time, he had lost the PK and died. His weapon dropped and before he could call over his friends to get it back, he saw Deception nimbly blend back into the chaotic crowd. After stealing his weapon, he just swaggered off without a second thought.

Chang Xian had seen everything clearly from his ghost’s view. That Thunder Fist was a weapon that he had spent who knew how much time and effort to obtain, but in just a quick PK, a scrap picker snatched it away. Chang Xian felt so disgusted that he stopped playing for a week.

He had thought of taking revenge on Deception, but in the vast Heavenly Domain, finding a single person wasn’t something that could be done with just patience and perseverance. Chang Xian persisted for a period of time, before finally giving up out of helplessness. Even though this incident had passed a while ago, seeing Deception among the members of Team Happy stirred up his previous anger. However, facing Team Happy, he needed to be professional. It wasn’t good to mix his personal emotions with his work. Deception may have been among the list of registered team members, he had never appeared on stage before. It wasn’t certain if he was actually in the team or not! The Challenger League rules were truly lax.

Chang Xian didn’t take the matter of Deception to heart up until now. When he heard the sudden introduction and realized that the cold, arrogant guy he thought was Ye Qiu actually turned out to be Deception, Mo Fan’s expression made him extremely annoyed. Impulse overcame him. He suddenly turned around and got into a fighting position in front of Mo Fan.

Everyone was astonished. To think such a coincidence would happen! Everyone clicked their tongues in wonder, but no one said anything. Mo Fan no longer had his expressionless face. He was somewhat dumbstruck. He probably wasn’t prepared to meet a victim of his in real life.

"Who….. are you?" Mo Fan finally asked.

"I’m called Death Reaper. My Lightning Fist was stolen by you. It seems like you don’t remember me?" Chang Xian shouted.

"Yes." Mo Fan said.

"Now that I’ve helped you remember, return it to me!" Chang Xian demanded. In reality, he already had a similar weapon now, but his arguing wasn’t over the weapon itself, but rather because of the grief he felt when he watched as his beloved weapon was stolen away. Chang Xian was already fairly calm at this point. After all, it had been awhile since that incident had occurred. If this meeting had happened within a week of that incident, he might have had the courage to physically kick him down.

"It’s gone." Mo Fan replied honestly, but it drove Chang Xian mad. He didn’t really want his equipment back. Now that you’ve been caught in real life by one of your victims, shouldn’t you at least have some sort of reaction? What is this?

"You you..." Chang Xian didn’t know what else to say. He wasn’t seeking his lost equipment, but looking to vent his anger. But now he realized that he didn’t know how the other side could make it up to him. Allow himself to get beat up? Chang Xian knew that wasn’t realistic.

The two were in the middle of their confrontation, when Qiao Yifan came back with water. He had no idea what had happened. When he saw Chang Xian over there, he delivered a cup of water to him under the gazes of everyone.

"Have some water." A fellow had popped up next to Mo Fan to give him some water. Chang Xian didn’t know how to respond.

Everyone had their hands to their foreheads. What type of scene was this!

"Cough, Little Chang, it looks like Mo Fan took your equipment. Today you’ve gotten a chance to meet us. How about we call it even? Arguing is pointless." Chen Guo revealed the air of a big sister and resolved this matter. In reality, her logic made no sense. However, Chen Guo could see Chang Xian’s anger. It wasn’t as exaggerated as his reaction had been. It had probably been a long time since that incident, so he wasn’t that angry anymore. That scar would still remain in his heart though. Someone more sociable might have even said a few words and ended up friends with him! Unfortunately, Mo Fan wasn’t that type of person. He replied with an earnest: "It’s gone." It was as if he were deliberately provoking him.

Chang Xian found himself facing such a person and found himself in an awkward spot. Chen Guo gave him a suitable excuse to get over this matter.

Chang Xian had been a reporter for a year. He was clever. He immediately understood that this was Chen Guo handing giving him a way out of the awkward situation between him and Mo Fan. He seized the opportunity, taking the water and thanking Qiao Yifan, while politely responding to Chen Guo.

QIao Yifan had gone to get water for the guest, so he didn’t know what had happened. He asked Mo Fan, next to him: "What’s going on?"

"He’s asking me for equipment!" Mo Fan replied with a simple answer. Chang Xian almost dropped his cup. He wasn’t asking for equipment! He wanted him to return his equipment. A single word made all the difference!

Chen Guo didn’t have a good impression of Mo Fan either way. Hearing his sharp and concise answer, she wasn’t happy. She said to Chang Xian: "Little Chang, how about we get down to business first. You two can talk about your private grievances later. No one will stop you."

"Oh oh, sure, sure. Then let’s start now? Speaking of which, I don’t have a good understanding of you guys. If I say something wrong, please forgive me!" Chang Xian spoke methodically.

"Haha, ask away." Chen Guo said.

"I really want to know if Ye Qiu, Team Excellent Era’s former captain, if God Ye Qiu is in Team Happy?" Chang Xian started off with the question he wanted to know the answer the most.

Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu. Everyone looked at Ye Xiu. They also wanted to know how he would answer this question.

"Ah, him! You could say he’s here. You could also say he’s not here." Ye Xiu said.

"What does that mean?" Chang Xian didn’t understand.

"You’ll understand when the time comes." Ye Xiu smiled.

How crafty! Everyone gasped in surprise. So he’s dodging the question? The reporter won’t pursue it, right?

Chang Xian didn’t pursue the matter. For an exclusive interview, he needed to pay attention to propriety. If he insisted on asking a question that the other side didn’t want to answer, he would bring the mood down. It would be very bad for the following questions. From this point, Chang Xian wasn’t experienced enough. If an experienced reporter like Cao Guangcheng had come for the interview, the reporter would not have let this opportunity pass. The reporter would not have asked this question first either. Asking this question last would not have been any better. If no valuable answer came, the reporter could just laugh it off and end the interview on a high note. If a juicy hint appeared, the reporter could pursue it relentlessly. Even if it irritated the other side, it at least wouldn’t affect the overall interview.

Chang Xian had been too impatient and started the interview with this question. He knew he couldn’t press too hard in the beginning of the interview, so when Ye Xiu dodged the question, he had to let this question go.

Afterwards, Chang Xian naturally asked about their thoughts on people denouncing them as being arrogant.

Ye Xiu smiled again: "The following match will prove everything."

"I can see that you guys are very confident. Do you think that your team is good enough to topple Team Excellent Era?" Chang Xian asked.

"As long as it’s a competitive match, anything is possible." Ye Xiu smiled.

Everyone wanted to boo in their hearts. There was no way Team Excellent Era would be a breeze to fight! If they had to fight against Team Excellent Era right now, Team Happy wasn’t confident in their chances. Ye Xiu was relying on the hope that the players on Team Happy would have a lot of time to improve. The current them and the future them would be completely different.

Ye Xiu had said these words to them, but facing an interview, he shut his mouth and didn’t mention it. He made it sound like they were very confident in their chances against Team Excellent Era.

"Uh, could I ask about your unspecialized? From what I know, your unspecialized Lord Grim possesses a unique Silver weapon that can switch forms."

"Yes."

"This weapon seems to have been created especially for unspecialized. Could you talk about how you came up with the idea for it? I feel that you must have exerted a lot of effort designing this weapon, right?"　　

Everyone looked at Ye Xiu.

Especially Chen Guo. This question very likely brought out a lot of emotions for Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu said that that youth, who had passed away already, was the most gifted talent he had known. Chen Guo had followed Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng to sweep his tomb. She didn’t doubt his words.

"I once had a friend..." Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 829: This is Enough

"I once had a friend…." Ye Xiu’s tone was severe, a smoking cigarette between his fingers. Everyone went silent, thinking that this would be an very unique, heart touching story. Chang Xian hurriedly moved closer with his recording pen, afraid of missing even a single word.

"Who was good at Glory." Ye Xiu said.

"And then, he died." Ye Xiu sighed, flicking ash from his cigarette and looking back at Chang Xian.

Having done some interviews and being quite a social person, Chang Xian wasn’t unfamiliar with this sort of look, but it’s appearance now was odd. It said that they were done speaking, and "it’s your turn to speak". Chang Xian doubted his understanding of the look and couldn’t help but ask, "That’s all?"

"That’s all." Ye Xiu said.

Everyone exchanged glances. It sounded like a randomly made up joke! Was this guy messing with that poor reporter?

That was what everyone including Chang Xian thought, but what could he do about it? He couldn’t point at the other party and say that it was bullshit. As a reporter, he had to interact with all sorts of people. He had to be able to tolerate them. Chang Xian had been on the edge of his seat with anticipation, and then he heard a story of "I once had a friend who was good at Glory and then he died," his emotions instantly changing to tearful.

"Ehem…." Chang Xian coughed lightly, self-consciously retracting his recording pen. The story made his brain short-circuit a little, unsure of how to continue.

Chang Xian pretended to sip his water, taking the chance to organize his thoughts. It wasn’t until there was only a quarter left in his cup that he recovered fully.

"To play as an unspecialized character, you need a lot of experience in Glory, or so I understand. How long as big brother Ye been playing Glory for?" Chang Xian asked.　"Ten years," Ye Xiu said.

"Ten years…." Chang Xian was startled by this. A Glory player with ten years of experience had to have started from when the game was first launched. Even in the pro circle, only Han Wenqing and a few other veterans had experience like that. Players who could play a game for ten years like that were few and far between.

"What’s so impressive about that? I have ten years of experience, too!" Wei Chen cut in.

"Amazing!" Chang Xian continued to exclaim. Wei Chen being the ex-captain of Blue Rain was a great topic, but Chang Xian hadn’t known anything about this beforehand, so he hadn’t done any research. Ex-Blue Rain captain? Wei Chen? These names were unfamiliar to him. As a worker in media, this wasn’t supposed to happen, but Chang Xian had only officially started working last year, so his research wasn’t that broad or deep. So when he spoke to Wei Chen, Chang Xian was very careful, afraid that he would anger the other.

"Um….Senior Wei, I’m a newbie in this line of work, so I haven’t read up on your background. Is it okay if you tell me about it?" Chang Xian hesitated, but eventually decided to be honest in his curiosity and ask.

"Hahaha, you want the tales of Glory of my youth? I could talk about that for days on end. You planning to stay the night?" Wei Chen said.

"No, no," Chang Xian sweatdropped, "Why don’t you pick a few interesting parts to tell?"

"Interesting? Then I would have to mention some big names. Like Ye Qiu, you know him, of course?" Wei Chen said.

"Of course!" Chang Xian hastily nodded. He was especially happy if these stories could allow him to further understand the other Gods; that information was very valuable. Chang Xian was so focused on listening to Wei Chen, that he didn’t notice everyone glancing at a certain someone when Ye Qiu was mentioned.　"I’m not just talking behind his back, but Ye Qiu really isn’t anything great!" Wei Chen said.　"Ah…." Hearing this, Chang Xian’s hands shook a little. Though pro players were enemies on the field, there were rarely any that would speak about another pro player like that. Chang Xian felt like he had struck gold.

"You know why he always refuses to appear in public eye?" Wei Chen asked.　"I don’t!" Chang Xian was excited! This was one of the great mysteries of Glory; would he be the one to solve it after all these years?

"The reason is…. That guy is very despicable, very shameless, very immoral. If he came under public eye, there’s no telling if he’ll survive the aftermath." Wei Chen said seriously.

"Um…." Chang Xian paused, "Why do you say that?"

"Because that’s the kind of person he is." Wei Chen said.

"How do you know this?" Chang Xian asked

"Thinking back to that time…." Wei Chen looked to be in deep thought, his other hand motioning towards Ye Xiu, asking for a cigarette. How shameless! Asking for a cigarette from the very person whose name you were blemishing!

The representative of justice, Chen Guo, was annoyed, standing up, even with the pain in her leg from the collision, "Don’t listen to his nonsense, Little Chang."

"N….nonsense?" Chang Xian stared in disbelief.

"This poor reporter came all the way over here, so be serious, don’t make things up," Chen Guo said.

"Make…. Make things up?" Chang Xian cried. He had thought he had gotten valuable information, but it was actually just a made up story. In comparison to this wretched looking older dude, Chang Xian was one thousand percent more willing to believe Chen Guo’s words.

"Eheh, I was just trying to make the interview contents more interesting! This way he could write a draft that would become the center of attention. We can let the readers try to figure out what’s true and what’s not," Wei Chen said.　

Chang Xian turned away decisively. It was better to interview someone other than this old guy. He had to do some more research and formulate some more specific questions; this guy’s bullshitting skills were just too damn good.

Turning his attention, Chang Xian’s gaze fell onto Qiao Yifan and his eyes lit up. A player originally from Tiny Herb, wasn’t that also a great topic? He hurriedly started to chat with Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan was such an honest person! In an interview, he was quite uneasy, but only said what was true. Chang Xian ended up a little disappointed by what information he had obtained. Though Qiao Yifan was from Tiny Herb, his story wasn’t that soul-stirring. He was a player who hadn’t gotten his contract renewed by a champion team or received any offers from other teams. A person who had been eliminated by the pro circle. In the end, he had found his place in a grassroots team like Happy. This… could be described as persistence, but if he really wanted to write about something inspiring, Happy hadn’t gotten any real accomplishments yet, so that wasn’t really possible.

Though there wasn’t anything soul-stirring about the contents, he could still write about his identity as a once-member of Team Tiny Herb. Chang Xian comforted himself with that before turning his attention to Tang Rou.

Her beauty made Chang Xian feel nervous as a budding young man, so he sipped his water and organized his emotions before speaking, "Before coming here, I had been wondering what kind of player the Battle Mage Soft Mist was. To be honest, I hadn’t expected them to be someone so beautiful."

"You flatter me," Tang Rou smiled.

"So, how long have you been familiar with Glory for?" Chang Xian asked.

"If we’re talking about just trying out the game, I had fought a few matches before. I only started seriously playing when the tenth server opened." Tang Rou said.

"You’ve only played seriously for half a year!!!" Chang Xian was shocked. What was up with Team Happy? If it wasn’t a monster from the early days, then it was a newbie from the new server. Were they purposefully trying to walk the extremes?

He hadn’t managed to digest his shock when Steamed Bun cut in like how Wei Chen had after "Ye Xiu’s ten years", interrupting them and further shocking Chang Xian with a "I started in the tenth server, too!"

"You, too…" Chang Xian was a little dumbstruck.

He suddenly realized that he didn’t need to get stories from these members of Team Happy in this interview. Just some background info was good enough to introduce them. How these people started playing Glory, got together, these topics were dull in comparison. Chang Xian knew that no tales of serendipitous meetings that would be more eye catching than their backgrounds.

This was just the beginning….

The phrase suddenly surfaced in his mind’s eye. No matter what, Team Happy had only gotten to the second round of the Challenger’s League so far. Though they had defeated the ex-pro Team Everlasting, no one could be certain of how far they would go. There was no need to look into it any further before they established their strength. Just the simple information he had gotten today was enough.

"May I take a group photo of you all?" Chang Xian was satisfied of his gains today after making that realization. He thought that Happy had potential, so he shouldn’t try to dig up everything he could get. Some, he should leave for the future, allowing for them to establish a stronger, longer relationship. Chang Xian was learning new things as he went.

"A group photo…. I don’t think that’s necessary? Some of our members aren’t even here today!" Ye Xiu said.

"Uhn, Cold Hands and Concealed Light, right?" What Chang Xian had looked into he had looked closely at.

"That’s right!" Ye Xiu nodded.

"Then…. How about a photo with just the owner?" Chang Xian asked.

No one here was stupid, they all knew that a topic like "beautiful boss" was a good one, so Chang Xian probably had such plans. Ye Xiu wouldn’t decide on his own for something like this, looking towards Chen Guo for her decision.

"Heheh, that’s fine, take one if you want!" Chen Guo didn’t mind. The title of beautiful boss was something she had in the Happy Internet Cafe too. Chen Guo didn’t boast about it or refuse. After all, she really was a beauty!

Chapter 830: Temporarily Not Publishing

Chang Xian had only been in this line of work for a little over a year and hadn’t had many chances to do exclusive interviews, but he had taken many photos over the past year, even when he had worked with Cao Guangcheng on an interview.

Chang Xian was rather skilled at photography. Chen Guo almost asked for a few copies of the photos he showed her, but she pushed down the urge; she couldn’t act like she was completely naive, right?

After the photos had been taken, the interview came to a close. Overall, it hadn’t taken very long. Chang Xian left after bidding them goodbye. Thinking back to it now, he knew he still lacked experience, which was why he had felt like he didn’t know where to start. And he had done so much preparation, too! If it had been Cao Guangcheng instead, he would be able to do much better at interviewing even someone he had met by coincidence and hadn’t prepared for.　　Difference! This was the difference in skill between them. To make a comparison to Glory, this was the difference between a rookie and a God.

Chang Xian lamented about this the whole way back.

"You’re back?" Cao Guangcheng was sitting in the living room, boredly watching TV. Seeing Chang Xian come in, he first glanced at the clock on the wall.

How much time it took to get to Excellent Era was something Cao Guangcheng was very clear of. Happy was across the street from Excellent Era, so the distance was about the same. The time that Chang Xian had used was, if his experience didn’t betray him, barely enough to familiarize himself with his targets.

"Yeah, I’m back," Chang Xian responded.

"Did you get to see Ye Qiu?" Cao Guangchang asked with false nonchalance. He had originally believed that Chang Xian definitely wouldn’t get to see Ye Qiu, but he started to doubt that after Chang Xian left. Times had changed! Ye Qiu was no longer the same Ye Qiu that was a part of Excellent Era. He had since left the pro scene. If he had changed his attitude and was now willing to be interviewed, wouldn’t that mean Cao Guangcheng had missed a great opportunity?

But Cao Guangcheng was a veteran interviewer in the Glory circle; he wouldn’t lose it for a big interview. So, even if he worried about it internally, he still sat in the room, peacefully waiting for Chang Xian to return.

"I didn’t."

Chang Xian’s answer was a huge relief to Cao Guangcheng. Though, if his experience as a veteran reporter was correct, there was no disappointment in Chang Xian’s words. That meant that Chang Xian had obtained satisfying results from his interview.

"Oh, then what did you manage to get?" Cao Guangcheng didn’t bother guessing and asked directly.

"Team Happy’s current captain, the one who applied with Lord Grim, is named Ye Xiu. He’s also a ten year veteran of Glory," Chang Xian started to introduce.

"Ye Xiu?" Cao Guangcheng was taken aback upon hearing this name.

"Yup, Ye Xiu. Xiu, not Qiu," Chang Xian said.　"That can’t be a coincidence, can it?" Cao Guangcheng had a sharp intuition. He immediately thought that Ye Qiu might have changed his name to apply for the Challenger League.

But, thinking over it again, Ye Qiu didn’t seem to have any reason to need to change his identity. It wasn’t as if he was doing some sort of top secret mission for the country. What did it matter if his identity was exposed? If it was, he would even be able to draw more attention. Cao Guangcheng had personally interviewed the Alliance’s representatives, knowing that the year in which a player couldn’t return after their retirement was only in regards to the Pro League. There were no similar rules for the Challenger League, since the Challenger League didn’t exist when the rules had been made. Even after the Challenger League was created, nothing like this had ever happened, so it was completely ignored.

So if it really was Ye Qiu, there was no problem with directly participating in the Challenger League under his own name.　In addition, if he really wanted to hide his identity, then why did he choose a name that made people think of Ye Qiu? And if he used a fake identity, how was he going to deal with the offline matches? He would definitely be exposed there!

Thinking of this, a fake name didn’t seem reasonable at all.

"Ye Xiu, has he been the player behind Lord Grim this whole time? What is his relationship with Ye Qiu?" Cao Guangcheng asked.

"Ah…." Chang Xian was stunned upon hearing this.

Difference! This was the difference in experience between them! How come he hadn’t thought to ask that before? This was a question that definitely should have been asked! Chang Xian became crestfallen upon realizing his mistake.

Cao Guangcheng could understand what he was thinking upon seeing his crestfallen look. He didn’t say much; he just smiled and said, "Don’t worry, take it slow!"

Speaking seriously, Cao Guangcheng was quite a good senior colleague to have. He often gave Chang Xian many useful tips, and although he had thought that this interview didn’t have much value, he didn’t stop Chang Xian from going. Even if this interview couldn’t be published, going out and trying for himself was a good learning experience for Chang Xian and could give him some experience. Later, when he realized Chang Xian might have the chance to interview Ye Qiu, Cao Guangcheng didn’t go and try to steal the opportunity from him.

"Ai, why didn’t I think of such an important question?" Chang Xian slapped himself on the head.

"Don’t worry about, there’ll be many more opportunities in the future for you. Tell me what you managed to find out first!" Cao Guangcheng said with a smile.

A beautiful boss, the strikingly attractive female player Tang Rou, Cao Guangcheng dismissed these topics with a smile after hearing them. This was esports, not entertainment, so beauty was only a peripheral advantage, not foundational. You had to have skills to earn achievements and survive in esports. Everything else was just on the side. For a team in the second round of the Challenger League like Happy, there was no reason to pay attention to how good the players looked.

"Is there anything else?" Cao Guangcheng asked. If that was it, there was no need to continue.　"Tang Rou only started playing when the new server was released," Chang Xian said.

"Oh?" This was definitely something much more interesting to Cao Guangcheng. Soft Mist was a character that had caught his eye a while back. If she had only started playing upon the launch of the new server, then the ability she had now was rather impressive. Only a person who had skill like that to back them up was worth the attention.

"Also, Bao Rongxing, Steamed Bun Invasion’s player, is also a player from the new server," Chang Xian said.

"Interesting, I diddn’t realize that Team Happy had such good talents!" Cao Guangcheng said.

"They don’t only have newbies. Qiao Yifan, the player of the Ghostblade, One Inch Ash, used to be a member of Team Tiny Herb last season. He’s a real pro player." Chang Xian said.

"Team Tiny Herb? Qiao Yifan?" Cao Guangcheng took a moment to process this. Though he was the team reporter for Excellent Era, he wasn’t clueless about the other teams. In fact, he was much more familiar with them than normal players and spectators were. He did rely on this to put food on the table after all.

But this Qiao Yifan…. Cao Guangcheng thought back through what he knew and vaguely had an impression of him. Using the process of elimination, he realized it might be the kid that joined Tiny Herb with Gao Yingjie.

"Tiny Herb didn’t renew his contract and he didn’t receive any offers from other teams, so he joined Team Happy," Chang Xian said.

"So it’s like that!" Cao Guangcheng nodded. Pro players like that weren’t very rare, but it was rare for one from a champion team like Tiny Herb to have fallen to joining a grassroots team. Even if they had to joined a team in the Challenger League, they would usually find a place in a team like Everlasting.

"There’s another person, called Wei Chen. He’s apparently the ex-captain of Team Blue Rain and…."　"Wei Chen?"

Chang Xian was about to say he didn’t know much about this person, but then Cao Guangcheng actually jumped out of his seat. He was an old reporter, so how could he not know who Wei Chen was? This was about a God from the first generation of Glory players. Starting with him, Team Blue Rain’s current captain Yu Wenzhou was the third successor of Swoksaar. Why would an old God like him, who had left the Glory circle for so long, suddenly return to participate in the Challenger League?

Cao Guangcheng was pretty sure he had met Wei Chen before. It was just that it was too long ago, so he only had a vague idea of what Wei Chen was like. At that time, Esports Home wasn’t comparable to other sports media like the way it was today! It was Glory that pushed the development of eSports to higher heights, allowing Esports Home to grow into the corporate giant that it was today.

The name Wei Chen really brought back memories!

"This Team Happy is very interesting," Cao Guangcheng nodded.

"Yeah, so I thought we could pay more attention to them in the future," Chang Xian said.

"Yeah, you should follow them!" Cao Guangcheng said.

"Then, I’ll go and organize the content for this," Chang Xian said.

"There’s no need to rush it. Just take it slow," Cao Guangcheng said.

"Oh yeah!" Chang Xian slapped his own forehead, "It’s only Saturday. I have over a day to do this!" Esports Home’s weekly papers came out every Monday and Friday. Since the Glory match days were usually held every Saturday, the reporters were used to organizing their information into drafts on Sunday, and Chang Xian had gone to interview a team from the Challenger League, which had its matches on Friday, leaving him with two days time to finish his article.

"You have plenty of time, don’t worry. The paper on Monday wouldn’t possibly publish your interview," Cao Guangcheng said.

"Why?" Chang Xian was startled.

"Because the match isn’t over," Cao Guangcheng said.

"Ah?"

"Do you think, with a hundred percent certainty, that Team Everlasting can’t turn the tides in the second round?" Cao Guangcheng asked.

"Well…."

"Only by completely claiming victory can Happy earn a place in the article for the Challenger League. For this issue, one sentence about Team Happy’s victory over Everlasting is the most you’ll be able to get," Cao Guangcheng said with certainty.

"In the second round of the Challenger League, Team Everlasting took a huge blow. Facing off against the recently popular Team Happy, they lost 8.5 to 1.5 on their home field. Their future in the Challenger League has become clouded. Team Everlasting began a closed training session after the match, planning on wiping away this shame in the second round."

Chen Guo flipped through the Monday issue of Esports Home, but didn’t find any other mention of Team Happy, and this article even had Everlasting as the main character. Chen Guo was confused.

"Where’s our interview?" Chen Guo began to suspect that her paper was missing pages.

"If we defeat Everlasting in this round, then it’ll appear," Ye Xiu understood the mechanics behind this.

Chapter 831: Rookie’s Block

The role given to Team Happy in this article was a foil to the real main character, no more than a sentence. It was submerged in the reports of the Pro League matches, struggling to stand out amongst the other information present.

For a team from the pro league like Everlasting, the amount of attention they received would greatly decline after they were eliminated last year. As for Happy, the attention they received was atypical at best. Most of those who paid attention to them did so with the hopes that they would lose. If Happy really did lose embarrassingly, then they would definitely rail and yell about it. However, with the victories that Happy had to its name recently, they were as silent as the grave. No one would come out to discuss them.

Most players didn’t purchase the issue of Esports Home to read about the Challenger’s League.

Last Saturday, the third round of the Pro League had come to a close, but the anticipatory air for the new season had not yet subsided. The one who drew the most attention was, once again, the youngest pro player, Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen. During the Blue Rain home field match against Royal Style, Lu Hanwen’s ability shocked everyone to the core again. He managed to consecutively defeat two members of Royal Style as the first player for Team Blue Rain in the group arena. His fighting spirit showed no signs of faltering in the third round against the ace of Royal Style, Tian Sen and his ancient god-level account, Peaceful Hermit. Though he lost to Tian Sen in the end, he had already taken the spotlight. Some even thought that, had Lu Hanwen not had to fight two others and lose a good deal of health, he would’ve beaten the god Tian Sen in a fair one on one match.

No one even cared about the resulting points of the match anymore. Everyone’s focus was on the group arena and the tactics that Blue Rain had used these three rounds.　

Dual Blademasters.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain and Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Clouds appeared together in the line-up for the Team Competition. The important position of main attacker that once belonged to Yu Feng was given so confidently to this young rookie.

Lu Hanwen’s account wouldn’t be weak in any way. If Team Blue Rain could armor Troubling Rain, then, so long as they had enough materials, they wouldn’t have any problem getting Flowing Clouds the exact same set of equipment either. However, pro characters had to be adjusted to each player, so there were rarely any two same characters for different players.

Flowing Clouds’ equipment hadn’t copied Troubling Rain’s, but the 10 pieces of Silver equipment on him were not a single bit worse than Troubling Rain’s. Out of these, four pieces were different, the most eye-catching being his weapon.

Troubling Rain held the lightsaber, Ice Rain, which was covered in a flickering blue light; Flowing Clouds’ Silver weapon was a greatsword: Flame Shadow.

Greatswords and lightsabers were two opposing extremes among Blademaster weapons. Lightsabers were the lightest and fastest swords, while greatswords were weighty and slow. However, greatswords were superior in physical attack.

Blademasters with lightsabers had a completely different playstyle compared to Blademasters that used greatswords. In the current pro circle, or even the entire Glory circle, lightsaber users were the majority, or maybe even taichi users. Either way, most depended on speed, preferring to fight with quick strikes. Yet, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Clouds was atypical. He gave up the speedy and light lightsaber for the heavy but powerful greatsword.

This problem was something people had been discussing ever since Lu Hanwen had debuted with Flowing Clouds. Now, after the third round, Lu Hanwen’s fierce performance had shut up all those who doubted him. Although, many experts had pointed out that, since he was a rookie with an all new character, Lu Hanwen and his greatsword Blademaster Flowing Clouds would be a surprise for all.

If Lu Hanwen could keep up his current pace, as the competition continued and other teams started to understand his playstyle, it was hard to say if he would be able to maintain his current performance.

This problem was something that was very common to the Alliance, called the Rookie's Block.

What it referred to was when talented rookies drew attention with their great performance, they slowly lost their pace as other teams became more and more familiar with the way they played. This situation was the so-called Rookie's Block.

As for what happened to rookies after that, it differed between each player. Some would hit the block hard and were thrown back equally as hard, slowly having to rebuild their style and get used to pro matches again. Others would be able to make the necessary adjustments to continue performing stably. However, their performance after hitting the Rookie's Block would never be as eye-catching as it used to be. In the history of the Alliance, there were only two people who managed to break through the block without faltering, excluding the first generation of pro players who were all rookies anyways.

The first was the current captain of Team Tiny Herb, Wang Jiexi, who debuted in the third competitive season of the Alliance; the other wasn’t currently in the Alliance, but struggling to fight his way through the Challenger’s League with Excellent Era: the seventh season Best Rookie, Sun Xiang.

Only these two managed to completely avoid the Rookie's Block. Apart from them, everyone, even the golden generation, Zhou Zekai, Tang Hao, and last season’s Best Rookie Zhao Yuzhe, had all been affected by the Rookie's Block.

The Rookie's Block existed subjectively. That was why each team would always take extra caution in understanding how each talented rookie would try to deal with it. For example, Team Tiny Herb’s genius Gao Yingjie hadn’t been sent out into matches immediately after his contract was signed. He started out as a backup player, slowly getting used to the pace of pro matches. Since his chances of getting onto the field were quite limited, he had to give up the opportunity of becoming Best Rookie, but this gradual accommodation allowed Gao Yingjie to slip past the Rookie's Block without too much trouble. Now, in this season, Gao Yingjie had enough experience and had managed to become accustomed to the pace of pro matches as a second year player. If he encountered any sort of problems, it wouldn’t be as serious as it might’ve been had he still been a complete rookie.

Different players had different ways to overcome the Rookie's Block that suited them.

Gao Yingjie had quite a soft personality, so his team chose this steady method of helping him past the Rookie's Block. Though it was rather unfortunate that he wouldn’t have a chance to get the Best Rookie award, it was still good for Gao Yingjie’s development in the long-term.

As for Team Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen? He had been protected in the opening round, not appearing at the press conference, but after the second round, he walked onto the stage with Team Blue Rain’s captain Yu Wenzhou and ace Huang Shaotian.

The reporters were, naturally, very interested in this rookie, but after meeting him face to face, they all thought that Team Blue Rain’s protection in the first round was overly excessive!

This young man was optimistic, energetic, open, and cheerful, unafraid of the offense these reporters were mounting. He was brave enough to say anything, opening up about everything. He was able to express himself clearly, though his words lacked the slippery edge of a veteran. He was only a fourteen year old teenager; if he had learned how to structure and smoothen his words, it would be a total blemish on his image. In comparison, Team Tiny Herb’s Gao Yingjie was more than a year older than Lu Hanwen and had a year’s worth of experience in the pro circle, yet wasn’t nearly as neat as Lu Hanwen when it came to interviews.

With the third round over, there was no way Lu Hanwen could stay hidden from the public after drawing such attention.

This budding young boy not only triggered the touting of the fans, but also became the favorite of the media. At Team Blue Rain’s press conference, not many people even bothered with Huang Shaotian anymore. That guy wouldn’t stop with his nonsense once he started, so most would rather listen to Lu Hanwen’s occasional clumsy slips in speech.

In this issue of Esports Home, Lu Hanwen had taken the cover story and the headlines. There was no doubt that he was the brightest star in this round of matches. However, Esports Home was still an all inclusive media. Their reports wouldn’t tilt too much towards any team, so, they pointed out the problem of the Rookie's Block even as they praised Lu Hanwen.

As for the local newspapers in the areas around Team Blue Rain, they weren’t nearly as clear headed.

These media channels weren’t focused on eSports, but all had section for sports. They, of course, couldn’t lack the continuously popular eSports, especially not Glory.　For these local media, their favoritism and biased opinion was obvious. The local media in Team Blue Rain’s area described Lu Hanwen as invincible. Rookie's Block? In their opinion Lu Hanwen would no doubt become the third person after Wang Jiexi and Sun Xiang to avoid the Rookie's Block.　Of course, they wouldn’t put this down without coming up with a reasonable analysis for it.

Wang Jiexi’s style was everchanging to the point of extreme success. The incredibleness of the Magician playstyle wasn’t someone that had ever appeared before, so for Wang Jiexi, it was the powerhouse teams that had hit a Rookie's Block, and had been hitting it hard over the course of the season. By the time they managed to make some headway into countering it, the season was over and Wang Jiexi managed to retain his halo all throughout that season.

As for Sun Xiang, he was a God coming from a small team. No matter how strong he was, his team would be holding him back from what he could truly achieve. All the powerhouses aimed to defeat teams, not just specific people, so they wouldn’t put too much effort into researching someone like Sun Xiang who was from an inconsequential team. That team would pose no threat anyways! Since Sun Xiang was very strong, this limited research wouldn’t be able to give him much trouble, making his debuting season smooth going.

These two Rookies who managed to avoid the Rookie's Block had reasons behind how they did it. Pro-Team Blue Rain media was now saying that Lu Hanwen could do the same, so they had to back themselves up with some form of evidence. To do so, these media channels found a relatively reasonable explanation. That was Lu Hanwen’s personality.

Though he was young, he also had no fear, just like how a newborn calf didn’t fear a tiger. What these media channels believed was that, with such a personality, Lu Hanwen wouldn’t falter no matter what difficulties lay ahead of him. Wang Jiexi didn’t give his opponents the chance to build a Rookie's Block and Sun Xiang’s Rookie's Block wasn’t strong enough for him. As for Lu Hanwen, many people believed he would be the first to completely shatter the Rookie's Block.

Chapter 832: The Alliance in Chaos

Chen Guo obviously wouldn’t get any local papers that reported on Team Blue Rain, so she only had an issue of the Esports Home. As for City H, the local papers would report eSports and even Glory news, but Chen Guo was too lazy to go out and buy them. Even if she bought them, she would be too lazy to read them.

It was similar to how the local papers for Team Blue Rain would just be praising the team. In City H, the local papers would just be praising Team Excellent Era instead.

Once Team Excellent Era was relegated last season, the team practically stopped being covered by national papers, but in the City H local papers, Team Excellent Era would always be talked about in the eSports section. Team Excellent Era was described with having an air of suffering patiently, but still firmly set on getting their revenge.

Chen Guo had initially thought about how Team Happy was a City H team too. Would Team Happy be covered by the local media?

During their period of infamy, Chen Guo had bought a City H evening paper. When she skimmed over it, Team Happy had been introduced, but they were treated like a joke and a disgrace…...

In the eyes of the City H local papers, Team Excellent Era was City H’s flag in Glory. You’re just some upstart Internet cafe team and you claim that you’re going to topple Team Excellent Era? To them, Team Happy was a traitor within their ranks.

Chen Guo had been furious at the time. She threw it into the trash can. From then on, she refused to buy any local evening papers and would only look at unbiased news sources that didn’t discriminate against any team.

In this week’s issue, Chen Guo didn’t see any content related to Team Happy, making her somewhat disappointed. As for all the hype in the pro scene, Chen Guo wasn’t as passionate about it anymore now that she no longer supported a pro team. From time to time, she would dream about Team Happy reaching the pro scene and becoming a part of the wind and rain covered in the news. She couldn’t help but feel moved during those moments.

"What? We have to wait for next week’s issue?" With no news related to them, Chen Guo threw this week’s issue onto the table.

"Tot put it more precisely, it would be the next next issue. The Friday issue comes out before our match." Ye Xiu corrected Chen Guo, while grabbing the newspaper off the table.

"F*ck, let me see." Wei Chen wanted to see it too, but he was farther away. When he reached over, Ye Xiu had already snatched it up, so he glared at Ye Xiu disapprovingly.

Ye Xiu didn’t look at him. He took a page out and gave it to Wei Chen. Wei Chen looked over it and threw it back: "F*ck, this senior doesn’t watch Interstellar Journey!"

Interstellar Journey was currently the most popular RTS game around. It also had a pro scene, but it wasn’t nearly as popular as Glory. It did have a fair amount of fans though, so the eSports section also did some coverage it. Ye Xiu had given Wei Chen a non-Glory page. Other eSport games like Fighting God, Interstellar Journey, etc. were squeezed onto this page. Everything Wei Chen didn’t want to see was on there.

"Ah, Interstellar Journey! I can play that. Let me see!" Steamed Bun Invasion happily picked up the page that Wei Chen had thrown away as if it were trash. This guy had played many different games before. Tang Rou was new to gaming. She only knew how to play Glory. It could be said that his talent partially stemmed from his experience from all the other games he had played. It looked like Interstellar Journey was one such game.

"It seems like this season’s quite chaotic!" Ye Xiu skimmed over the news and then flipped to page with the Glory Alliance point rankings.

Only three matches had been played, so the relative ranking between the teams weren’t too different from before, but because a total of ten points could be obtained for each match, after three rounds, the difference in points between each grouping was quite obvious.

The powerhouses were still as strong as ever. Team Samsara and Team Blue Rain continued their outstanding performance from the previous, and because of the Four Heavenly Kings of Team Tyranny, their dominating strength placed them at the very front of the point rankings. Apart from these three teams, Team Wind Howl had also managed to start off strong. Tang Hao’s addition to the team, as well, the rookie Zhao Yuzhe’s steady performance, and their old guard Fang Rui’s dirtiness made Team Wind Howl appear very strong. Compared to the other big names in the leading group, it was their first in the history of the team.

After them, Team Tiny Herb, Team Misty Rain, and Team Void had good records too, but they weren’t as outstanding as the aforementioned teams.

The others were in the middle or were pacing back and forth between relegations. The one team that made people the most conflicted was Team Hundred Blossoms.

After three rounds, Team Hundred Blossom’s Dual Blossoms had returned, but their performance disgraced the name of the original Dual Blossoms that had consisted of Zhang Jiale and Sun Zheping.

Yu Feng wasn’t in form with his new Berserker, Falling Scattered Flowers.

After Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was sold, Zou Yuan obtained a new Spitfire character: Blooming Blossoms. As the core of the team, Team Hundred Blossoms easily created a new set of powerful equipment for it, similar to how Team Blue Rain equipped Flowing Cloud. Blooming Blossoms’ strength wasn’t weak, but Zou Yuan still hadn’t left his slump from last season. This was quite disappointing for many fans of Team Hundred Blossoms.

Team Hundred Blossoms was currently in 17th place. They were just two steps away from entering the relegation zone. A three-time championship contender to have declined to such a state was way too sorrowful. No one knew if Team Hundred Blossoms would be able to get back up from this.

"Okay, it’s time for practice." Ye Xiu only cared about the final point rankings reported on the paper and then put the paper aside.

But Chen Guo knew very well that it wasn’t that Ye Xiu didn’t care. It was just that the analysis done by the author wasn’t any use to him. After leaving Team Excellent Era last year, Ye Xiu practically watched every single match that was played in the Pro League and even organized them all into a file. The new season was the same. Early in the morning last Sunday, Chen Guo had gone to get a drink of water, when she noticed Ye Xiu sitting in front of the computer, quietly watching the third round of matches that had just finished Saturday night.

Ye Xiu wasn’t currently in the pro scene, but Chen Guo was certain that he still knew the pro scene inside and out like before.　　

Everyone on Team Happy needed to practice everyday. This week’s practice was more specialized than it had been the past few weeks. With an 8.5 to 1 lead, Team Happy still didn’t dare to be negligent. Having direct experience fighting with Team Everlasting, Ye Xiu organized more focused practice this week. This week, they would be facing Team Everlasting with a home field advantage. Ye Xiu wasn’t planning on setting their goal at just winning two points.

With a huge 8.5 to 1 lead, you could say that you wouldn’t be careless, but subconsciously, it was hard to completely rid yourself of those thoughts. In this situation, if you set your goal at only winning two points, you might indulge yourself in laziness. In a single-elimination tournament, there was no room for negligence.

Three days soon passed. In the blink of an eye, Thursday came. Ye Xiu asked Team Heavenly Swords to borrow their equipment temporarily.

"God….. I don’t think we can keep doing this." Lou Guanning lent the equipment to Ye Xiu, but he couldn’t help but voice his complaint.

After all, Team Heavenly Swords was still participating in the Pro League too. Lending equipment in this way would certainly affect them too. Once or twice didn’t matter too much. In any case, Team Heavenly Swords didn’t have any ambitious goals for this season, but doing this repeatedly would only magnify the effects.

Team Happy played in the Challenger League every Friday, so they borrowed the equipment on Thursday to get used to the equipment, but by taking these equipment away, Team Heavenly Swords lost two days of practice. Team Heavenly Swords had their match on Saturday too. Even if the equipment was returned on Friday, they only had half of Saturday left to get their practice in. Before a match, no team would conduct any intense practice. Adjusting their mind set was what was more important. Two days of practice without equipment would add up and impact Team Heavenly Sword’s practice.

Lou Guanning was certain that God understood this reasoning, so he didn’t think God would be so indiscreet, but Ye Xiu borrowed the equipment so naturally and calmly. Lou Guanning couldn’t help but complain, hoping to remind him.

"Mm, I know. It’s just because of special circumstances this time. If not, we wouldn’t have inconvenienced you. We have to do our best to get our own equipment too!" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh? God, you have ideas for Silver equipment?" Lou Guanning was suddenly interested. This was an important resource! For a new team like Team Heavenly Swords, they lacked this resource. They had to start their research on Silver equipment from scratch. Their wastage of rare materials was very large. If there was a reliable method to produce Silver equipment and create one in a single try, then he would naturally be interested in it.

Lou Guanning knew that no one would give him this sort of information without good reason. He had tried trading with Clubs before, but which Club would easily sell this information? If they had to sell, they would just sell equipment. Unless they could no longer keep the team operating, no one would even think about selling their creation methods. Lou Guanning had gone full circle, but was only able to purchase either the outdated or unnecessary equipment from other teams. He obviously hoped to have a reliable long-term method. As soon as he heard that God had this kind of resource, his eyes lit up. 　

"I have a few ideas, but I’m still in the process of organizing my thoughts." Ye Xiu replied.

Lou Guanning was excited: "Then... are there any suitable ideas for us to use?"

"That... I’ll have to think about that in the future. Right now, I’m mainly focusing on our team’s current classes." Ye Xiu said.

"Please God! If there’s anything suitable for us, please come to us. The price will be easy to negotiate." Lou Guanning said. He had the money, but the problem was that no one was willing to sell! If the other side didn’t want to sell, but you insisted on buying, then the price would just be raised sky high. No matter how rich Lou Guanning was, he didn’t want to spend so much money without good returns. A character could equip a total of thirteen pieces of equipment, including the weapon. If he had to throw away his money for everything, his pocket wouldn’t be able to take it.

As a result, Lou Guanning first bought twenty pieces of equipment. The rest would depend on the situation. As soon as he heard that this God, who he had a very good relationship with, might be creating equipment, of course Lou Guanning would be excited.

Chapter 833: Control

"Even if it’s sound, it’ll also depend on if you have the materials to make it." Ye Xiu said.

"We’ll have enough." Lou Guanning was quite confident. In the Heavenly Domain, their wild boss hunting was becoming more and more prosperous each day. They had a stable harvest. In the normal servers, Guild Heavenly Justice had established their power a long time ago throughout all ten servers, so their competitiveness was high. What’s more, there may only be one Heavenly Domain, but there were ten normal servers. Even though wild bosses refreshed every week, the total output from the normal servers was ten times greater than that of the Heavenly Domain. In terms of the number of accumulated materials, there were much more normal server materials than Heavenly Domain materials.

Guild Heavenly Justice wasn’t founded just on a whim. They had started accumulating materials in the normal servers early on. If God Ye Qiu had a mature concept in mind, there wouldn’t be an unnecessary consumption of materials. Producing a piece of Silver equipment at such a low price was no different from a pie dropping from the heavens.

"Okay then. I’ll help take a look for you guys. If you have enough materials, my side needs materials too. Help us out too!" Ye Xiu said.

"That’s not a problem!" Lou Guanning happily replied. This trade wouldn’t be a bottomless pit. If they could create a piece of Silver equipment in one attempt, that sort of capital was nothing for a guild like theirs. Ye Xiu had to work on his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella alone, which was why it had been so difficult. If it had been a Club, with already completed blueprints, producing it would only take a few minutes.

After Lou Guanning reached an agreement with Ye Xiu, he bid goodbye in high spirits. He once again experienced the advantages of being on good terms with God Ye Qiu. This wasn’t something money could do for him. If he could get it with money, Lou Guanning also hoped that his side would have such an all-around talent.

Ye Xiu once again borrowed equipment from Heavenly Justice and distributed them to everyone. Everyone had the same equipment that they had last week. Following afterwards, they would need to start getting used to their new equipment.

That night went by quietly. The next day, they did some adjustment practice before the match. Team Happy would now be officially starting their fourth match, so Ye Xiu no longer needed to walk everyone through the practice routine by the hand. Everyone had already grasped the routine and would finish it every day on their own accord.

Eight o’clock that night, the second round of their second match officially began. For this round, Team Happy would have their home game. Thus, the maps would be chosen by Team Happy.

In Team Everlasting’s practice room, their boss personally showed up to supervise the match. Everyone had solemn expressions. After the end of the previous round, Team Everlasting’s boss had given a bottomline to the players: if Team Everlasting was eliminated in the second round, the team would have difficulty surviving.

After all, Team Everlasting wasn’t just some grassroots team formed by normal players. In those grassroot teams, it was just a bunch of good friends getting together to have some fun. Pay didn’t need to be considered, but for Team Everlasting, apart from the players, the Club also had other employees. The wages for these employees as well as the bills for electricity, water, etc. wasn’t a small expenditure. Despite Team Excellent Era residing in the Challenger League and their hopes of breaking through to the pro scene was miniscule, as long as they could hold on until the offline matches, they would be able to survive the entire season.

Once the offline competition started, the Challenger League matches would be streamed, and there would be advertisements and sponsors for the matches. The participating teams would earn a portion of that money. Even though it wasn’t nearly as profitable as the Pro League, with the help of this revenue, Team Everlasting could still survive the season. As for those grassroot teams, if they could actually reach this stage, it could be considered as a fair amount of money.

As the offline matches continued and teams began to get eliminated, the bonuses would continue to increase. For Team Everlasting, which had come from the pro scene, even if they couldn’t beat the final boss, Team Excellent Era, they thought that as long as they didn’t meat Team Excellent Era or any other former pro team in the early rounds, they would easily be able to walk into that elimination stage. But now, they were only at the second round and they were close to being eliminated. It was way too early. Team Everlasting’s boss didn’t have the money to support the team for another season without any revenue.

Team Everlasting’s boss notified the team about this matter. The current Team Everlasting had a mindset of desperately fighting for survival. With a life and death crisis approaching, every player practiced extremely diligently. This week, their practice quality was very high. After a final period of adjustment before this match, the moment that would decide their fate had finally arrived.

How would Team Happy arrange their line up? What maps would they choose?

Team Everlasting studied Team Happy day and night. Each player in Team Happy was studied carefully and repeatedly. They formulated their strategy according to the strengths of these players and their guesses towards Team Happy’s line-up.

The preparation phase of the match began. For this time’s life and death battle, there were actually fewer spectators than before. The vast majority of the crowd this time consisted of actual Team Everlasting fans who wanted to cheer for their team in this crucial moment. As for those waiting to watch Team Happy burn, coming to this match didn’t make much sense. With an 8.5 to 1 lead, was a comeback going to be so easy? With the face slappers not coming, those with a slight interest in Team Happy wouldn’t come either. Most of those who came to watch Team Happy were there to watch the face slappers choke and laugh at them. If the face slappers weren’t coming, they weren’t going to come either. As for the others, the point difference was too wide, so they were too lazy to come out and watch too. This once again proved how the current tournament format could potentially kill the suspense of a match too early, reducing the next round to be of little interest.

The only ones who wouldn’t think in this way would be the two participating teams and Team Everlasting’s fans.

In the preparation phase, Team Everlasting’s fans tried their hardest to support their team. Chen Guo was very easily absorbed into this type of mentality and accidentally started to sympathize with these fans. Team Everlasting would certainly be defeated by them. There would be no miracle. Chen Guo was incomparably confident about this point.

In the preparation stage, the two sides arranged their lineups and the home side chose the maps. After everything was finished, the match officially began.

When the map was announced for the first match of the individual competition, Team Everlasting’s side suddenly exploded into an uproar.

Map: Ring.

Yes, Ring. In the game’s Arena, it was the most commonly used map, but in the pro scene, very few chose this map.

This map was very simple and made matters easier, but it could be considered as a huge waste of the home game advantage. The home game advantage came from the maps. Choosing a map that the team was familiar with and often practiced in would strengthen a team, but Ring? It was a flat rectangular platform without any sort of terrain.

Choosing this map was equivalent to throwing away their home game advantage. This choice left Team Everlasting perplexed, but the match had already started. The starting players leapt into the competitor position. Team Happy - Steamed Bun Invasion. Team Everlasting, Dawn Rifle.

The first players to go on stage were the same tow as in the first round. However, in the first round, Team Everlasting had wanted to show the other side their might. However, in the second round, their thoughts were now that they could not lose. They had to win this point no matter what.

As a result, Team Everlasting’s captain Wu Chen, their most reliable player with three years of professional experience, once again came out.

Dawn Rifle stood on the competitor spot. Wu Chen sucked in a deep breath of air and watched the clock countdown: 3, 2, 1. Start!　　

Attack!

As soon as the match loaded in, Wu Chen attacked. The Ring was a small map without anywhere to hide. The cannon on Dawn Rifle’s shoulder boomed and an artillery shell flew towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

Wu Chen did not underestimate Steamed Bun Invasion. Even though he won the first round against him with ease, winning because of such a strange reason made him puzzled. From the other data on Steamed Bun Invasion, as well as from their team competition, Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t seem to be a stupid player!

All out!

The current Wu Chen completely forgot about Steamed Bun Invasion’s embarrassing performance in the first round and only thought about defeating his opponent.

Steamed Bun responded nimbly. Attacking him from such a distance wouldn’t pose a threat to him. Steamed Bun Invasion twisted and dodged past the artillery shell. That was just the overture though. Wu Chen’s following attacks continued to arrive. On a simple map like the Ring, even Steamed Bun wouldn’t get lost. While dodging these attacks, Steamed Bun Invasion gradually grew closer to Dawn Rifle.

In a fight against a long-ranged class like a Launcher, the health on both sides would rarely closely follow the other. While the distance between them was far, the Launcher could continuously suppress and deal damage to the opponent, but as soon as the opponent successfully closed in, a large chunk of the Launcher’s health would usually instantly disappear.

The health of the two characters would often fall through these trades. The final victory depended on which side made the most of their situation when they held the dominant position. Apart from technical skill and decision-making, a certain level of calculating prowess was needed. For someone like Steamed Bun, that wouldn’t be easy. In an even playing field, Steamed Bun Invasion eventually fell in the end after a few exchanges.

Steamed Bun’s technical skill was no worse than Wu Chen’s. His loss could mainly be attributed to his lack of control over the situation. The health on the two sides continued to drop through their exchanges, but Wu Chen actually had a grasp on the pace of it. Steamed Bun was just charging in recklessly and missed many opportunities.

"Oh oh oh oh!!!" With the first round of the individual competition won, the Team Everlasting fans among the crowd surged. Even in Team Everlasting’s practice room, everyone had smiles on their faces. Even though winning one point didn’t make much of an impact on their overall situation, a good beginning made them feel like luck may be in their favor.

The second round. Map - Indigo Temple. Team Happy - Windward Formation.

When they saw this name, Team Everlasting’s heart jumped. Everyone looked at their chosen player and their expressions became very complicated.

Chapter 834: Training

As soon as the veteran made his move, the outcome became very obvious.

Windward Formation’s ruthlessness was deeply felt by Team Everlasting that round. In the eyes of Team Everlasting, Windward Formation was second only to Lord Grim as their most troublesome opponent.

He had now appeared in the second round of the individual competition. As for Team Everlasting? Their second contestant was their Sharpshooter, a half-main roster seventh player. Asking him to take down Windward Formation was asking too much of him.

If Team Everlasting lost two points, they would be eliminated from the Challenger League. The group arena and individual competition didn’t need to be mentioned. Both competitions were worth more than two points each. They could not lose a single point here. As a result, they sent out their strongest line-up to face the challenge. Ensuring that their team won at least two points in the individual competition was a difficult issue, because the Sharpshooter seventh player was slightly worse than the six players of the main roster.

Team Everlasting puzzled over it for a long time. In the end, their line-up was the exact same as in their previous round. They entrusted their fate to the heavens.　

But Team Happy made a change in their line-up and placed Windward Formation second. On paper, it looked like Team Happy had a much higher chance of winning. However, Team Everlasting didn’t seem particularly worried.

They had been prepared for their Sharpshooter to lose this point. If this point was lost to Windward Formation, it would be similar to Tian Ji’s horse race (accepting one loss to ensure two wins). It was the exact situation that Team Everlasting had been hoping for. Now it had really happened.

3, 2, 1. And the match started.

Wei Chen had picked Indigo Temple himself. It was undoubtedly his most familiar 1v1 map. In an official match, Wei Chen withdrew his intentions of toying with his opponent and unscrupulously wiped the floor with his opponent. Wei Chen utilized the characteristics of his character and the map to the maximum. Team Everlasting’s side was their slightly weaker seventh player. In the second round, Wei Chen easily took the match without any suspense.

Even though Team Everlasting had expected this outcome, the result still made them nervous. The following third match would decide their fate in this life and death match.

Because they had anticipated this result, Team Everlasting sent out an Elementalist player with a strong mentality, who appeared on the competitor seat for the third round. This battle would determine Team Everlasting’s fate. Someone without a strong mentality wouldn’t be able to bear this sort of pressure.

Even this player was constantly breathing deeply to adjust himself. He wanted to get rid of that last thread of nervousness in him.

But at this moment, Team Happy sent out a player that had never appeared before last round against Team Everlasting: Concealed Light.

Team Everlasting stared foolishly.

For the entire week, apart from improving themselves, they thoroughly studied Team Happy, but this Concealed Light wasn’t within their range of investigation. Even though he was registered as a team member, there was no information on him at all.

And now this completely blank character was actually going to fight. Team Everlasting suddenly panicked. Even their mentally strong Elementalist player was starting to seem troubled.

While his hands were trembling slightly, Luo Ji was already so nervous that he couldn’t even keep his mouse steady. He felt like his hands and feet had turned numb. His heart was beating so fast that he didn’t need to feel it to feel it. Sweat covered his forehead.

"Experience needs time to be accumulated." Ye Xiu said to him, when he called him onto the stage. Even though Luo Ji wasn’t at City H, the match took place, so he could still participate from school.

Experience might need to be accumulated, but was directly having him go into such an important match to accumulate it a bit too excessive? Luo Ji cried in his heart. He was often bullied around in the in-game Arena. Now he needed to face a player from a former pro team. It was just too frightening for him.

Even though it wasn’t good to relax just because they had a big lead, giving a new player a chance to feel the pace and atmosphere of an official match was necessary. They couldn’t just keep training him forever until a critical moment in a match appeared before pushing him onto the stage. There were certainly players who astounded the world with just a single brilliant feat, but Luo Ji’s personality and skill level didn’t fit into that category of players. As a result, with an 8.5 point lead, Ye Xiu arranged for Luo Ji to give it a try. In fact, Ye Xiu had wanted to do it in the first round. Throwing in Chen Guo to fulfill the quota was a bit of a waste. After all, Chen Guo didn’t have much potential. She wouldn’t be actually be a part of Team Happy’s line-up. Unfortunately, last Friday, Luo Ji had important business to take care of, so he couldn’t participate in it. As a result, in the second round, Ye Xiu wasn’t going to let this training opportunity go and put him in the individual competition.

3,2,1….

No matter how nervous Luo Ji or Team Everlasting’s Elementalist player was, the system mercilessly started the match as soon as the countdown ended. This match wasn’t a Ring, but a map that Luo Ji chose himself. In terms of utilizing a map’s advantage, Luo Ji’s skill in that aspect was above Steamed Bun’s.

But being panicked, it was hard to say if he could utilize the map properly. As soon as the match started, Luo Ji immediately began summoning. He should be familiar with this, but because he was nervous, he appeared all over the place. His summoned creatures started automatically started wandering around. For a moment, there didn’t seem to be any control over them.

Summoning a bunch of creatures all at once was also somewhat of a noob move. Summoners relied on their summoned creatures to battle, but their summoning skills had cooldowns. By letting out a huge swarm of them, he was practically using up all of his skills, making his pace of the battle seem lacking. However, against an experienced player, such a lack of pacing was devastating.

Team Everlasting’s Elementalist entered the match with a thread of fear against Concealed Light, but as soon as the match started, he saw the other side summon one creature after the other. Then, these summons ran around randomly. It was a magnificent sight, but... it didn’t make sense!

Is this a trap?

In a life and death battle, this Elementist didn’t dare to be careless. He naturally played very cautiously. A very unprofessional move would need to be analyzed as if it were dangerous. As the say went, there can never be too much deception in war. Trusting what was in front of his eyes would simply be too naive.

The Elementalist carefully neared. Halfway there, Luo Ji finally summoned everything at his disposal. He swiped his mouse in a circle and clicked ahead. All of his summons began marching over. During this process, Luo Ji began adjusting the formation of his summons, while also calming down. His playing became smoother and smoother. Not long afterward, the summons were lined up in an orderly fashion.

The Elementalist saw that the orderly formation and didn’t dare to advance any further. He maintained his distance, waiting for those summons to get closer, so he could rely on his range advantage. The Elementalist threw out a probing spell.

When Luo Ji saw his opponent attack, he didn’t stay idle either and immediately ordered his summons to retreat. However, no player’s offense would just be a single skill. After casting a spell, players would know ahead of time how to follow up. While observing the situation, the Elementalist continued to attack. As a result, Concealed Light’s summons slowly began to become more and more and more and more disorderly.

Luo Ji couldn’t keep up with his opponent’s pace, and he insisted on a specific counter against his opponent’s attacks. He was being haunted by his pursuit for perfection, but because his skill wasn’t good enough, the more he sought perfection, the less perfect it became. In the end, the Elementalist could finally tell that this brother wasn’t some expert.

He saw it. Everyone in Team Everlasting obviously saw it too. Suddenly, the practice room seemed to be filled with celebration. They had won two points in the individual competition. If the match had three obstacles to pass through, they had passed through the first one. However, even passing through all three obstacles wouldn’t determine their victory. The individual competition ended with 2 points to 1. Even if Team Everlasting won both the group arena and the team competition, their point total for this match would be 8.5 to 1. The two sides would be tied and they would need to participate in an additional tiebreaker match.

But in any case, Team Everlasting at least still had hope.　　

The third round of the individual competition ended without any suspense. Team Everlasting easily took the win. Luo Ji was naturally very disappointed.　　

"Compared to that you who wrote guides, you’ve been improved a lot." Ye Xiu messaged.

Luo Ji knew that too, but he also knew that Ye Xiu was just consoling himself. He replied back with a forced smile emoji listlessly.

"For the current you, you don’t need to worry too much about winning. Cherish every battle and continuously work on improving. As you slowly build up confidence and experience, victory will naturally come to you." Ye Xiu said.

"I will." These words lifted Luo Ji’s spirits. He knew that Ye Xiu wasn’t consoling him, but giving him guidance. It might not have been the first time that Ye Xiu said this argument before, but when it was time to implement it, it was easy to forget. A good teacher who gave sincere advice kept this in mind.

When the individual competition ended, the group arena began after a short break. Because neither side had too many players to choose from, it was clear who would be appearing in the group arena.

Team Happy’s side would consist of Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Qiao Yifan.

Team Everlasting’s side would continue to have their experienced ace He An as the general, leading their Warlock and Qi Master in their fight to the death.

Chapter 835: Helpless

The first in Team Everlasting’s line up was their Warlock. In the last round, he had been the the player sent out in the third individual competition and ended up losing badly with a disadvantage in cast range against Windward Formation. After a week, everyone had composed themselves and Windward Formation, the one who had left a scar on his heart last round, had already gone up the individual competition. The last bits of worry in his mind faded, and he brought his Warlock, Leopold, confidently into the arena.

For Team Happy, the first one to fight in the group arena was Tang Rou and her Battle Mage, Soft Mist.

The preparation Team Everlasting had done in the past week was, first and foremost, analyze the reason why they had suffered defeat in the first round.

There was a method to this. Analyzing their defeat was with the goal of obtaining victory in the next round; it was to energize their team. When they analyzed the reason for their defeat, they had to find a way to solve that problem as well.

In their eyes, they had underestimated Team Happy’s strength. Though they had prepared, but both the skills and the equipment of Team Happy were far beyond what they had originally estimated. Especially how some information was useless, like the info they had on One Inch Ash, who had managed to crush one of their team members.

What defeat brought them was priceless experience. In their battle against Team Everlasting, Team Happy was no longer able to wipe the floor with Team Everlasting like they had with their challengers. In a high-end exchange like this, Team Happy’s performance and skill was far more evident.

After their week of preparations, Team Everlasting felt like they finally had an in-depth understanding of themselves and their enemies.

It was through these adjustments that Team Everlasting didn’t fall into despair at the gap between scores. They had to close the gap and retained their competitive spirit.

Now, the individual competition was over. They had lost a point, so this meant that they could, at most, tie with Happy. However, this start was enough to boost their morale.

Soft Mist?　Seeing the character on Team Happy’s side, Team Everlasting’s Warlock quietly ran over everything they had dug up regarding Soft Mist in this week.

Passionate, ferocious, abnormally aggressive, a definite offensive character with technical skill that wouldn’t lose to any pro player. However, it was clear from the details that Soft Mist wasn’t a veteran at the game. So, although she had the hard mechanics down, she wasn’t so familiar with other techniques. Her style relied on using her mechanics to overwhelm her opponent, but she didn’t have much awareness for the situation of the match.　On Team Everlasting’s tactical notes, that was the analysis they had given to Soft Mist. Of course, there were parts about the player behind the character, but since they didn’t know Soft Mist’s real name, they used her character name. As for Soft Mist’s equipment, it also shocked Team Everlasting to the core. They could only get a vague idea of the Silver equipment from one match, but the other Orange equipment she wore had already been thoroughly analyzed. This information was also jotted down clearly in their tactical notes.

Team Everlasting’s Warlock knew how he should deal with Soft Mist.

After the three second countdown, the group arena officially began and both characters spawned into the map. Though Happy had the home field advantage, it didn’t really mean much since they had newbies like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. There probably wasn’t a map that Tang Rou and Steamed Bun would know better than Everlasting’s players.

Steamed Bun’s map had been chosen as the Ring, because any other map and they might be handing the map advantage over to their opponents.

Everyone thought that this choice of Team Happy’s was giving up their advantage, but in reality it prevented them from being put at a disadvantage.　

However, since the group arena only used one map, Team Happy would struggle to take into account both their extremes. So, Team Happy chose Red Flower Pavilion for the group arena. It had some special terrain, but it was definitely not complicated.

After the match began, Soft Mist and Leopold were placed into two opposing corners of the map. In the very center stood the pavilion and around it, red flower petals danced distractingly through the air.

Yet, who would bother to pay attention to the scenery in such an important match? As soon as the match began, both characters started charging towards the center, where the pavilion stood.

Tang Rou, as always, wanted to go head to head in the most direct manner with her opponent. For someone like her, the Ring was a great map. As for Team Everlasting’s player, he might look like he was charging fiercely towards the center, but his mind was as calm as the surface of a mirror. He wasn’t planning on having a direct exchange with Soft Mist; that was something he knew not to do from their analysis.

In an offensive exchange, Soft Mist would only become fiercer no matter if she had the advantage or not. So, against Soft Mist, Team Everlasting had three words: drag it out.

Intentionally dragging it out, both the length of the match and the contents, from the smallest of actions, and finally completely neutralizing Soft Mist.

This was another tactic they had come up with in their tactical notes after their week of prep, written under all the analysis on Soft Mist. If they didn’t execute it, then wouldn’t that be a waste all their efforts this past week?

So, when the characters came into the proximity where Leopold could cast, Leopold stopped his movements decisively.

His casting range wasn’t as far as Windward Formation’s, true, but against a Battle Mage, it was more than enough. This was an exchange between a ranged class and a melee class. Wu Chen’s victory in the first Individual Competition was a prime example of this sort of exchange. Team Everlasting planned to use this same method of taking control of the pace of the match to defeat Soft Mist.　Curse Arrows!　It seemed to early to fire a low stage skill like that, but this was all a part of the tactic that Team Everlasting was using. The dark ball of light hadn’t been charged much before streaking over, splitting into a row of a few black arrows. Yet, at this distance, Soft Mist easily sidestepped.

Whereas he had been charging just as fiercely as Soft Mist before, Leopold immediately started retreating after the skill had been cast. Whichever direction Soft Mist charged, he would retreat in the same direction.

Tang Rou wasn’t too surprised. When a ranged character faced a melee character, they would often kite around them like this. She had enough experience to know that.

No hesitation, Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

This powerful Battle Mage skill had become a way to increase movement speed under Tang Rou’s control. Soft Mist sprinted, spear in hand, instantly closing in like expected. However, just as Dragon Breaks the Ranks ended, hexagram lights flashed and a Hexagram Prison was released under Soft Mist’s feet.　Team Everlasting was a professional team. After analyzing Tang Rou’s simple and direct playstyle, her use of Dragon Breaks the Ranks to gap close on her opponent was within their expectations. Seeing Soft Mist raise her spear, Everlasting’s Warlock was clear on what he had to do. Where Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks would take her, under the circumstances, was something that was naturally noted down in their tactical notes.

Hexagram Prison had begun casting the moment Tang Rou raised her spear to charge.

As Dragon Breaks the Ranks arrived, the skill was unleashed. It was as if the two sides had planned it. The rising pillars of light instantly trapped Soft Mist within.

A skill like Hexagram Prison was mostly used as a zoning method and rarely struck a direct hit. If someone was really hit by a skill like that, then they would be in big trouble.

Without hesitating, Leopold immediately began to cast a powerful skill, summoning Death’s Door. Soft Mist couldn’t possibly escape while encaged by Hexagram Prison. She could only look on helplessly when the dark energy from Death’s Door caught her.　Corrosion Curse, Soul Strike, Soul Slice, Soul Devourer, Surrender Life...

A string of skills activated in quick succession with a hint of vengance. In the first round, Leopold had gotten the same treatment from Windward Formation after being caught by Death’s Door. Now, this combo of offensive skills had been reenacted on Soft Mist by Leopold.

As Death’s Door ended, a storm of Chaotic Rain was summoned.

Warlocks focused on control and Leopold showed off that trait spectacularly in this match. Chaotic Rain fell from the heavens and Soft Mist couldn’t escape, having just been released by Death’s Door. She immediately fell into confusion, losing control of her actions. Leopold continued to fling all sorts of spells, holding the advantage tightly in his hand. The Soft Mist that had managed to break through to the third player of Team Everlasting was now completely helpless.

The audience’s chat instantly became more active.

Not many of the faceslappers returned to watch this match, but there were still some. They were very discreet though, very cautious, not daring to be too openly mocking and afraid that their words would be shoved back into their faces. Yet, in this match between Soft Mist and Leopold, the Warlock was able to display his talents beautifully, stably maintaining the upper hand. The faceslappers had been holding back for a long time. When they saw the Chaotic Rain masterfully link with the previous skills, giving Soft Mist no chance of escape, they couldn’t endure it anymore and erupted!

"Nicely done! A flawless victory!" Someone predicted.

"This is more like it! This is more like it!" Someone madly expressed their impatience to see such a scene.

"Don’t give her any openings! Wipe her out!"

"Well played! Continue this! One versus three!"

It was clear that their eruption wasn’t too crazy. At the very least, no one could clearly tell them apart from Team Everlasting’s fans with their wording.　

Tang Rou was, of course, rather depressed at the current situation. From the Hexagram Prison onwards, her mechanical skill and hand speed became meaningless. She had no way of dealing with the situation at hand. Even now, under the Chaotic Rain, she was still completely helpless.

Chapter 836: Still Need to Practice

It had been a long time since Tang Rou was put in such a difficult state. Within her short experience in Glory, she had only felt this powerless when she fought against Ye Xiu in the beginning and when she had gone up against Wang Jiexi, who had once invited her to join Team Tiny Herb.

However, Tang Rou clearly knew that those two people were far more skilled than her. Her skill level had been low at that time too. Fighting against them was like Tang Rou bullying a normal player.

Until now, as Tang Rou improved and accumulated experience, she thought she wouldn’t be as powerless as before if she fought against the two Gods again. But now, this player from Team Everlasting who she didn’t even know the name of and was toyed around by Wei Chen in the last match, which resulted in Wei Chen laughing at for half an hour, was able to suppress her.

Completely suppressed.

It was like facing Ye Xiu’s unspecialised, or Wang Jiexi’s Magician in the beginning, Tang Rou felt powerless.

Of course, Tang Rou knew the Warlock class was strong at controlling. But if her opponent’s class was the only reason she was being beaten up so badly, wouldn’t this make the Warlock unrivalled? In the professional circle, there were various classes that could oppose Warlocks, including the Battle Mage she was using. Wouldn’t this mean that everyone would be have no power to retaliate when facing a Warlock?

Of course it wasn’t. She needed to find the reason on herself. The reason was because she didn’t fight well in the beginning, which caused her to fall into the opponent’s pace.

Tang Rou was no longer the rookie from before. She had learned to analyze the problems in her matches, and she was pretty accurate in her analysis.

But even if she felt regretful, she couldn’t return to the moment from before. She needed to face her current situation. But after she was drenched with Chaotic Rain, she could only watch helplessly. Her equipment played as a factor in this. The characters in top pro teams would pay a lot of attention to their resistance against abnormal statuses. If they were going against classes like a Warlock, they would definitely adjust their equipments accordingly.

Team Happy didn’t have such conditions, so Soft Mist’s resistance was mediocre. When she faced the Warlock, the skills were already enough to affect her greatly. Now that she was under an abnormal status effect, she was unable to resolve the situation for the time being. For example, when one was facing class based on physical damage, then one would need physical defense; when one was facing class based on magical damage, then one would naturally need magical defense; similarly, when one faced a Warlock, an abnormal status resistance, which was affected by Spirit, was important. Soft Mist didn’t take any precise and directed actions, so part of this played as a reason for her difficult situation. This was why Warlocks used to be thought of as an OP class that broke the balance in the game. But as more people paid attention to their resistance towards abnormal statuses, many players understood that every class simply had their own advantages and could mutually restrain one another.

Tang Rou wasn’t able to think so much at the moment, so she could only find the reasons from herself. When the confusion status effect finally seemed to come to an end, Leopold had already prepared another control skill in advance.

After Soft Mist was trapped by a Binding Curse, another dark, murky wave arrived.

The spectator chat became increasingly lively. Between the two characters, one character’s health line dropped at a rapid pace, while the other character’s health didn’t move a fraction. The face slappers no longer held any reservations or restraints. Some people even started to call out for their companions. A satisfying face-slapping circumstance like this was too good to miss.

The Warlock player from Team Everlasting was also immensely excited. This week’s preparation was timely indeed, the feeling of having everything under his control was great! The more the Warlock player played, the smoother he played, his mind was clear, his technical skill was nimble, and his ability to grasp opportunities was accurate. Among all of this, it felt as if his breathing and heartbeat became one. At that moment, he felt as if he was Leopold, as if he was standing under Red Flower Pavillion while he casted his dark curse.

Under the opponent’s excellent performance, Tang Rou wasn’t able to turn the tables around, Leopold achieved a perfect victory. When Soft Mist fell, what the cheering in the audience’s channel was like goes without saying. The spectators that came to face-slap immediately took over the channel. They were even able to best the fans of Team Everlasting.

All sorts of in-the-face insults and taunts like "The east wind blows, the battle drum sounds, who should Soft Mist fear?" started to overflow the channel.

As for Happy, the atmosphere there was quite nervous.

Everyone had experienced Tang Rou’s eagerness to win. Now that the opponents had gotten a perfect victory out of her, how much mental damage did she take? It was obvious that Tang Rou wouldn’t have a smile on her face. It was as if the word ‘gloomy’ was written on her face. The way she pushed the keyboard back and let go of the mouse showed her unwillingness.

Chen Guo walked over in attempt of comforting her. But... it was true that she lost in an unsightly manner, what good things could Chen Guo think of to say?

At this moment, Ye Xiu opened his mouth to speak. He only spoke five words: "You still need practice!"

So heartless!

Wei Chen nearly failed to restrain himself from reprimanding! The gloomy expression of a beauty losing a match was rather heartbreaking. You b*stard, is that how you comfort people?

Before Wei Chen could ridicule, Tang Rou already made her response. Her reply was very simple, with only one word. "Mm!"

After she spoke, her hands returned to the keyboard and mouse. Chen Guo already turned to her side, preparing to comfort her, but she saw Tang Rou log out of the match. Chen Guo was startled. "What are you planning to do?"

"Practice!"

Chen Guo was between laughter and tears. If she didn’t really know Tang Rou, she would have thought Tang Rou was angry at Ye Xiu’s blunt "you still need practice ", and was peeved to do it.

"The match isn’t finished yet!" Chen Guo said.

"We have to win!" Tang Rou rose her hand and called out loud.

"You don’t say." Ye Xiu replied concisely.

The second to enter the match for Team Happy was Qiao Yifan with his One Inch Ash. His character was already standing on the match’s seat. Tang Rou had left behind a full-health opponent for him, so he felt a bit pressured. However, after hearing the blunt and simple conversation between Tang Rou and Ye Xiu, who had yet to play his round, it was as if he gained courage again.

The second round of the group arena soon began.

Qiao Yifan, One Inch Ash.

Since Chang Xian’s interview had yet to appear in the papers, aside from Team Excellent Era, no one knew that One Inch Ash was played by Qiao Yifan, who had been a part of the pro circle. In addition, he barely came out to fight before, so in the first match, Team Everlasting had little to no information about One Inch Ash. They only knew that this character completed Heavenly Challenge and entered Heavenly Domain at Level 55. Judging from this point, this person shouldn’t have started from the new server.

After the first match of the competition, Team Everlasting only had one conclusion towards Qiao Yifan: Deceitful, very deceitful.

How should they face deceitful players? They would naturally have to be careful, very careful.

Through their analysis, Team Everlasting came out with a beneficial point: One Inch Ash was a Phantom Demon.

Phantom Demon and Sword Demon’s style was completely different, so their basics were something that could be told just by seeing. Phantom Demon would lean towards the team’s support, so their fighting strength in duels was slightly weak. As for this point, it immediately became an important part in dealing with One Inch Ash.

All these were what they knew that were relevant. The Warlock player from Team Everlasting, who defeated Tang Rou just then, was in a stage where his confidence was surging. When he saw One Inch Ash coming out, he silently revised in his mind about this player’s character and characteristics. He already came up with a plan in mind. They weren’t able to predict every opponent they were up against beforehand, so they needed to prepare in advance for any possibility of every encounter. Whether it was dealing with Soft Mist, One Inch Ash, or even Windward Formation and Lord Grim. Throughout the week, every player in Team Everlasting already analysed and discussed about how they should respond. Their preparation for this round was truly adequate.

Three, two, one…...

After the countdown, the match started. The map was still Red Flower Pavillion. Both players controlled classes of the dark powers, Ghostblade and Warlock.

Although both were closing on towards the map’s centre, Qiao Yifan wasn’t as simple and straightforward like Tang Rou. One Inch Ash already started to use any possible covers on the map to his advantage. In the eyes of Team Everlasting players, this was being deceitful!

Qiao Yifan wasn’t proactive in getting closer to his opponent, so the Warlock player of Team Everlasting also didn’t come up proactively. Were they kidding? The sharpshooter of Team Everlasting in the first round fell into One Inch Ash’s trap because he was too proactive. How could they make the same mistake twice?

In reality, such traps would be ineffective for teams made up of normal players. There were too many normal players who lacked integrity. There were no supervisors online, it was very likely that they would be using the bird’s eye view to warn and call out for one another. However, Team Everlasting was strictly following the rules. Until now, the only exception was when He An was fighting in the group arena, someone wasn’t able to refrain and called out once. As for this incident... After that round, no one brought it up again. Team Everlasting ended with their loss in that round, so if they really won, that cry of warning would make them win with an unfair advantage. Even if they were happy about their victory, there would be a shadow in their minds.

Even though the second round of the match was a matter of life and death, from the single matches till now, Team Everlasting didn’t do anything that violated the rules. They only earnestly prepared for a whole week and never thought about using any cheating methods to help them get through that difficult stage.

One Inch Ash and Leopold haven’t confronted for a long time, even the audience found it difficult to restrain themselves. Those who were nervous at this point, were mostly the spectators. The bird’s eye view was able to let them clearly grasp onto both side’s activity. Both side’s various ways of walking and positioning was twisting and turning, so they never encountered.Finally, Leopold quietly turned to One Inch Ash’s side, One Inch Ash was already exposed within Leopold’s area that could cast spells.

"Get rid of him!!" Many spammed in the spectator’s chat.

Chapter 837: Having the Upper Hand

Was it close enough?

Team Everlasting’s Warlock player was more nervous than anyone right now, because according to their research, One Inch Ash was a very cunning person. He had successfully managed to close in on his opponent’s side, but could it be trap?

Leopold didn’t continue to close in or start to cast. Team Everlasting’s Warlock wanted to observe a little more, but Red Flower Pavilion didn’t give much cover. One Inch Ash turned suddenly and Leopold had nowhere to hide, becoming fully exposed in the other’ range of vision.

　

The spectating members of Team Everlasting all let out sighs of regret. They could clearly see, from their omniscient view, that One Inch Ash hadn’t been laying a trap and Leopold had really stumbled on a great opportunity to take the upper hand. However, he was overly cautious, so he missed it.

Upon turning his body, One Inch Ash immediately noticed Leopold was at his flank and hurriedly started to move away. Directly charging at a ranged character wasn’t a good idea, especially ones like Warlocks that had powerful control skills.

His chance was gone. Seeing One Inch Ash’s hurried retreat, Everlasting’s Warlock knew he had missed his chance at grabbing the initiative and was very frustrated. But, he had to be cautious! He then recalled the important points that were repeated brought up on the tactical notes for One Inch Ash. So, he started to wonder again, was this retreat the next step in some scheme?

So, not only did Team Everlasting’s Warlock not pursue him immediately, he even changed direction and took a longer route to close in on One Inch Ash.

The spectating members of Everlasting exchanged looks. They could tell that Leopold was being a little too cautious this round. With this attitude, he would become overly suspicious of his opponent’s actions.

After a while of cautious movement from both sides, their paths crossed once more.

Under the dancing petals of the Red Flower Pavilion, the two characters, both in control of the powers of darkness, noticed that they had somehow come into such proximity with a single turn of the head.

　

This competition had already been going on for eight whole minutes….

The audience was exhausted to the point where they didn’t even have the energy to cheer any longer. Team Everlasting’s Warlock was being extremely cautious, but Qiao Yifan was the same. However, Qiao Yifan’s caution was reasonable. It was better to be close when against a dangerous class like the Warlock. It could be seen from the delight Wei Chen had towards Death’s Hand, which had a cast range bonus of +4, that the increase in this range meant a lot to a Warlock.

Under this background, it wasn’t as if they hadn’t come across each other before. It was just that they both didn’t think it was a good opportunity and retreated.

So, they had traversed the terrain through their own paths for a whole eight minutes. This meeting was coincidental. For the audience, it was even kind of funny, like two people backing up to look for each other, only to back into each other.

Of course, what actually happened wasn’t so absurd. But they were surprised to notice the other, and at such a close distance too.

A chance!

A trap!

That was what each of the players immediately thought.

At such proximity, Qiao Yifan definitely had the advantage.

His cautious movements were simply to find a chance to close in on the other. Now that it had happened out of coincidence, why would he wait instead of taking this chance?

As for Team Everlasting’s Warlock, he had no idea that Qiao Yifan was just as surprised as he was. As soon as he saw that the situation gave the other the upper hand, he immediately believed he had fallen for the other’s trap.

Was his eight minutes of careful circling useless?

　

The Warlock couldn’t help but freak out a little. He didn’t even know when he had started singing the other’s tune.

One Inch Ash was already charging over.

Moonlight Slash!

　

A graceful arc of light sped out in a 216 degrees curve. The dark Phantom Power was already heading straight at Leopold.

Although Team Everlasting’s Warlock was anxious, his hands didn’t slow, hurriedly sidestepping the attack. A Full Moonlight Slash after the Moonlight Slash was a combination both Sword Demons and Phantom Demons were familiar with using. The current One Inch Ash was no exception, apart from how the 360 degrees attack came out at an angle instead of parallel to the ground like with normal players.

　

This was using one’s mechanics to change the angle of the attack. This execution had its own fan-given name, "Slanted Moonlight Slash."

The name was just a nickname made up by players. The damage and other effects of the skill had no change. However, with this slant, the angle of attack would be changed. Leopold may have dodged Moonlight Slash, but he was struck full by the Full Moonlight Slash.

Full Moonlight Slash also had a blow away effect. Leopold was blasted back as the attack landed. On the other side, One Inch Ash raised his sword towards the sky and a purple light flashed. The sky above the sword tip seemed to rip open, and continuous thudding sounds rang out. Several tombstones of varying lengths and heights had fallen from the heavens in this Ghostblade skill: Death’s Tombstone.

This skill was purely a damage dealing skill, but if you were hit by these tombstones, you would be briefly stunned. This was something all attacks did.

The current Leopold was still soaring through the air. How could he possibly dodge the falling tombstones? He was quickly smashed to the ground by a falling tombstone. In the current situation, Death’s Tombstones’ situation control was greater than its damage. After the tombstone that knocked Leopold to the ground, more were still falling. This skill would continue for a while. The knocked down Leopold couldn’t dodge out of range.

Then came a performance of setting Boundaries. He kept chanting, so by the time Death’s Tombstones had ended, One Inch Ash had sent out two Ghost Boundaries already.

Ice Boundary, which did the best in limiting movement, was obviously set. The other boundary was a Plague Boundary, which reduced the defense of the victims inside it.

Leopold was first slowed by the shards of ice that clung to him from the Ice Boundary. Then, the Plague Boundary reduced his defense. Characters that were affected by Plague Boundary took on a hunched over and frail look, struggling to move out of the boundary. It was then that the third Ghost Boundary fell.

Sword Boundary!

Something that enhanced the strength and intelligence of characters on one’s own side.

Strength and Intelligence were two stats that directly influenced damage output. With his opponent slowed and their defense weakened, while his own character had a boost in Strength and Intelligence, it was the perfect time to strike for a Ghostblade.

Without hesitation, One Inch Ash’s blade fell towards Leopold.

Leopold had no chance of fighting back with the Ghost Boundaries. Even if they weren’t there, the level 55 One Inch Ash had once made things very difficult for the level 70 Windward Formation. Warlocks really weren’t good at close combat.

The power of the Phantom Ghost swirled around the blade that continuously flashed and hacked away at Leopold’s life. The three Boundaries disappeared one after the other, but new Boundaries were already there to take their place. When the Ice Boundary disappeared, a Flame Boundary was set. When the Plague Boundary vanished, an Ash Boundary appeared.

The Ash Boundary was a very interesting Ghost Boundary. A character under the effects of an Ash Boundary would have the weight of all the objects on them increased in proportion to the level of the Ash Boundary. A full levelled Ash Boundary could double the weight on a character.

　

As the weight a character had to carry increased, the direct effects included reducing a character’s jumping power and movement speed. The effects on attack speed wasn’t very important to normal players, but at a pro level, not paying attention to these changes and effects could result in losing the match.

Team Everlasting’s Warlock didn’t have the time to calculate this. Having been closed in on by One Inch Ash, he was struggling with or without the Ghost Boundaries. In the first eight minutes, both had been cautiously moving about. They would even part after seeing each other. Yet, this wave of attacks had brought Leopold’s health down, all the way to half in a minute. As for One Inch Ash? Leopold didn’t have the chance to counter. He had just won a flawless victory against Soft Mist, yet now it seemed he was going to be flawlessly beaten by One Inch Ash.

Team Everlasting’s Warlock was definitely displeased. They had managed to make it 3 versus 2, but having the opponent so easily close this gap wasn’t something they could accept. Thinking of this, he suddenly realized something.

That’s right! This was a group arena. Though it was a one on one match, there was an element of teamwork to it, too. He could lose this match, but he had to try his best to create an advantage for his teammates first.

Victory didn’t require the first match to be won, but definitely required the first player to do their best.

　　

Maybe he should’ve been a little more brave in the beginning?

Team Everlasting’s Warlock was a little frustrated. With a three versus two advantage, there had been no need for him to play it so safe! If he had taken the initiative, then maybe the situation would be different.

There might still be a chance, if he tried his best now.

Team Everlasting’s Warlock suddenly calmed, while Qiao Yifan’s performance was, naturally, not to the point where he could mount an offense completely without openings. Soon, Team Everlasting’s Warlock managed to grasp the moment between two attacks. He rolled to dodge the strike and immediately began to cast.

Before, he probably would’ve thought his proximity was too risky, but now his attitude had changed. He had to deal as much damage as possible to give his remaining teammates the best advantage.

Soul Slice!

After that instant cast skill, Curse Arrows were fired without any charging.

　　

Soul Strike, Decaying Curse, Control Curse...

Offensive and control skills were cast by Leopold indiscriminately. Team Everlasting’s Warlock immediately found that feeling he had in the last match, getting better and smoother as he attacked. Having taken that small opening, he instantly counterattacked.

Chapter 838: Apologies are Unnecessary

The sudden wave of counterattacks caught Qiao Yifan off guard. Although he had been a part of the Pro League for a year, he hadn’t had any real battle experience there. He had seen a lot in the Pro League, but he barely had any true experience. With his abilities as a foundation, normal players didn’t stand a chance, but Team Everlasting’s players weren’t so easy to deal with. This opening wasn’t something that a normal player could take advantage of.

In the end, what Qiao Yifan lacked was battle experience from this sort of high-end match. Even in-team matches, letting him practice against the members of a champion level team like Tiny Herb. Yet, practice was still very different from a real match.

　

Qiao Yifan became anxious and hasty after his opponent got the better of him; on the other side, Team Everlasting’s Warlock was doing better and better. He had originally been closed in on by One Inch Ash, but now he was pulling apart their distance as he attacked. But this time, Team Everlasting’s Warlock no longer retreated to an overly cautious distance. After coming to a fair distance away, he stopped moving back. If he stayed relatively close, his attacks would be harder to dodge. Team Everlasting’s Warlock decided to keep the initiative in his own hands, furiously attacking and discarding the caution the tactical notes said he should have when dealing with One Inch Ash.

On the field, tactics and strategy were important, but sometimes it was better if a player did what they felt was right. That was what Team Everlasting’s Warlock was doing right now. He was using his own judgement to create a critical turning point to the match.

On the other hand, Qiao Yifan was unable to steady himself after having the tables turned against him. The more he wanted to take back the upper hand, the more his performance slipped.

Of course, the public chat channel had become extremely active by now. When Leopold was being suppressed by One Inch Ash, no one spoke, but now that the situation had turned, those clenched fists could finally start waving.

Leopold received waves upon waves of encouragement. Even though the players on the field couldn’t see it, the audience could tell that Leopold was linking his moves more and more smoothly, while One Inch Ash’s actions were becoming mechanical, unable to keep up with the pace.

Originally, the audience had the same attitude as Team Everlasting’s Warlock. He didn’t need to win this match, but he at least needed to deal some damage so that the next players could use the advantage. Yet now it seemed that he could use this counterattack to completely wipe out One Inch Ash!

Qiao Yifan had also thought of this. If he lost, then that would mean his opponent had wiped out two people, bringing the situation to a one versus three match. This situation would be the reverse of what had happened in the last round. And in the last round, the one who smiled to the end was Happy with their three to one advantage.

He couldn’t let that happen!

Qiao Yifan became anxious, but he didn’t have enough experience to calm his emotions. His performance was slipping. Instantly, Leopold caught another opening and brought on another wave of attacks. What was even worse was that this opening left him exposed to the Warlock’s control skill. To escape this sort of control, he had to sacrifice a lot, and the cost was something One Inch Ash couldn’t afford.

　

He…. He lost

One Inch Ash fell.

Under extremely favorable circumstances, his opponent had taken a chance to unleash a wave of counterattacks, catching Qiao Yifan off guard and messing up his pace. He never managed to turn the tides again.

.

Two of Team Happy’s players had already been defeated. As for Team Everlasting? Warlock Leopold still had a third of his health remaining. This advantage was even greater than what Tang Rou had managed last round.

"S… Sorry...." On Happy’s side, Qiao Yifan stood with an expression of shame and didn’t look at anyone as he spoke.

　

He was an inconsequential member of Team Tiny Herb, an errands runner. Apart from to his best friend Gao Yingjie, he was a person whose existence didn’t matter. Yet, in Team Happy, a team that couldn’t compare to Team Tiny Herb, he felt special.

This feeling made Qiao Yifan wake up smiling, and he was set on not wasting the attention and care everyone gave to him. Unfortunately, he had slipped up in such an important match. After their opponent had gained a flawless victory against Tang Rou, he should’ve been the one to stabilize the situation since he had more experience than her. Especially under such favorable circumstances, losing the upper hand due to a wave of counterattacks that wiped him out, he couldn’t forgive himself and he didn’t have the hope that his team mates would either.

"Apologies are unnecessary." It was then that he heard that voice. At the All Star Weekend, when he was at his lowest, preparing to give up his career as a pro player, it was this voice that rebuilt the foundation of his confidence.

"Victory is never certain. If you apologize every time you lose, that would be too troublesome," Ye Xiu said.

Victory was never certain, but losing at such a critical moment, wasn’t that a waste of the expectations everyone had in him?

"I did terribly…" Qiao Yifan said.

"Then do better next time," Ye Xiu replied. He was very calm and didn’t seem to mind at all. This manner often pissed Chen Guo off, but here, it helped the worry in Qiao Yifan’s heart disperse.

"Good luck, boss!" Steamed Bun suddenly came out of nowhere with that yell. That was when everyone came back to reality. The competition wasn’t over; they still had Ye Xiu and Lord Grim. If they could pull off a one versus three...

"One against three, can you do it?" Chen asked bluntly.

"Haha." Ye Xiu laughed.

"What are you laughing about?" Chen Guo was pissed off again.

"How is it one against three?" Ye Xiu replied, "It’s just one against two and one third at most."

"Alright then…" Chen Guo admitted that she was wrong. Leopold only had one third of his health left.

"We can do this step by step!" As Ye Xiu said this, his Lord Grim had already entered the arena. As for Team Everlasting, they had just finished a round of victorious cheering. Team Everlasting had been like the audience. They hadn’t hoped for any sort of victory, only that Leopold could deal as much damage as possible. In the end, Leopold manage to win beautifully, and they were elated.

"Nicely done!"

　

"Absolutely wonderful!"

Between matches, no one would stop the players from communicating. Everyone from Team Everlasting had crowded over with all sorts of praise.

"Continue to do well!" In end, this sort of more serious talk was left to their boss, who had personally come to watch.

The third match of the Group Arena soon began.

　

Unspecialized Lord Grim and Warlock Leopold entered the map after the countdown.

Lord Grim!

This was, without a doubt, the focus of Team Everlasting’s preparations. Lord Grim was rather well-known, but unfortunately, recordings of actual matches between him and others were few and far between. In the end, they could only rely on the experience He An, the only one to fight Lord Grim one on one, could share with them.

120 low end skills were what they had to familiarize themselves with when going against Lord Grim. Being who they were, they weren’t unfamiliar with these skills. They could manage to list them out without thinking if you gave them a piece of paper. However, a character with all 120 skills and all their possible combos was something no one had ever seen.

The difference between different classes was mostly shown through the skills. This sort of all new combination was like an entirely new class in itself. In a single week, was it possible to easily familiarize themselves with and figure out how to deal with a new class?

Even without the class, this player...

Although the media said that the person who applied with Lord Grim wasn’t Ye Qiu, the applicant and the actual player was not necessarily the same person.

Violating the rules like this was common in the Challenger League. Ye Qiu was from the Pro League, but who was to say he would be willing to scoop as low as this? Who was to say he wouldn’t?

Team Everlasting didn’t dare, so they had to prepare for the worst.

If this was before, hearing a name like Ye Qiu would probably make their hands cramp up. Now that they were fighting with their backs to the wall, they were all encouraging each other. Those who had willpower promised to topple this god, those who didn’t silently use "that’s not Ye Qiu" to try and delude themselves.

They would, of course, exaggerate the flaws Lord Grim had.

Especially his low damage output, which was something clear from when Lord Grim went up against He An’s Go Forth.

"So, even if it is Ye Qiu, we still have a chance. Don’t forget, our goal is to defeat Excellent Era."

At times like this, Excellent Era had to be mentioned. When compared to this powerhouse, Ye Qiu alone seemed brittle. This comparison was something Team Everlasting was used to making and had lots of practice in making in the Pro League.

"If you perform like you did just now, you won’t have to fear even Ye Qiu. This a competition, and Ye Qiu doesn’t have certainty for victory." Just as the match started, Everlasting’s players gave their Warlock one last round of encouragement and quietly backed away.

As for the Warlock, he in an optimal condition. He decided to continue to use the same tactics as the latter half of the last match, actively challenging his opponent. Even if he lost, he had to take out an equal amount of health from his opponent.

　　

Bring it on, Lord Grim!

Team Everlasting’s Warlock thought to himself, letting Leopold shoot forwards. Soon enough, Team Everlasting’s Warlock saw Lord Grim amongst the dancing red flowers of the map center.

"Lord Grim, do your worst!"

The Warlock player shouted in the chat, feeling his blood pumping and igniting a round of cheers from the audience.

"Coming." Lord Grim’s reply was simple and brisk, because he planned to let his actions speak for him.

　

Three Anti-Tank Missiles were already soaring over.

Do you think you can hit me from that distance? The Warlock player had Leopold easily sidestep, but following that was the continuous noise of a gun firing. Lord Grim closed in even as he shot. The fast movement seemed to have no effect on his accuracy.

Leopold could only keep dodging, while Lord Grim attacked as he closed in.

Yet, on Team Everlasting’s Warlock’s face, there was no anxiety, only the hint of a triumphant smile.

Chapter 839: To Show the Wolf Into the House

Team Everlasting’s Warlock had learned his lesson from the last fight. He wouldn’t face this fight with extreme caution. With a huge lead, he decided to be braver.

Lord Grim closed in quickly?

Of course. He hadn’t put in all of his efforts to stop him. He intentionally let Lord Grim get near. When his opponent reached a satisfactory distance away, he immediately switched up the tempo to catch him off guard.　　

As for Lord Grim, he was closing the distance while attacking. To the Warlock, none of that mattered. Even if you weren’t attacking me to stop me from escaping, I wasn’t going to push you away anyways!

Team Everlasting’s Warlock closely followed Lord Grim. Every step forward was another step towards his ideal scenario.　　

That’s about right.

Finally, the distance between Lord Grim and Leopold had reached a value that the Warlock was satisfied with.　　

At this distance, he could attack or retreat. When he cast his curses, it wouldn’t be easy for his opponent to dodge.

Let’s start with a Bind!

The Warlock had been waiting for this moment, so he naturally had a plan in mind. His attack sequence rolled out without much more thought. He tapped a key and waited for his Bind to be cast, when he heard a gunshot.　

D*mn…...

The Warlock saw Lord Grim’s gun let out a tongue of flame and cursed to himself.

Even though it was just a normal attack, it was timed during his casting, so it would interrupt his Bind.

Warlock control skills were frightening. As soon as you were hit, you would be in their control for a few seconds. If their cast times were instantaneous, they would be too overpowered. As a result, Warlcok curses had cast times or required preparation. At the very least, they wouldn’t come out as quickly as Blade Master or Striker skills.

Bind had a cast time. Even though the cast time wasn’t long, it couldn’t be faster than Lord Grim’s bullet. Helpless, the Warlock had Leopold avoid this shot.

By moving, his casting would naturally be interrupted. Mobile Cast was a special Elementalist skill. Warlocks couldn’t learn it. Being hit by a bullet would have interrupted the casting as well. Moving would too, but at least he would avoid that bit of damage. Anyone would choose to dodge.

After learning his lesson, the Warlock player didn’t choose to cast another curse. Curses that didn’t require cast times had fairly long starting lag, but they could at least be used while moving.

But this time, before he could complete the inputs, a gunshot rang. And this time, it wasn’t just one gunshot, but several in a row. Lord Grim directly let out a Gatling Gun. The bullets flew in a straight line. Dodging wouldn’t be so easy. How could the Warlock have any time to complete his skill?　　

Dodge dodge dodge dodge dodge…...

The Warlock player adjusted Leopold’s position, frantically moving his hands to avoid the endless stream of bullets. It put him in a disadvantageous position.

His opponent was controlling him too well. It seemed like not a single bullet of Gatling Gun’s rapid firing was wasted. This level of skill was above even their team captain Wu Chen!

The more surprising part hadn’t even come yet. When the last bullets of Gatling Gun fired, Lord Grim had already switched his umbrella’s form and began using another skill. It was a skill that the Warlock was incomparably familiar with: Curse Arrow.

A ball of dark energy instantly congealed. The Warlock couldn’t tell if it had been charged or not. From what he could tell, as soon as Gatling Gun ended, a Curse Arrow flew straight towards him.

The dark arrow moved slightly slower than the bullets from Gatling Gun. However, the arrow seemed to be linked together with the Gatling Gun bullets. Even if the Warlock player wanted to block it with his own Curse Arrow, because of the distance between the two sides, he didn’t have enough time to cast it.

Not good!

The Warlock player had already realized that the situation wasn’t good.

This feeling of being unable to deal with incoming attacks because of the distance had been what he had planned to give to Lord Grim, not now, it seemed to be the other way around.

First, Gatling Gun. Then, Curse Arrow. Because of the distance, avoiding them became much more difficult.　

Retreat first? Or should I avoid them and hurry to counterattack?

The Warlock player originally had everything planned for, but at this moment, he had to make a choice.

The incoming Curse Arrow wouldn’t wait for him though. As soon as the ball of light burst open, the skill could be considered as complete. As the Curse Arrow flew, Lord Grim didn’t slow down and continued to close the distance, following behind that arrow.

This isn’t good!

The Warlock player didn’t hesitate anymore. He needed to maintain a distance away from Lord Grim. As a result, he dodged, while having his Leopold retreat.

Bang!

Before the Curse Arrow was completely released, Lord Grim actually fired a bullet to add to the attack.

There was also a bullet alongside the Curse Arrow…...

Besides unspecialized, no other class could accomplish this. The Warlock had been caught off guard and was hit by the bullet. The attack induced a brief hitstun, causing Leopold to also be hit by the Curse Arrow. These were low-leveled skills. And because Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had low attack, the damage dealt wasn’t actually much, but it still struck a blow to the Warlock’s confidence.

The first fight had progressed smooth like butter, all according to plan.

In the following fight, he was like fire and beautifully completed a comeback.

In this Warlock’s Glory career, he had played his very best today. His confidence had reached its peak, so even when facing the suspected to be God Ye Qiu, he didn’t waver or play cautiously. He courageously thought of dealing as much damage as possible to help the players behind him.

But now, he was in at a complete disadvantage. He felt as if his hands were tired. His mind was wavering. It was different from his confrontation versus One Inch Ash.

In that match, his Leopold had accidentally gotten close to One Inch Ash. Being on the disadvantage was normal. But in this match, Lord Grim had come from far away and pushed him into a corner in a very direct manner. Moreover, he was in this situation despite his careful planning and preparation. And now? If he said he intentionally let Lord Grim get closer so he could deal some damage to his opponent, who would believe him?

After their distance closed, he was clearly at a disadvantage! His actions were the same as showing a wolf into the house!　　

And now the distance between them was still closing…..

"Shadow Clone Technique!"

In the match’s public chat, these words suddenly popped up. Despite Lord Grim’s tight pace, he unexpectedly had time to type out these words.

When these four words came out, the Warlock jumped up in fright. At their current distance, a Shadow Clone Technique would be able to reach im. Shadow Clone Technique was an under Level 20 Ninja skill, so an unspecialized would definitely have it.

The Warlock player frantically turned his viewpoint left and right, but all the spectators could clearly see that the instant Leopold turned around, Lord Grim used Shadow Clone Technique.

Too despicable!　

The spectators were having a hard time keeping still. You actually blurted out the name of the skill to bother your opponent. Do you think you’re Huang Shaotian?　　

Even the players in Team Everlasting looked in disapproval! The other side is clearly blurting out the skill name to distract you! You should be paying attention to his movements. You can see when he uses Shadow Clone Technique. What are you looking around for?

That was easier said than done though.

Leopold had been forced back by Lord Grim’s closely linked attacks, so it was hard not to miss something done by Lord Grim. When he suddenly saw Lord Grim suddenly blurt out a skill, he was very worried that the Lord Grim in front of him was a clone.

But naturally, when the Warlock player discovered that there was no one around him, it happened.

Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Double Stab, Falling Flower Palm…..

This Battle Mage combo was something that Ye Xiu could perform with just one finger. But after Falling Flower Palm, he utilized the unspecialized’s feature. After being hit flying away, Leopold was struck by a sword into the air. A sword wave revolved around him at the center. Spellblade skil: Wave Wheel Slash. 　　

After Wave Wheel Slash, the follow ups continued.

24 classes. 120 base skills flowed out from Lord Grim’s hands, shocking everyone. At this instant, the majority of people had forgotten about the outcome of the fight. A single thought popped up in their minds again and again: F*ck, that can be done too?

No player had ever seen such a combo before. Right now, it was being performed by Lord Grim, making them feel fascinated at the novelty of it. At the same time, they hoped to see what more new tricks could be brought out. This lasted up until Leopold’s health bar changed color. Everyone returned to the match.

This was a match. Victory and defeat mattered. Leopold’s health bar was already red. He only had a tenth of his health left. He was going to lose! Ah! You can follow up like that!

Everyone became distracted again.

In comparison, Team Everlasting wasn’t like them. After all, they cared about the outcome of this match. The outcome affected their team and their future. No matter how shocking the scene was, it wouldn’t erase their concerns.　

He’s lost…...

Everyone was already certain.

After Lord Grim closed in, he unleashed the frightening continuity of an unspecialized’s offense. Even though the combo count was sometimes broken according to the system, in the eyes of real players, some of those attacks that weren’t recognized by the system were still combos because they couldn’t be dodged or blocked due to the situation. These types of false combos were even more terrifying than normal combos. Normal combos could be forcefully interrupted. However, false combos relied on the opponent being unable to react in order to connect the attacks.

Chapter 840: Lord Grim’s Flaw

Leopold fell.

At this moment, the spectators felt like they had woken up from a dream. Afterwards, they felt incomparably disgusted because they had actually been enamored by the combo performed by a player that they had determined to reject. For the face slappers dedicated to watching Team Happy fall, it was too disloyal.

The instant that Team Everlasting’s Warlock player saw his Leopold fall, he wasn’t too shocked. He was more puzzled.

He suddenly felt like that fight seemed unrelated to him, especially once Lord Grim closed in on him. Leopold was like a sandbag whose purpose was to get pummeled unable to put up any resistance. He became support for the performer to show off on.

When his character fell, he hadn’t been able to deal a single bit of damage to Lord Grim with his third of his health. This two and a third or three versus one situation looked as if it had been kicked aside easily.

The other Team Everlasting players consoled the Warlock. Next up, the two who would be fighting next used this brief break between fights to discuss ideas. The group arena was also fought as a whole.

Team Everlasting’s second player in the group arena was their Qi Master. He An and his Spellblade Go Forth would act as Team Everlasting’s anchor and trump card for the third fight.

After the two players strategized briefly, He An saw that their Warlock player was still staring into space blankly. He went over and patted his back with a smile.

"You’ve already done a great job." He An’s smile was sincere.

The Warlock player was even more at a loss. He was unable to deal any damage to the opponent. How was that a great job?

He An continued to smile: "In our current situation, Lord Grim’s biggest issue can be fully utilized."

"What is it?" The Warlock player didn’t understand.

"Mana." He An’s smile began to reveal his confidence.

"Mana?" The Warlock player checked his screen. He had already withdrawn from the group arena. His Leopold could not stand on the competitor spot anymore, which automatically placed him in the spectator view. And here, he could clearly see Lord Grim on Team Happy’s side as well as Lord Grim’s health and mana.

Lord Grim’s health was full, but he had used a quarter of his mana.

The Warlock player suddenly realized something.

Even though Lord Grim’s skills were low-leveled skills with low mana costs, but because the damage was low as well, if you look at his total mana consumption for a complete fight, he doesn’t have it better than any other class.

"From the data retrieved from our first round and other simulations, the attack power of Lord Grim’s Silver weapon should be quite low. Even though he has other stats from his other Silver equipment, from an overall perspective, Lord Grim’s attack power is lower than other equipment at his level by a third." He An continued.

The Warlock player nodded his head. In their preparation this week, they had included their conclusions on Lord Grim during their strategizing. When He An once again emphasized this point, the Warlock player was even more clear about it. Lord Grim’s mana consumption wouldn’t be any lower than another class’s. In fact, it would be even higher because his low damage output didn’t only stem from his low-level skills, but also his weapon’s low attack.

Low-level skills required less mana. High-level skills required more mana. There was a balance. However, if the weapon had low attack power, more mana would be required to make up for it.

The Challenger League’s tournament rules were more lax than the Pro League’s. Characters could also bring potions, but its usage was limited. Potions could only be used once. Right now, Lord Grim had used a quarter of his mana against a Warlock with only a third of his health left. Even if he drank the best mana potion in the game, it would only restore 20% at most. For the current situation, it probably wouldn’t be of much use. Lord Grim needed to face two more opponents, who would both be at full health!

"Why did I forget this point!" The Warlock player now understood and became annoyed at himself, "If I had noticed earlier, I wouldn’t have tried to deal as much damage to him and instead tried to waste as much of his mana."

"All of us forgot too, but it isn’t too to realize it now." He An smiled.

The reason that they hadn’t thought about this point before the group arena was because they didn’t think they’d be able to get such a huge lead. After all, even if Lord Grim consumed more mana than other classes, with the help of a mana potion, he had more than enough mana to last against an opponent with a sliver of health and an opponent at full health. Most group arenas were won by just a hair. Let alone a 1v3, a 2v3 was already very rare in the pro scene.

Team Everlasting had admittedly prepared well for this match, but don’t forget that they had almost been 1v3ed by Team Happy, so they didn’t have the confidence to believe that they would be able to obtain such a huge lead. As a result, not too much importance had been placed on Lord Grim’s mana issues.

It was only until their Warlock player 1v2ed and started fighting against Lord Grim did He An suddenly remember.

The fight had already started though. He obviously wasn’t so lacking in competitive integrity that he would remind the Warlock player. In his eyes, Lord Grim didn’t have enough mana to deal with two full health characters. However much mana Leopold could force him to waste would be fine! In the end, Lord Grim had lost a quarter of his mana. It was equivalent to him using up his potion. It was already quite a good result, which was why He An smiled so confidently.

The Qi Master went onto the stage and walked to the competitor spot. He had already talked with He An before. For this fight, his goal wouldn’t be to win, but to drag this fight with Lord Grim for as long as possible and waste as much of his mana as he could. Of course, if he could deal some damage to Lord Grim, that would be even better.

The group arena’s fourth round began.

As soon as the match started, the Qi Master Heavenly Rage went on the attack. The reason was because every class would automatically recover health and mana slowly over time. Of course, during the brief respite between group arena rounds, the status effects on characters would be reset and the character’s stats would be locked. No recovery would occur. But as soon as the match started, the automatic recovery would immediately begin to take effect.

He An was a very careful person. When he talked with the Qi Master, he wasn’t willing to neglect even this small matter. In reality, the automatic recovery was extremely slow. Relying on that recovery rate wouldn’t be enough to last a fight. However, He An was afraid that their opponent would be despicable enough and refuse to fight, so he could rely on his automatic recovery for an hour or two to recover his mana back to full.

Heavenly Rage charged forward.

He An immediately checked on Lord Grim through his spectator view. He discovered that Lord Grim was also running forward to face him head on. Lord Grim didn’t seem to have any intentions on using such a despicable strategy. He heaved a sigh of relief. Once the match began, he wouldn’t give the Qi Master any reminders. He could only quietly watch the match.

In terms of range, Qi Masters only had a few mid-ranged attacks. They weren’t like gunners, who thoroughly relied on their long range. As a result, when he and Lord Grim encountered each other, the first person to initiate should be Lord Grim.

If this was in the past, the Qi Master would have felt troubled fighting such an opponent, but at this moment, the Qi Master was happy. Attacks from far away weren’t easy to hit. If Lord Grim really started attacking from as far away as possible, he might as well not advance and pretend like he couldn’t approach, so Lord Grim would waste more mana.

The Qi Master quietly made his decision. Gradually, he saw Lord Grim’s figure. He approached and sure enough, Lord Grim started attacking from far away.

But the Qi Master wasn’t excited at all.

Bang! Bang bang! Bang bang!!

Gunshots continued to fire, but there was never more than two in a row. Lord Grim was just using normal attacks, and normal attacks didn’t consume mana!

The Qi Master pretended to have his Heavenly Rage dodge, but Lord Grim continued to bang bang bang with normal attacks.

F*ck, are you hunting a rabbit?

The Qi Master was somewhat angry. Lord Grim’s gun was clearly a rifle, which could fire two times in a row. Lord Grim was standing there leisurely at a distance. He would constantly lift his rifle and then put it down. From time to time, he would fire twice for fun. It looked like he was out hunting.

Wouldn’t dragging it out like this be the same as letting him recover mana? The Qi Master saw that his plan wasn’t working out. He might need to continue approaching. However, if he did it half-heartedly, as long as Lord Grim mixed in a few skills with his attacks, he could definitely pretend like he was having trouble getting closer.

As a result, Heavenly Rage charged forward half-heartedly. Lord Grim didn’t continue hunting and also rushed forward.

Skills! Use your skills!

The Qi Master repeatedly prayed. At this distance, Lord Grim should have plenty of skills to choose from!　　

Under this warped mentality, the distance between the two sides became shorter and shorter all the way until even the spectators were dumbfounded.　　

F*ck! Heavenly Rage, are you stupid? You’re at this distance already! Why aren’t you attacking? Are you planning on fighting Lord Grim at such a close range?

Qi Masters had some close-ranged ability, but it wasn’t too outstanding. But for Lord Grim, he had a few long-ranged moves, but when he decimated Leopold from before, everyone could see how terrifying unspecialized characters were at close range. And now, this Heavenly Range could already attack from mid-range, but he was still swaying around like he was waiting to take a beating. This guy... had Team Happy bribed him?

Chapter 841: Mana Consumption

Everyone in Team Everlasting, including He An, who had discussed the plan in detail with the Qi Master, was completely speechless.

Mentality. This was an issue with his mentality. As soon as your mentality shifted off balance, your thoughts might run into a dead end. For example, this Qi Master had determined that unspecialized could attack him first from afar, so he tried to get him to waste mana that way. However, he was too tunnel-visioned on this strategy. When his opponent was clearly within his attack range, he was still waiting for Lord Grim to attack him first.

The spectators wondered whether he had been bribed. It wasn’t too outrageous for that to happen. However, his way of doing so was too unusual. Moreover, this guy still hadn’t reacted. Lord Grim and Heavenly Rage were still moving closer and closer to each other.　　

He An really wanted to slap his teammate awake. It was such a crucial match. How can you commit such a stupid blunder? However, he didn’t do it in the end. He also knew that it was easy to make mistakes at crucial moments. It was because the player cared too much and wanted to win too much.

The distance continued to close. Team Everlasting’s Qi Master suddenly woke up. The previous round had left a deep impression on him.

This distance was how far Shadow Clone Technique could reach. Leopold was unable to escape from Lord Grim, starting at this distance. Leopold was then completely crushed.

The Qi Master finally woke up because of his sensitivity towards this distance. At this distance, he could have started attacking long ago. Even though his goal was to waste as much of Lord Grim’s mana as possible, that didn’t mean he couldn’t go on the offensive. Attacking was also a way to waste the other side’s mana. In addition, there were also opportunities to consume the opponent’s health and mana simultaneously.

Qi Bullet!

At this point, the Qi Master didn’t hesitate to start attacking. Heavenly Rage fired a Qi Bullet. The crowd’s suspicions of him throwing the match were finally dispelled.

The Qi bullet flew out. Lord Grim’s figure flickered.

The Qi Master had committed a big blunder, but his attention was fully focused on the fight. He saw Lord Grim’s flicker clearly.

As expected, Shadow Clone Technique.

The Qi Master had been expecting it and instantly deduced it. Without another word, he put an input. Heavenly Rage’s two palms rose towards the sky. Then, he bent his waist and slammed the ground. A wave of qi spread from his two hands. This attack covered all around him. Whether Lord Grim teleported to to the front, behind, left, or right of him, he would certainly be enveloped by this attack.

However, at this moment, the crowd let out a gasp of astonishment because Lord Grim had used Shadow Clone Technique to get above him, not to the front, behind, left, or right of him.

The airborne Lord Grim looked as if he were about to give Heavenly Rage an attack as he fell. Following aftewards would be a continuous combo. But Heavenly Rage stood up after slamming the ground and his palms faced Lord Grim.

Sky Piercing Strike!

The Qi Master had actually predicted Lord Grim’s movements. He had been prepared for this attack. A ball of qi flew out from his palms towards Lord Grim.

At this moment, Lord Grim raised his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Ka ka and his umbrella split into propellor. Tu tu tu tu, it spun around rapidly, lifting him up. He casually loosened his hand and a grenade dropped onto Heavenly Rage…..

Heavenly Rage was still in the ending lag of his Sky Piercing Strike. He had no way of dodging the grenade, so it exploded on top of his head. The Qi Master wanted to cry. He obviously knew what options an unspecialized had, but he couldn’t react fast enough in the middle of a fight. They had only prepared for a week. How could he have mastered everything so quickly?

He had at least consumed some of his mana.

The Qi Master failed to strike Lord Grim, but that at least gave him some console. Being at ease made it easier for him to keep his mental state in balance, no? As a result, the Qi Master was still fairly calm. He immediately had Heavenly Rage turn around to continue attacking Lord Grim. However, Lord Grim had only used Rotor Wing to switch directions in the air, so he could dodge Sky Piercing Strike. After avoiding the attack, he followed with his own attack. Heavenly Rage’s turn of the body matched it too perfectly. It was so perfect that everyone in the crowd wanted to smack their foreheads.

Lord Grim’s Falling Light Blade struck Heavenly Rage’s forehead…..

A grenade and then a slice to the head. If this wasn’t a game, he would have died twice. Heavenly Rage was knocked down with this Falling Light Blade. He immediately teched it and rolled, but as soon as he got up, Lord Grim’s spear thrust towards him. Circle Swing grabbed Heavenly Range and threw him back to the ground. He fell so hard he didn’t know where he was anymore.

Too pitiful.

Everyone thought to themselves. The current Heavenly Rage had been closed in on just like Leopold! An unspecialized at melee range was too terrifying!

It was just as everyone predicted. When Heavenly Rage got up, Lord Grim’s attack arrived. The Qi Master chose the correct choice this time though. When he got up, he pushed his palms outwards to create a Qi Shield. Lord Grim’s attack just happened to hit this Qi Shield. Borrowing the shockwave from the Qi Shield being shattered, Heavenly Rage slid back several steps. He thought he could pull apart the distance, when Lord Grim carried his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and rushed forward with the Knight’s Charge.

The Charge skill was faster than a character’s movement speed. However, Heavenly Rage had borrowed the resulting shockwave, so his movement speed was faster than normal too. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella charging at him missed him just by a bit. His heart thumped with joy!

Lord Grim didn’t hit him. He had wasted some more of his mana.

But that Charge wasn’t everything. Lord Grim didn’t reduce his speed. A glint of light shined and a sword was unsheathed. A Berserker’s Colliding Stab followed after…..

This time, Heavenly Rage couldn’t avoid it. The sword struck his chest. Colliding Stab’s momentum wouldn’t stop with just that. Lord Grim rushed forward along with the target. It looked like he refused to let go until this sword killed Heavenly Rage.

Ye Xiu didn’t need this skill’s charge effect. When it was about right, he switched skills, not letting the other side any time to adjust before he performed his unspecialized combo.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella constantly switched forms. All sorts of skills from different classes were unleashed at a speed that the crowd couldn’t keep up with. The previous combo that made everyone forget themselves in its beauty reappeared.　

However, with the combo from before, the crowd wouldn’t lose themselves. It was still stunning to see though, even if they didn’t want to admit it.

The other players in Team Everlasting had expressions of horror. If this continued, would Heavenly Rage be killed in this way just like Leopold?

Only He An followed Lord Grim’s mana bar closely. Every point of mana was another point of happiness. He knew that hoping the Qi Master to make a huge comeback wouldn’t be possible. Now it was a matter of how much more mana Lord Grim would use up. Next, it would be up to him to use this advantage and win!

Use a bit more mana!

He An paid attention to Lord Grim’s mana bar, while checking on Heavenly Rage’s health bar from time to time.

The Qi Master hadn’t given up. He was still struggling because he knew that he wasn’t here to win this round, so he wasn’t too troubled by the opponent suppressing him. He just needed to make things hard for his opponent, so his opponent would need to use more skills to kill him.

Qi Masters were also Cloth classes. From their equipments’ stats, their defense wasn’t anything much. But in reality, Qi Masters had far better defensive stats than other Cloth classes because of their passive skill: True Qi Protection.　　

After learning this skill, the Qi Master’s mana directly affected their defense. Their defense would increase proportionally according to their remaining mana.

Qi Masters that emphasized offense and disregarded defense might not use this skill, but the majority of Qi Masters sought consistency, so True Qi Protection would usually be maxed. Even though the effects of the skill would decrease as their mana decreased, the increase in defense was still very distinct.

It was because of this skill that many Qi Masters valued equipment, which improved their mana and mana recovery in order to increase the benefits from this skill.

In the pro scene, few players would specifically choose equipment for the benefit of just a single skill. Pro characters would change depending on their needs.

He An was regretted not preparing for this beforehand. If he had known Heavenly Rage’s goal woud be to waste mana, they would have stacked mana and health on him. It would have been very effective.

Right now, Heavenly Rage could only rely on himself to struggle. But seeing Lord Grim’s mana compared to Heavenly Rage’s health, He An let out a sigh of relief. If this continued, even if Lord Grim’s mana didn’t go completely empty, there should only be 10% remaining. Even if he drank the best mana potion, it would be at 30%.

With 30% mana and Lord Grim’s damage output, He An was confident his Go Forth wouldn’t fall even if he just stood there letting Lord Grim attack him.

Go Forth was a Spellblade. Don’t look at how they dealt magic damage. The health and defense of Spellblades were first class. Among the Swordsman classes, Berserkers only wore heavy armor. Spellblades wore plate armor though, which had the highest physical defense out of all the armors. Spellblades also stacked Intelligence, so along with accessories, their magic defense was very mighty as well.

No matter how many skills an unspecialized possessed, whether it was physical or magic damage, trying to get through a Spellblade would require enormous damage output. And how much mana did Lord Grim have left?

Seeing the situation, He An’s smile grew wider and wider.

Chapter 842: Almost Out of Mana

Heavenly Rage finally fell. In this brave struggle of his, he had managed to deal some damage to Lord Grim, taking a tenth of Lord Grim’s health with him.

However, what was more satisfying was that he knew he had done well to deplete Lord Grim’s Mana.

Lord Grim had drunk a mana potion in this match, the kind with the best effects that restored 20% of his Mana. Yet, by the time he had crushed Heavenly Rage, only 25% of Lord Grim’s Mana remained.

By then, not only Team Everlasting, but even the normal players had noticed Lord Grim’s trouble with Mana. They had realized in this match that Lord Grim’s mana consumption was terrifyingly high.

After all, one versus three was wasn’t rare in the pro circle or the casual one. Especially for players who played casually, the difference between the skill levels of different players was sometimes rather absurd, making one versus three more common.

If it was a sandbag style one versus three beating, there was little need to worry about mana. For Lord Grim, beating Heavenly Rage wasn’t nearly as absurdly easy as hitting a sandbag, but his advantage was absolute. Nearly running out of mana and having only 25% left after ingesting a mana pill under these circumstances showed how inefficient Lord Grim’s mana consumption was.

As the match went on, the audience had made some realizations, too. The reason why Lord Grim consumed so much mana was because his damage output was really quite low. The damage output to mana input ratio wasn’t high at all.

Some of the smarter players, the players who were rather skilled, had guessed Team Everlasting’s intentions from seeing Lord Grim’s mana and the course of the match.

Spellblade Go Forth had entered Team Everlasting’s side of the area. The results of the winning match of the Group Arena seemed to be obvious when looking at the characters on either side.

The players were clear about the Spellblade’s defensive capabilities. If beating a Qi Master required so much mana, then how was it possible to beat a Spellblade with just 25% of his mana left?

Team Happy had fallen into a trap!

The faceslappers who realized this were elated. There was no way anything would go wrong here. They could finally openly mock Happy now, right?

It was just unfortunate that the faceslappers present today were rather few in number. Even they thought that there was no way that Team Happy would lose with such an advantage. Another unfortunately thing was that though the group arena might be in the bag, Team Everlasting had to win the team competition as well to tie. After that, they would have to win an extra team competition to completely win against Team Happy. If Team Everlasting still ended up eliminated, then their mockery would be meaningless.

But why should they care so much now?

Seeing how Team Happy’s failure in the group arena was set in stone after falling for a trick, the spectating faceslappers began to excitedly cheer once more.

He An watched the audience’s mockery with a smile. He didn’t mind the audience’s blabbering. If even they had noticed, how could Team Happy’s experts not? It was too bad for them that they noticed too late.

Seeing the countdown start, He An took a deep breath, composing himself. By the time he had done so, Go Forth had been loaded into the match. The fifth round of the group arena, the winning match, was finally starting.

The map was still the same map. He An believed he didn’t need to do too much planning and preparations. A character without mana was like a sitting duck.

Go Forth wandered around the map, and He An even had the heart to start admiring the scenery of this map.

Red Flower Pavilion, huh?

He wasn’t very familiar with his map. It was rather beautiful, with red petals dancing through the air! However, it didn’t seem to have any special terrain effects. He hadn’t seen Team Happy use the map to their advantage in the previous matches either.

Thinking of this, He An suddenly felt uneasy.　That’s right, he hadn’t seen any terrain advantage from this map yet. Team Happy couldn’t have picked it so carelessly, right?

But… even with the map helping, what could 25% mana do?

He An calmed down as he remembered this. Go Forth walked forwards a bit and could see Lord Grim charging through the dancing red flowers from the opposite corner.

He came rather quickly. It wasn’t unexpected though. It wasn’t like Lord Grim was going to drag it out and attempt to recover mana naturally. With the speed at which he consumed mana, how long would it take for him to recover it that way? He An thought to himself and had Go Forth run over to meet the other.

Spellblades were like Qi Masters, their skills were mostly mid-range attacks. Against an unspecialized, they would usually attack last. However, He An wasn’t at all afraid of this, charging into Lord Grim’s attack range without care.

He An believed that Lord Grim wouldn’t dare use long-ranged attacks to play any tricks with him anymore. That sort of depletion of mana wasn’t something he could afford.

Just as he expected, Go Forth was only targeted by a few normal attacks from Lord Grim upon entering the latter’s attack range. No skills were released.

He An let Go Forth close in with confidence. The audience’s chat channel was a sea of mockery. Seeing Lord Grim in such a difficult position,, they were giving all sorts of ideas on how Go Forth should beat up Lord Grim.

He An, of course, couldn’t see these ideas. His eyes were still glued to Lord Grim’s mana bar, watching it even more closely than Lord Grim’s health bar. But since Lord Grim had only been attacking with normal shots, he hadn’t consumed any mana as of yet.

Normal attacks couldn’t prevent Go Forth’s charge. As soon as he got in the Spellblade’s attack range, Go Forth immediately sent a soul stirring Ice Sword streaking across the ground towards his opponent.

He An was just simply making fun of his opponent!

From this distance, how could a slow skill like Ice Blade hit it’s target? He An was just purposefully wasting a skill, shoving it in Lord Grim’s face that he had the mana to do so, unlike Lord Grim who had been using normal attacks the whole time.

Lord Grim sidestepped it easily, moving forwards and continuing to close in on Go Forth.

You still want to close in? With what little mana you have remaining, what’s the use of doing so? He An thought to himself, but couldn’t let Lord Grim close in fear of becoming a punching bag. So, he attacked once more, sending all sorts of Sword and Wave Formation attacks without care.

Go Forth’s Wave Formations immediately took up a large area of the map, but still didn’t manage to trap Lord Grim. Lord Grim’s movements were smooth and sleek and his knowledge of the range of the Wave Formations was precise, allowing him to slip by them and leave them behind.

Amazing!

Even He An couldn’t help but admit this to himself. His Wave Formation techniques were completely useless against Lord Grim, who slipped by as if they didn’t exist. But so what? Even if you charge right in front of me, can you defeat me?

Earthquake Sword!

Go Forth quickly sent out a strike. This low end skill activated quickly, but Lord Grim still gracefully dodged it, and then finally went on the offensive.

Anti-Tank Missiles!

After a sidestep to dodge the Earthquake Sword, Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s tip opened and fired. Three missiles, aimed at three points, it was a Tri-Shot. With the current proximity, He An didn’t have the time to dodge. Go Forth strained to avoid them, but was still hit by two missiles.

Under the smoke of the explosion, Go Forth was pushed back by the shockwave. The Anti-Tank Missiles that hit him wouldn’t knock his character over, though.

A blade flashed and Lord Grim sped out with a Colliding Stab, catching up with Go Forth easily. With that stab done, a knock-up struck Go Forth and the combos started as he was suspended.

Falling Light Blade!　He An didn’t want to let Lord Grim just show off like that, activating Falling Light Blade even as he was knocked up. Go Forth swerved to the side in mid air, aiming to land a little ways away. Then, a blade flashed; Go Forth’s landing was somehow anticipated by Lord Grim. and a quick Sword Draw sent him flying again.

Slide Kick, Knee Strike.

Lord Grim used the two skills to catch up with Go Forth, not letting him land. Go Forth’s Falling Light Blade was still in cooldown as well and Spellblades didn’t possess so many intricate sword techniques. Both Sword and Wave Formation attacks were imposing and direct, with little finesse. Under such a intricate combo attack, Spellblades couldn’t do much to turn the tables.

Even worse, the current opponent was Ye Xiu, and he was using an Unspecialized with a combo that He An could barely keep up with.

Though Go Forth was helpless under this assault, He An was still very calm. With this fierce wave of attacks, his mana was quickly depleting. Looking at the rate his life was going down at, he knew that 25% mana was nowhere near enough to devour all his health. Let’s see what you can do after your mana’s all gone.

He An was thinking that, but Go Forth was being beaten rather badly. He An’s attempts were all futile, so he started typing into the chat to overcome his awkwardness.

"Is there any use? With that mana of yours, you think you can kill me?" Go Forth sent in the public chat.

"Haha." Lord Grim took the time to reply, but with this laughing response, it was like he was mocking He An, as if what He An had said was dumb.

"You’re still laughing? In a moment, you won’t even have the time to cry. Your mana is almost at red!" He An said. Obviously, the mana bar wouldn’t go red as a warning upon hitting 10% like the health bar would. He An was just pretending to be good natured and humorous, hinting that you only had 10% of your mana left and would soon be helpless.

It was at this moment, that He An suddenly felt Lord Grim’s attacks pause.

An opening!

Was he affected by my words?

He An thought this and his fingers weren’t slow. He quickly used a Falling Light Blade to land, and then jumped back several times. Turning back around to look, he immediately froze in surprise.

How come Lord Grim looked completely different?

That’s right, he was different, because almost all of Lord Grim’s equipment had been changed.

"Haha," Lord Grim laughed again as he spoke, "Gotta change my equipment since I’m almost out of mana."

Chapter 843: Equipment Change Counterattack

Equipment change!

He An didn’t know how to react for a moment. It wasn’t like this was against the rules. Even in the Pro League, it was ok to switch your equipment out whenever, so long as it was in your inventory. With the freedom of switching equipment, it seemed to be very useful for differing situations, but the problem was that too much equipment caused your character’s weight to increase, affecting the character’s jumping and movement.

In the online game, it didn’t really matter. However, in the Pro League, this tiny difference could mean the difference between life and death. So if you wanted to bring equipment into the field, you couldn’t bring too much, or else you’d be dragged down by the weight of the equipment. Usually, characters would carry extra accessories, since accessories were relatively lighter so the weight wasn’t as evident.

But Lord Grim?

He An looked over the equipment on Lord Grim. He was completely different from head to toe. His headgear, shoulderpads, top, trousers, belt, shoes, which one was the same? They had all changed!

This sort of full reequip was obsolete in today’s Glory. You could only find this reckless playstyle in the early days, when players were still figuring out different strategies for Glory PVP.

This had to be Ye Qiu!

He An stared blankly at the completely rearmoured Lord Grim. He felt like only a God who had survived from those ancient times like Ye Qiu could think of a strategy like this. It was far too outdated!

Yet, was there anything impractical about this strategy?

No, none at all...

Lord Grim had already wiped out two members of Team Everlasting and had the upper hand all throughout his exchange with He An’s Go Forth. And this was done under the weight of all that equipment. Since it hadn’t had a visible effect on his performance at all, his strategy was completely viable.　What was the equipment on Lord Grim?

He An’s mouse moved rapidly.

Headgear… There was no need to click into that. This tall, pointy hat was the Great Witch’s Hat, right?

As for the top… There didn’t seem to be a need to look into either. Cloud Flow Battle Robe was something Qi Masters usually wore.

Pants, belt, shoulder pads, shoes, cloak, necklace, badge, etc.　Some were easily recognized, others He An had to move his mouse over them to make sure.

In reality, after seeing the equipment he could recognize, He An had already obtained a conclusion. He knew what the other equipment did without having to look.　Lord Grim’s attire consisted entirely of mana replenishing equipment to help a character endure for longer, especially those that He An recognized immediately; they were all reputable pieces of equipment in game.

After all, endurance was something needed in PvE, which could drag on. As for PvP, the lack of mana was a rare situation. No matter what class, one full bar of mana was more than enough to kill a character.

But now, Lord Grim was using these pieces of equipment that were rarely used in PvP.

It was because his character really was facing the awkwardness of running out of mana.

He had been prepared!

He An realized that now. Since the participating characters had to be prepared before they gave in the lineup, these pieces of equipment couldn’t have been added when Lord Grim realized he had to fight three people. From the individual competitions onwards, Lord Grim had been carrying the equipment and would continue to do so all the way through the team competition.

Yet, would there still be a team competition now?

Lord Grim’s mana was replenishing at a visible pace and he wasn’t impatient anymore at all. He An didn’t have his Go Forth attack either; he just stood there casually.　He couldn’t let this drag on!

He An suddenly returned to reality.　Even if he had a set of mana replenishing equipment, his mana would still be consumed faster than it could recover in a fast paced match. He should press on, keeping Lord Grim’s mana at the brink of being used up. If he didn’t hang onto this advantage, how else could he win this opponent.

Thinking of this, He An didn’t dare dawdle. Go Forth hurriedly charged forward, sending out Sword and Wave Formation skills. This time, he didn’t do it to show off the amount of mana he had, he really wanted to hurry and suppress Lord Grim.

The current Lord Grim wasn’t as strong as he was before! That was what He An told himself. Lord Grim currently only aimed for mana recovery, even having Purple equipment on him. As opposed to the combination of Silver and Orange he had before, the stats of his current equipment definitely weren’t as good as before.

But He An soon realized that he was still helpless against Lord Grim.

Lord Grim’s equipment may have fallen by a grade, but the player behind him was above He An by who knows how many grades.　He An thought that Lord Grim would use this set of equipment to restore some mana before switching back to the stronger set and mounting an offense. He hadn’t thought Lord Grim would actively attack with this set of equipment.

However, this wave of attacks wasn’t nearly as overwhelming as before. It seemed like he was casually sparring, so He An wasn’t losing too badly.

Yet, during this exchange of blows, He An’s heart ached when he saw the other’s mana keep rising. If this continued then it was all over! If he lost this round, Team Everlasting and the futures of their team members would be in jeopardy.

He couldn’t lose!

He An’s fighting spirit roared. His hand speed erupted. Grasping onto an opportunity, he let himself tank the damage and did a tri-wave attack, sending out three Sword skills at Lord Grim.

Lord Grim didn’t waste any time either, lifting his gun and shooting. Amidst the gunshots, his character leaped backwards. He was using Aerial Fire to retreat.

He An’s magnificent counterattack had only just started, when it ended with the opponent’s retreat. Lord Grim had Aerial Fire and Shadow Clone and Rotor Wing. His retreat was just as skillful as his combos.

He An really wanted to cry. His burning spirit petered out . He really didn’t know how to deal with this opponent anymore. Though he knew he had to keep close to Lord Grim, the other managed to get away so easily. This made him realize that keeping a hold of Lord Grim was just as difficult as escaping from his control.

How hard was it to get away from Lord Grim after he decided to stick to you? He An had experienced it in the last round, and after today, their Warlock and Qi Master could answer that question for everyone as well.

While He An was over here in a sticky situation, the audience had exploded.

Lord Grim had changed equipment under their eyes. Just the speed at which he switched out equipment could show how skilled he was. As for the equipment he had switched into, like He An, the audience knew what he was planning after a few glances.

What a dirty move, to have brought mana replenishing equipment from the start!

As the side that opposed Lord Grim, no one would think that Ye Xiu was sagacious for thinking of this strategy. He was just playing dirty.

The faceslappers were cursing all over the place in the chat channel, while Everlasting’s fans were terrified. They were the the ones who really cared about the results of this match. Seeing Lord Grim come up with this, they realized that Team Everlasting’s plan had become futile. Now how would He An deal with Lord Grim?

The scene in the match ruined their confidence in He An.

He couldn’t beat him or trap him. This match raised the hopes of Everlasting’s fans high and then smashed it against the ground.

He An hastily tried to get Go Forth to find a chance and attack. Everyone could see by now that he was a mess. Go Forth’s attacks still had a method to them, but they had lost their sense of direction. He An was improvising. As for Lord Grim? He was calmly dealing with He An’s attacks, occasionally counterattacking. His counterattacks weren’t fierce and everyone knew this was purposeful. Lord Grim’s mana bar was slowly filling up even as he fought. This sort of thing would rarely happen even if you wore a full set of mana replenishing equipment. Lord Grim was keeping a very slow pace for himself. Yet even at such a pace, He An couldn’t obtain any sort of advantage, It was as if he was a huge wave and Lord Grim was a piece of driftwood. No matter how tumultuous he got, that piece of driftwood would never sink.

Under this rhythm, Lord Grim’s mana was pulled back to half full. Everyone knew that Lord Grim wouldn’t draw this out for lo nger than he needed to. He was waiting for when he had enough mana to launch a counterattack.

Everyone knew this.

That included He An.

However, he had no way of dealing with this. Helplessness coiled around around him. He started to remember how he started playing Glory, how he worked so hard in improving his skills yet never had an opportunity to show them off, how he was discovered by the eliminated Team Everlasting. He had wanted to climb to the top, but was his journey about to end here?

Yes, it was.

As soon as his mana hit 50%, Lord Grim’s pace changed, turning to the offensive. He An, who was unable to compose himself any longer, was quickly and completely suppressed. It was Go Forth who became a tiny boat amidst the raging waves, but this boat wasn’t stable. The waves were smashing it, making it creak and bringing it onto the verge of being torn asunder.　　It was over...

He An’s complexion went pale. His hands were still moving, but his mind was blank; he didn’t even know what his hands were doing.

Glory!

As the word flashed on the screen, He An’s hands left his keypad and mouse and he buried his head into them. His palms felt wet; he was crying.

It’s not that I don’t want to try, but I really can’t win!

Chapter 844: Finally in the Papers

"Win!"

The moment Go Forth fell, Chen Guo immediately jumped up in excitement. This time, she had known about Ye Xiu giving Lord Grim mana recovery equipment, so when she realized Team Everlasting’s strategy against him, she looked forward to the results.

Sure enough, Ye Xiu didn’t disappoint her. He switched his equipment, slowed down the pace of the match to recover mana, and then counterattacked to defeat his opponent in one go. The second round of the match could be considered over at this point. By winning the group arena points, even if Team Everlasting won the team competition, they wouldn’t be able to turn the situation around. This was the so-called match killer.

"Calm down. It’s just the second round that’s over." Ye Xiu saw Chen Guo’s excitement. Even though he said that, he still had a smile on his face.

In the crowd, the spectating face slappers had quietly left. In reality, it proved that those who decided not to come were very wise. Was an 8.5 to 1 point lead so easy to come back from?

The face slappers ran away at top speed as if waiting even a second longer would result in their faces being slapped. The remaining crowd members were the few actual fans of Team Everlasting. All of them were dejected. They didn’t know what Team Everlasting would do next, but from their understanding of how pro teams operated, it would be hard for their team to continue.

Silence filled Team Everlasting’s practice room.

He An’s head was still buried in his two hands. He felt like he couldn’t show his face to his teammates. But at this moment, who would go up and blame him. This result wasn’t because of any one person’s mistake, but rather the collective mistakes of the team, which ended in their tragic elimination from the Challenger League.

Would Team Everlasting stop here?

Everyone was quiet. From time to time, they would glance at their boss, who would be deciding the fate of the team.

Team Everlasting’s boss was naturally very disappointed and grieved. However, he knew that every member of team was also feeling down, especially Wu Chen, who had never abandoned Team Everlasting starting from the pro scene. His feelings towards the team might be even deeper than his own.

As the boss, he knew that Wu Chen had received invites from other teams, when Team Everlasting had been relegated. But in the end, he stayed. However, the results were disappointing. He wasn’t able to return back to the pro scene with Team Everlasting. He would even have to personally witness Team Everlasting’s disbandment.

The boss sighed. He wanted to say a few words to console everyone, but at this point, trying to comfort He An would be fruitless. No matter the result. It had to be faced head on.

"Everyone’s worked hard... today, go to bed early..." The boss said and then left.　

He might have said go to bed early, but would anyone in the team be sleeping tonight? The boss himself let out a long sigh after leaving. Starting from tonight, he probably wouldn’t be able to get a good rest for a long period of time.

Winning and losing came with happiness and sadness.

At City H, there was one other person excited about Team Happy’s victory.

"Happy won!" Chang Xian had gone to watch the match. The instant Go Forth fell, he ran out of the room shouting wildly.

"Cough..." Cao Guangcheng, who had been drinking beer while watching the big screen, choked because of Chang Xian’s sudden shout. Beer spilled everywhere. Just when he was about to curse angrily at him, he saw Chang Xian flipping through the material that he had prepared last week. He didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

"An 8.5 to 1 lead, isn’t it normal for them to win? Is there a need for you to be so excited?" Cao Guangcheng wpied the beer that he spat out as he spoke.

"I can send out my draft now, right? Let me see if there’s anything I need to revise." Chang Xian said.

"I recommend that your article not be too long. Even though it’s an upset, it happened in the Challenger League, so its value is only so much. It’s best for the article to have less content, more news." Cao Guangcheng said.

"Teacher Cao, could you help me take a look then?" Chang Xian asked.

"Sure!" Cao Guangcheng actually quite liked this eager newbie Chang Xian. He would do his best to guide him. Looking over his draft took only a slight effort. Of course he wouldn’t refuse.

With so many years of experience, Cao Guangcheng reviewed the draft very fast because he knew how to see the important points. After skimming over his draft, Cao Guangcheng nodded his head: "Good. The member introductions are quite good, but the later parts related to the match could be more brief. Just going over the course of the match like a clickbait article is fine."

"Oh, okay let me revise it." Chang Xian respected his senior, Cao Guangcheng, and didn’t object any of the suggestions.

As for Cao Guangcheng, who was holding his beer, he was a bit distracted. After seeing the interview material that Chang Xian got last week from Happy, from the their player backgrounds, Cao Guangcheng had become aware that Team Happy had much more to talk about than those relegated teams.

Those relegated pro teams really didn’t have too much to talk about. But for a team like Happy, if they really did have the strength, there was a lot of topics that could be discussed. The existence of this type of team was a pleasant surprise. Unfortunately, this season’s Challenger League had another big surprise: Excellent Era.

With Excellent Era keeping watch, would Happy be able to continue surprising everyone all the way to the end? Cao Guangcheng smiled bitterly. This was fate! Sometimes you might not admit it, but there was no other way around it. If this was any other season, a grassroots team that could defeat a relegated pro team might have made it to the front page. But this season, getting onto the front page might need them to go further. Perhaps when they encountered Excellent Era, they might be mentioned in the front page as loser to be pitied?

The experienced Cao Guangcheng had plotted out the attention that Team Happy would get this season.　　

The night of joy and sorrow soon passed.　　

Cao Guangcheng’s prediction was on point. After Team Happy eliminated Team Everlasting, a grassroots team defeating a former pro team was worthy of being reported.

　

A complete report on Team Happy had finally been published in the Esports Home.　

Even though it had been published on an ordinary page and only took up space about the size of a chunk of tofu, it was a report dedicated to them. In the history of the Glory Pro Alliance, no non-pro team had ever obtained this type of report. The Challenger League had been nicknamed the Revival Tournament because up until now, no non-relegated team had ever entered the Alliance through the Challenger League.

The Esports Home’s professionalism, authority, and influence was shown here. After Team Happy’s report in this week’s issue, the amount of attention that they received was far greater than what they had received through Chen Guo’s free Internet event. Chen Guo’s promotion had attracted a bunch of face slappers too, and then a bunch of face slappers who wanted to face slap the face slappers. Team Happy had become an important topic among these two groups. The support for Team Happy was similar to the faceslappers who supported Team Everlasting those previous two rounds. It was temporary and fake. They wouldn’t feel bad about Team Everlasting getting relegated at all.

The attention received from the Esports Home report was relatively positive. Many players who didn’t care about the Challenger League now knew that such an interesting team had been hiding there all along. When they saw the introductions on the team members, it wasn’t just normal players that were amazed.

"Qiao Yifan?"　

Although Qiao Yifan was invisible, he had only left Team Tiny Herb three months ago. Team Tiny Herb’s players wouldn’t forget someone that they had seen everyday for a year so quickly. When they saw this name, they thought they had mistaken the name, but they soon clearly saw how the name was written. It was the Qiao Yifan that had been kicked from the team.

"That fellow ran to this team?" eam Tiny Herb’s members discussed. They didn’t care too much about Qiao Yifan, but they were still curious.

"What’s all this commotion so early in the morning?" Someone’s voice came from the practice room. Everyone immediately returned to their seats. An Esports Home paper was left on the table, where everyone had dispersed from. It was on the Challenger League page.

Wang Jiexi went up and picked it up. He soon saw what everyone had been discussing.

Qiao Yifan. That kid had ran to this team? That’s a good choice! Wang Jiexi thought. He couldn’t help but think of that phone call he personally received from the manager, asking about Qiao Yifan. He didn’t deny Qiao Yifan’s talent, but he was certain that Qiao Yifan wasn’t a player that Team Tiny Herb needed right now. Wang Jiexi didn’t ask further about the reason for that phone call. But after seeing Qiao Yifan at Team Happy, he approved of his decision.

Wei Chen???

Following afterwards, when Wang Jiexi’s gaze swept over the rest of the article, he noticed this name. Wang Jiexi had become a pro player his third season, right when Wei Chen had retired that season. Even though he had never interacted with this former God, it wasn’t like he had started playing Glory in season three. Before his pro career, he had known of Wei Chen’s fame.　　

"How old is he now? He’s also gone to Team Happy?" Wang Jiexi lifted his head and thought about it. Then, he saw Gao Yingjie sitting in front of his computer in a daze.

Gao Yingjie soon noticed the captain’s gaze and froze in fright.

"Sorry….." Gao Yingjie said and immediately went back to practice.

"Work hard!" Wang Jiexi obviously knew why Gao Yingjie had been distracted, "When you meet again, it’ll be on the stage."

Chapter 845: A 1.4 Unit of Difference In Cast Range

Wei Chen’s name only stunned Wang Jiexi because he questioned Wei Chen’s age. The two had never met each other before, so Wang Jiexi didn’t think too much about it. However, the significance of Wei Chen’s name was very different for Team Blue Rain.

The latest weekly eSports paper was laid on the table. All of Team Blue Rain gathered around to look at it, but no one stopped them, because everyone was lost in thought.

For Team Blue Rain, even young fellows who had a large age difference with Wei Chen like Lu Hanwen, had heard of Wei Chen’s name. Wei Chen was a part of Team Blue Rain’s history, and established the foundation of Team Blue Rain. The two Gods of Blue Rain had ties with Wei Chen.

Captain Yu Wenzhou had inherited the character Swoksaar, which was a character Wei Chen brought from the online circle to professional circle. Although he left, his character stayed and became an important member of the shining generation of stars.

Moreover, Huang Shaotian was discovered by their first captain Wei Chen and brought into Team Blue Rain’s training camp to be trained as an official pro player. Speaking of which, his relationship with Wei Chen was even more complicated. It could be said that if it wasn’t for Wei Chen, they wouldn’t have had the Huang Shaotian they had today.

"Why did Boss Wei go there?" Judging by how Huang Shaotian addressed Wei Chen, the other players could tell Wei Chen had a special position in his heart. To address someone as "boss" showed respect without creating too much distance. Neither the current captain of Team Blue Rain, Yu Wenzhou, nor the second captain, Fang Shijing, were addressed in such a way.

"Could he have contacted Ye Qiu after Ye Qiu retired? Did Ye Qiu invite him to join him in his return to the scene?" Yu Wenzhou predicted. They had little information, but Yu Wenzhou was certain that it was related to Ye Qiu.

"Were those two friends?" Huang Shaotian asked in return.

Yu Wenzhou was startled. At that time, both Huang Shaotian and him weren’t official players yet, they had only been newbies in Team Blue Rain’s training camp. It was the early stages of the Pro League, so the Club wasn’t as regulated as it was now. The difference in status between the pro team and training camp was not so obvious. Everyone was like a family, so even though they weren’t in the system, both Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian were pretty clear about the team’s situation at the time.

"In my opinion, not only was he not friends, he hated Ye Qiu to the bones. I remember that we were eliminated in the season one playoffs by Excellent Era. After that match, Boss Wei cursed Ye Qiu for about half an hour, right?" Huang Shaotian recalled.

"I think that happened." Yu Wenzhou nodded.

"And now you’re telling me that those two have ganged up together?" Huang Shaotian asked.

"It’s probably because... he also felt unresigned." Yu Wenzhou sighed.

Huang Shaotian was at a loss for words. When Wei Chen retired, it was quite pitiful. Team Blue Rain had a serious slip in their performance in the season two, and he wasn’t able to bring out the skills he should’ve had into play, so many people thought he was getting old. In addition, he unexpectedly lost to Yu Wenzhou three times in a row in the team’s training camp. Even though a match where the senior gives advice to the newbies shouldn’t be taken seriously, Yu Wenzhou wasn’t someone like Huang Shaotian, who was confirmed to become their future ace player. At that time, he was regarded as a member who didn’t have any talent.

It was inevitable that such a loss would bring about various kinds of rumors in the club. This was why Wei Chen decisively retired at the end of that season. From that moment onwards, he no longer stayed in contact with the pro scene and vanished without trace. But now, six years had passed, it came to everyone’s surprise that Wei Chen’s name would appear on the eSports weekly news. Could it be that he spent those six years cut off from the world just to practice hard?

"I must see Boss Wei’s current skill level!" Huang Shaotian was the first to leave the crowd and looked for a computer to search up Team Happy’s matches. It wasn’t likely for Team Blue Rain to check on the Challenger League.

When Huang Shaotian left, everyone followed along. Yu Wenzhou watched from the back. They still had an official match tonight! It wasn’t good that everyone was focused on the gossip. But if he forcibly stopped everyone from paying attention to the gossip, it might produce the opposite result, as everyone will find it difficult to concentrate. This was why he didn’t stop them and allowed everyone to join in the fun. As for Yu Wenzhou himself, he quietly stood on the side while he watched Huang Shaotian use the computer.

"I’ve got it!" Huang Shaotian was swift with his actions, and he soon found the recording of the match between Team Happy and Team Everlasting. There were too many teams at the early stages of the Challenger League, so the authorities wouldn’t record and organise the videos. What Huang Shaotian found was by searching for VODs posted online by the spectators.

The video included the entire first round of the competition. Huang Shaotian originally wanted to find the fight with Wei Chen’s Warlock, but in the first match’s first round, he noticed the character: Steamed Bun Invasion. He knew this guy! Wasn’t this the idiot who asked him for his horoscope? Huang Shaotian immediately took interest, so he didn’t move and just watched the match.

After watching for a while, the players of Team Blue Rain, including Huang Shaotian, showed surprise. After they inspected further, Huang Shaotian was the first to confirm, and immediately laughed out loud. "He’s an idiot as expected! He couldn’t even find the way, hahahaha, so stupid."

When everyone listened, they casted sidelong glances at Huang Shaotian one by one. A player asked at once. "Huang Shao, you know this person?"

"Cough, why would I know an idiot like this guy." Huang Shaotian hurriedly fast-forwarded the match. However, Huang Shaotian personally wanted to see if Steamed Bun Invasion had any moves in the end, so he fast-forwarded and played, fast-forwarded and played. This happened until the very end, when Steamed Bun Invasion was actually beaten to death like that.

"F*ck!" Huang Shaotian cursed.

The other players casted sidelong glances once again, as they thought, what on earth was he doing?

One Inch Ash was the player for the second round.

"That’s the guy from Team Tiny Herb." Someone immediately recognised him, it was mentioned on the report after all! To have a player that originated from Team Tiny Herb was rather eye-catching.

As a result, Huang Shaotian didn’t fast-forward the match, while everyone appreciated Qiao Yifan’s performance. Huang Shaotian’s comment in the end was: "Both sides are very professional huh."

Everyone immediately understood. All the spectators with the bird’s eye view would definitely know about Qiao Yifan’s arrangement. But Team Everlasting’s player still fell for it, which meant that none of the other teammates had warned him. Achieving this under the regulations in the Challenger League meant that the team demonstrated good sportsmanship. But on the other hand, even if one was warned, he needed to dodge it on his own. Otherwise, if a player predicted everything through warnings, it would draw out a lot of suspicion. The opponent had the right to report and send a recorded video of the match to come to a trial. If it was too obvious, was discovered, and failed to pass through the trial, the team would be punished accordingly.

After this match, following Team Blue Rain’s expectations, Wei Chen’s Windward Formation finally went on stage.

Windward Formation’s opponent was coincidently Leopold, the Warlock from Team Everlasting. One’s fundamentals would show most prominently when fighting against another of the same class.

The spectators were all pro players of Team Blue Rain. Was it necessary to say who they were leaning towards? No one hoped for Leopold to do well from the very start. The results also met their expectations. Windward Formation was basically able to deal with Leopold however he wanted.

"Tsk tsk tsk, too cruel, he’s totally playing with him! Boss Wei is still so... like that!" Huang Shaotian said.

Everyone straightened their ears! Among the players of Team Blue Rain present, only Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian had directly been in contact with Wei Chen. It was needless to say that they hoped to get gossip out of their captain. Even though Huang Shaotian was about to reveal some information, he blocked out the keyword. Where did his usual, endless, talkative character go?

Due to Huang Shaotian’s personality, despite being the ace player in the team, everyone was accustomed to him, so someone immediately pointed out the crucial point. "He’s still so what? What is ‘that’?"

"Cough!" Huang Shaotian coughed deeply and didn’t reply.

Everyone watched Windward Formation completely torture Leopold in laughter, and no one really took the match seriously. Only Yu Wenzhou watched attentively and interrupted. "Windward Formation had a clear advantage in his casting distance! Take a look at his equipment."

Everyone present was no amateur, they just didn’t notice. When their captain said so, they soon realised as well.

They could also check a character’s equipment through the replay. When Huang Shaotian shifted his mouse forward, the first equipment was Silver. The stats of the Silver equipment was hidden, so they couldn’t see it. But Huang Shaotian was surprised and cried out loud. "Not bad! There’s Silver equipment!"

They continued to check the other equipment. Every player present was paying attention to see if there were any equipment for casting distance until they reached the weapon.

"Hey, the weapon is also Silver!" Huang Shaotian was surprised.

"It seems like it comes from this weapon." Yu Wenzhou said. He was obviously incomparably familiar towards Warlocks.

"This casting distance..." When Huang Shaotian started to pay attention, his skills in observation and judgement were rather astonishing. "It’s two units less than Swoksaar’s isn’t it."

"But his other equips are inferior!" Yu Wenzhou said.

Huang Shaotian understood what he meant. The weapon was not the only equipment that could increase the casting distance. Compared to what Windward Formation had at the moment, there was a lot of space for improvement. It was needless to imagine how much Windward Formation’s casting distance would increase if Windward Formation had Swoksaar’s equipment because it could be calculated. After all, Windward Formation’s set of equipment mainly consisted of orange equipments, which there were stats for. In fact, if one were to mix and match equipment like this, it was very easy to expose the stats on a piece of Silver equipment. Huang Shaotian had a rough idea of the stats of Windward Formation’s Silver equipment. He believed that Yu Wenzhou would only be clearer.

"It would be 1.4 units farther!"

Exchanging Swoksaar’s equipment was only what Huang Shaotian imagined. But Yu Wenzhou was able to directly come up with the results.

This would mean that if Windward Formation kept his Silver weapon but exchanged everything else with Swoksaar’s equipment, his casting distance would exceed the Alliance’s number one Warlock by 1.4 units.

This 1.4 difference in casting distance could be a deadly advantage that determined life and death in a high-level match.

This was a true Death’s Hand!

Chapter 846: Taking Advantage of Someone’s Misfortune

"I’ve seen some amazing things from this match!" Yu Wenzhou commented on Windward Formation’s fight that round. As for Wei Chen’s skill level, Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian had personally experienced it for themselves six years ago. At that time, the two had still been young trainees. Now, the two were famous Gods in the Alliance. Wei Chen was already thirty something years old. In the pro scene, he would absolutely be the oldest player in the league. The two Gods tacitly agreed not to make any comments on their senior’s current skill level.

That fight unsurprisingly ended in Windward Formation’s victory. Everyone’s gossip craving had been satisfied, and were prepared to leave. The match recording had removed the waiting time between matches and the group arena competition soon followed. The first player to come out for Team Happy was Soft Mist.

The eyes of the Team Blue Rain players suddenly lit up. The ESports Weekly had reported that the player controlling Soft Mist was Tang Rou, a very beautiful girl. Even though there was no picture, the ESports Weekly was a reliable news source, unlike tabloids that made things up just to attract attention. If the ESports Weekly dared to make such a claim, this sister must be stunning.

"Hot girl! Hot girl!!!"

The Team Blue Rain players hollered. The ones, who were just about to leave, immediately turned back. Their enthusiasm seemed to explode even more than when they had watched their former captain play. Someone even started ranting how their team’s greatest failure was that they had no girls on their team.

That was certainly a true fact. Of the traditional four powerhouses, Excellent Era, Tyranny, Tiny Herb, Blue Rain, only Team Blue Rain had never had any female players. Tyranny and Tiny Herb might not have any girls as a part of their main roster, but they were still there. Excellent Era was even more mighty. The number one most beautiful female player in the Alliance was on their team. When this was mentioned, who knew how many players were jealous of them!

"I say this is good enough. We have a match to play tonight. Everyone go practice." Yu Wenzhou saw that their gossip was never going to end and finally couldn’t bear it any longer. He spoke up to stop this from continuing.

As soon as they heard their captain speak, they didn’t dare say anymore rubbish. They clicked their tongues and returned to their seats. Huang Shaotian still had the match playing on his computer. He turned his head and said seriously: "This sister’s skill level is quite good. She might be a formidable enemy in the future."

"We’ll worry about it when the time comes!" Yu Wenzhou said.

Huang Shaotian also complied to his captain’s orders. He closed the recording of the Challenger League match that they originally wouldn’t have cared about and also started the practice adjusting their mentality before today’s match.

In the pro scene, it was mainly Team Tiny Herb and Team Blue Rain who had the biggest reaction towards the ESports Weekly. Their reason was obviously because two of their former team members were now part of Team Happy. As for the other teams, when they saw the news, they didn’t pay too much attention to it. It was only the second round of the Challenger League. Regarding Team Happy as an imaginary opponent would just be avoiding their important work, no? The Alliance still had nineteen other opponents that they needed research to be done on! Even more so, the Challenger League had Team Excellent Era. If they had to study a team from there, shouldn’t they be placing more importance on Team Excellent Era?

This was the helplessness Cao Guangcheng thought Team Happy would experience. Even though their team’s strength’s was extraordinary and had much to talk about, they would always be treated as a passing traveler because of Team Excellent Era’s monstrous existence. In the pro scene, no one would pay too much attention to them. As for the player base, after some fervent discussion, they would also feel sorry for Happy because of Excellent Era. In reality, even those who stood by Happy because they wanted to see those face slappers fail wouldn’t bet on Happy beating Excellent Era.

But Team Excellent Era themselves didn’t feel as relaxed as those spectators. Team Happy beating Team Everlasting with ease two rounds in a row forced Tao Xuan to ponder things over. Should they be more vigilant towards Team Happy?

Tao Xuan’s thoughts weren’t on his own team. Excellent Era had encountered two player teams as their opponents. There wasn’t really anything to say. However, Happy had been tested by Everlasting. It would be idiotic if Tao Xuan didn’t take notice. More importantly, the two teams were playing in a you die I live battle. If Happy had barely won, Tao Xuan wouldn’t be as concerned, but Happy won their away match 8.5 to 1 and then ended their home match early. Such a dominant win made it seem like they still had energy left to spare. Tao Xuan had trouble sleeping that night, and repeatedly counted how many pieces of Silver equipment his team possessed.

When he saw the section dedicated to Happy on the ESports Weekly, his mood dropped even lower. In this week’s paper, their Excellent Era had only been mentioned in one line, but Happy had an entire section of its own!

Terrible! Really terrible!

Tao Xuan barely glanced at the paper before throwing it in the trash can. He couldn’t stifle his nervousness. Team Happy clearly didn’t have as many resources nor were their players heaven-defying. Why did he feel so uneasy?　　

While Tao Xuan was having a bad day, Team Happy was having a good day.

With Happy in the news, Chang Xian grasped this opportunity and paid Happy another visit for more interviews. His eagerness made Cao Guangcheng think of his first few days in City H. At that time, he would head over to Excellent Era whenever there was an opportunity. In the end, he was able to establish himself as the team reporter for Excellent Era. He was like the current Chang Xian and didn’t understand their business relationship, only relying on their passion for work. He had run around frequently before being able to establish such a relationship, but, Little Chang! Is your passion for Team Happy truly worth it?

Cao Guangcheng had the heart to advise him, but when he thought about it again, passion was truly a good thing! This season, their news station at City H would only be concerned with the Challenger League anyways. Chang Xian was willing to follow a Challenger League team. That was a good thing! Why should he stop him?

When Chang Xian arrived at Happy, Chen Guo gladly welcomed him. Even though Chang Xian was young, he still understood basic relationships. Chang Xian naturally asked about how Chen Guo was doing after he had accidentally crashed into her last time. Afterwards, he expressed that he had come here to send them the news. At the same time, he apologized for not being able to use Chen Guo’s picture.

"It’s because there was limited space, butthere will definitely be more chances in the future." Chang Xian confidently said to Chen Guo. He believed that Team Happy would definitely continue gaining more and more attention.

"That’s good!" Chen Guo didn’t really care too much about her picture being published and welcomed Chang Xian in to have a seat.　　

"Uh, where are the others? Where’s Captain Ye?" Chang Xian asked. He obviously didn’t want to come over for no reason. Wouldn’t asking a few more questions to get more information on them be good too?

"They’re each busy doing their own thing? Are you here to interview us again?" Chen Guo asked.

"Oh oh, no no. I was just wondering….." Chang Xian hastily said. He just hoped to ask some passing questions. He wasn’t here for a formal interview. For one, he wasn’t prepared. Secondly, if he did an interview and then it never appeared on the news, he wouldn’t be able to excuse himself.

"Sit anywhere you’d like. I’ll get some water for you." Chen Guo welcomed Chang Xian in like a good friend. Chang Xian wanted to maintain this type of atmosphere for his visit, so he didn’t stop her. His eyes would constantly shift towards the second floor. He had asked about how the rooms were arranged in this area, so he guessed that Team Happy lived upstairs and went downstairs for practice and matches. The players might be resting in their rooms right now? Chang Xian didn’t want everyone to come over to say hello. If he could grab one or two and have a one on one chat, how great would that be?

Chang Xian was hoping for someone to come down. Upstairs, in Ye Xiu’s and Wei Chen’s room, Ye Xiu was lying in front of his computer working!

Everyone had a computer in their personal rooms, but they used it less than the ones downstairs in the practice room. These computers were for their own personal use. For example, if they wanted to go online and watch some TV shows or movies, they could lie on their bed and relax while watching instead of needing to run downstairs and put on headphones.

Ye Xiu’s business wasn’t in the game, so he naturally didn’t need that setup. There was only a QQ window on his computer screen. He had two chat windows open, which constantly blinked. He was clearly in a conversation.

On the left window, QQ name Dawn Rifle.

Team Everlasting’s Wu Chen used his character’s name on QQ. It was a habit that many pro players had, especially the older ones. Nowadays though, with the Alliance prospering, player trades were more frequent. Sometimes, their characters might get traded away, putting those who used their character’s name as their ID in an awkward spot. Still, many players liked to do this. It was also a way of showing their loyalty to their team!

Wu Chen’s loyalty to Team Everlasting naturally didn’t need to be questioned. His QQ name had been Dawn Rifle for many years now. Ye Xiu didn’t originally have his contact info, but after being in the scene for so long, he had a lot of contacts. Once he asked around, he was able to get it easily. For Team Everlasting, Ye Xiu was only able to get Wu Chen’s information. The other players had joined after Team Everlasting had been relegated, so they had no relation with anyone in the pro scene! Ye Xiu had a high position in the scene, so he wasn’t able to get anything.

Lord Grim…..　　

When Wu Chen saw the friend invite, he was very surprised, but he still accepted it subconsciously.

"How are you guys doing?" After being accepted as friends, the other side messaged him.　　

"Not very well." Wu Chen laughed bitterly. He obviously knew what the other side was asking about. When the winner asked the loser this type of question, was it to console them? Provoke them? Wu Chen didn’t hurry to a conclusion. He had been in the scene for a long time, so he had experienced all sorts of things. A competition would always have a winner or a loser. Even though the results made him sad, he could still accept it.

"What does your team plan on doing next?" Ye Xiu asked.　　

Now Wu Chen understood his intent. This guy was trying to take advantage of their misfortune.

Chapter 847: Also Having Much to Offer

With Team Everlasting eliminated from the competition, Wu Chen was feeling down. However, he was a pro player who knew how to act appropriately. He knew that this was a competition and only victory mattered, so he didn’t hate Happy for eliminating them. Yet, now as Team Happy’s members impatiently came knocking, asking about the future of their team without a hint of sincerity, all of Wu Chen’s composure and tolerance couldn’t keep him from getting angry.

How did the future of Team Everlasting look? As a team captain, he understood this better than normal team members. Currently, their disbandment was set in stone. Their boss couldn’t keep their team running for a whole year without it achieving any further gains. After all, they had already struggled to stay afloat for a year after being relegated.

If the team disbanded, then their accounts, equipment, materials and others would have no use anymore. Selling these things would be the last bit of profit they gained from the Glory circle. However, anything sold under these circumstances wouldn’t be worth much. After all, these things weren’t hard currency. They had no value outside of the Glory circle. With their team disbanding, they were in need of quickly getting rid of this stuff. In regards to needs, this was a market where the buyer had the absolute advantage. In addition, Team Everlasting wasn’t anything impressive, so their goods weren’t either. They might not even be able to clear everything out, nevermind getting a high price for it.

Wu Chen understood this. To be honest, Team Happy wasn’t a bad choice of buyer. Since only these kinds of teams would need what a weak team like them were selling. Or, at least, it would be absurd to even imagine the powerhouses of the alliance even looking at their assets.

Although this was how it was, he was still pretty angry that Happy had the audacity to ask just like that.

Yet, then, Ye Xiu continued to talk, "Don’t feel too bad about this. Competitions are competitions, now business is business. You should realize, your number of possible buyers won’t be in excess. If we’re talking about sincerity, Happy is definitely the best choice."

Seeing these words made Wu Chen feel depressed again. Did he even say how, exactly, his team was doing yet? Then again, this was God Ye Qiu, who was far too experienced in this circle. Being able to guess their position with confidence wasn’t surprising.

Thinking here, the last wisps of displeasure in Wu Chen’s heart dispersed, and he eventually responded, "I’m not in charge of this sort of thing, but I can help you pass your interest on."

"Alright, thanks. I couldn’t find anyone else on your team, so I had to come to you for help," Ye Xiu said.

"Right…." Wu Chen wasn’t in the mood to chat, making his replies as brief as possible.

"If we wanted to buy everything, how much do you think it would cost?" Ye Xiu then asked.

"I’m not certain," Wu Chen said. In reality, having been with Team Everlasting for so long, how could there be anything he didn’t know? But how could he give an outsider such information?

"Alright then, I’ll await your good news," Ye Xiu said.

"Ok," Wu Chen replied. Not long after, the other’s profile picture darkened. Wu Chen sat, stunned, in front of his laptop, staring into mid-air for quite a while. It was now that he truly felt that the team he had poured his heart and soul into, Team Everlasting, was not going to survive any longer.

And what about Dawn Rifle?

　

Wu Chen’s gaze shifted to Dawn Rifle’s card, which sat quietly on the desk. Would he have to leave the one who had accompanied him throughout his entire pro career?

When he thought of this, Wu Chen suddenly felt a little impulsive, picking up his card, leaving the room he was in and walked towards the meeting room.

Team Everlasting’s countdown had started. After organizing the last of their assets, they would soon announce their disbandment.

The meeting room was currently hosting one of their last meetings. As the team captain, Wu Chen had been asked to go, but he had declined. It was because he knew that it didn’t matter if he went or not. Their prior meetings were always about the future of the team, so they needed the captain’s and player’s suggestions. Yet, now, as the end drew closer, was the captain’s advice really needed anymore?

　

Those responsible for management knew this, too, so they allowed Wu Chen to decline. So, when Wu Chen rushed into the meeting room, everyone was surprised.

The meeting was in motion and the participants were all the heads of different departments. The Captain, the head of the the core department, didn’t have to be here, and that made Wu Chen feel another wave of devastation. He almost lost control of his emotions, but thankfully his boss spoke up, "Little Wu, is something the matter?"

The boss’ question scattered Wu Chen’s thoughts, allowing him to compose himself. "Have we accepted anyone’s offer yet?"

"Not yet." Though the boss was a little confused as to why Wu Chen would suddenly care about this, he still gave a clear reply to the player that he relied on the most, "We thought we should observe for a little longer. If there’s any way we could find a buyer who actively asked us first, then we would be able to minimize our disadvantage."

The club didn’t have anything else to work on right now, so they focused on turning in the greatest profit from their Glory assets. If someone actively asked after their assets, it would flip for a far greater profit than if they had to advertise their assets to others.

"Someone just came asking me about it," Wu Chen said.

"Oh?" Everyone was stunned for a moment, but then became excited. "Who was it?"

"Happy," Wu Chen said.

The room suddenly quieted as everyone froze. The one who broke the silence was He An. As the Club Manager, he naturally had the right to participate in this meeting. "Happy… They actually had the audacity to come knocking…"

"There’s no audacity about it," Wu Chen said, "Competition is competition, business is business."

"Whose side are you on, Wu Chen?" He An seethed immediately.

"I’m merely stating the truth," Wu Chen replied calmly.

He An opened his mouth to continue, but was stopped by the boss’ raised hand. Everlasting’s boss didn’t explode upon hearing it was Happy, but his expression did twist a little. Even Wu Chen had been angry when Ye Xiu came to speak to him about it.

"What are Happy’s intentions?" Everlasting’s boss wanted a more in-depth explanation.

"They wanted to find out our future plans, and if we are willing, I think they’re sincere in their intentions to buy out our assets," Wu Chen responded.

"Sincere…" He An wanted to scoff at this, but, being able to become the manager, he wouldn’t look at things so shallowly. However, his dreams and ambitions had been completely destroyed because of Team Happy. Hearing that Team Happy wanted to buy out what was originally Everlasting’s, he had a hard time thinking straight. However, he had realized this himself and swallowed his words, not expressing his opinion, but sitting there quietly.

His strained silence showed one thing. Even someone with a bone to pick like him was unable to deny a certain truth: Happy was a very good choice to sell to.

"Their sincerity… I think it should be trusted, but we aren’t sure of what sort of financial backing they have. The newest issue of the ESports Home weekly said something about their boss being the owner of an internet cafe?

After someone confirmed this, everyone sunk into silence once more.

To sell something, it wasn’t like you could pick any price you liked and not care if the other side wanted to buy it or not. The other’s ability and willingness to pay also had to be considered. If Everlasting really wanted to complete a transaction like this with Happy, then they had to have a clear understanding of other’s ability. This way, they could get an idea of what the price range they were willing to negotiate within. No matter what you did, you had to have an understanding of yourself and the others as well.

So, Everlasting’s boss didn’t immediately get someone to contact this possible buyer, but first had someone start preparations first.

"We should go and figure out what sort of internet cafe Happy is running, how many stores, if they have any partners," Everlasting’s boss planned.

It was then that He An and Wu Chen exchanged a look, and eventually He An spoke, "Wu Chen and I went to Happy to take a look last time. It was very ordinary, and didn’t seem like a chain..."

Hearing this, Everlasting’s boss was dumbstruck once more. If they were just an ordinary internet cafe, what backing did they have to say that they wanted to buy out everything Everlasting was offering?

Team Everlasting wouldn’t last much longer, but they were still a team that managed to survive the Pro League for three whole years. Glory was thriving, so even if they had to clear out and sell everything, it wasn’t like just anyone on the street could pick up what they were offering. Everyone here knew that the equipment and materials that Team Everlasting had managed to collect was worth no less than thirty million on the market. Even if they were having a clearance sale and their prices weren’t as high, it wasn’t something that an internet cafe owner could afford, right?

It wasn’t like they could assume that Happy didn’t understand anything. Wasn’t God Ye Qiu watching over them there? It seemed like Happy’s internet cafe background was a ruse, and that they had some other powerful supporter behind them! This might be something they couldn’t find out.

"For Happy… Who should we contact? Let’s get into contact with them first…" After some consideration, Everlasting’s boss came out with `that conclusion.

Chapter 848: No Inquiries

For Team Everlasting, everyone was clear on what they had to do in this clearance. Those who were responsible for internal affairs, those who were responsible for external affairs, those who were responsible for the inventory, and those who were responsible for settlements did as they were supposed to.

As for contacting Happy, it should be the responsibility of the manager He An, but since it was Happy, He An wasn’t the most pleased. After some consideration, Everlasting’s boss let this task fall on Wu Chen’s shoulders.

Having been a part of the team for so long, Wu Chen had his boss’ explicit trust. Actually, if it weren’t for the fact that Wu Chen wanted to focus on the competition, he would be the manager instead of He An. He An was very competent, but he still lacked the Pro League experience that Wu Chen had. Wu Chen’s professionalism was something that He An needed more of.

Wu Chen accepted the task silently, not commenting on it.

There were things that he had used before in the clearance sale and things he had managed to personally obtain from the online game. Yet, now, he had to personally give these things over to another party. Wu Chen wasn’t sure if this counted as a commemoration.

By the time he returned to his room, his laptop had automatically gone into sleep mode. After moving his mouse to revive it, he saw that the chat window with Ye Xiu was still open. Wu Chen directly sent a message over, giving an even more straightforward reply than the one Ye Xiu had sent him, "How much money are you prepared offer?"　Wu Chen, of course, didn’t expect the other to answer his question directly. This was a test of the other side’s attitude, looking at what tone and words they used to answer. In reality, such an important negotiation shouldn’t be conducted online, though this was still the preliminary negotiations.

Yet, just the preliminary negotiations between these two were a little too blunt; they immediately started out with the ultimate questions of "how much money are you offering" and "how much money do you want?"

Just as Wu Chen expected, Ye Xiu was still next to his laptop and quickly sent a reply, "We’ll have to see what you have to offer first."

"If it’s to your liking, are you prepared to buy it out?" Wu Chen asked. For them, they definitely hoped that they could sell everything all in one go, but this sort of situation was actually very rare. From what they knew of previous relegated teams, each of them turned into a supermarket. Everyone would come and have a look and buy whatever they needed, ignoring what they didn’t. So in the end, the good stuff was all picked off, and the not so good stuff was left with them to rot. In the end, they could only sell that stuff at a disgusting price to those offices.

"Of course not, we’re really poor!" Ye Xiu replied.

Wu Chen was speechless. It was hard to tell if this was the case or not, but it was clear that they weren’t going for a buyout. If that was the case, there was no need to get in too deep with Happy right now. Everlasting still wanted to wait and see if there was anyone willing to buy them out.

"Can we have a look at what you have to offer first?" Ye Xiu then asked.

"We’re still taking inventory, so maybe later...." Wu Chen was already beginning to stall for time. In reality, the information on the more valuable items had been given to him long ago and there was no need to take inventory anymore. Those that still needed it were the items that were many and unorganized. Anything that they could collect a lot of was, naturally, low in value.

Everyone wanted something good from them, but what Everlasting hoped for was that these buyers would also take a few things that were hard to sell with them too. In truth, this was a good idea, but was much hard to achieve than in theory. With their current circumstances, Team Everlasting didn’t really have much power.

"To be honest, we won’t ask for much," Ye Xiu responded, "You’ve probably already realized, the overlapping classes on our teams aren’t many in number."

"Not many? Launcher, Warlock, that’s already two!" Wu Chen said.

"We don’t need any Launcher equipment," Ye Xiu responded.

Wu Chen paused. The launcher Chasing Haze Happy had sent out on that day was rather noobish; was she really just a bench-warmer?

In such an important match of the Challenger League, they actually dared to send up a bench-warmer. Wu Chen couldn’t help but think of the match they had just finished. The Summoner they had sent up also seemed like a fill-in without any particularly striking abilities.

Could it be that Happy was stronger than they had thought, so they actually had nothing to fear from Everlasting? Wu Chen couldn’t help but wonder.

"So, for Silver equipment, we mainly want your Warlock’s equipment. However, there are a total of seven pieces of Silver equipment on that Warlock; I don’t know the specific stats for each, but they don’t seem like top quality goods overall. For the individual pieces, I’ll have to see the stats before offering a price," Ye Xiu informed him.

"You don’t want it all? If I’m remembering correctly, your Warlock Windward Formation has a total of three pieces of Silver equipment, including his weapon?" Wu Chen said.

"We do want it all, but we’re too poor! We have to be careful with where we spend our money and what we buy," Ye Xiu replied.　He’s still saying they’re poor! Yet, Wu Chen still couldn’t tell if it was honest or not. However, he had already figured out Happy’s intentions. No wonder a team with only the backing of an internet cafe dared to come and negotiate with them about buying their assets. They weren’t really here to make any big purchases; they were treating them like a convenience store, preparing to buy some soy sauce and leave. They had no money, but wanted to buy quality goods.

This sort of buyer was the kind that people hated most. Wu Chen and Happy’s preliminary negotiations were more or less finished. After that, they exchanged a few words out of politeness, but didn’t give any hint of how they planned to respond before leaving. Immediately after, Wu Chen went to tell his boss of what he had found out.　Hearing this news, Everlasting’s boss was, naturally, rather depressed. He had thought that Happy would be a good choice of buyer and not the clingy brat they had turned out to be. That sort of person wasn’t worth paying attention to so soon! All they had to do was scatter some rice for them if, in the end, they didn’t have anyone willing to buy them out.

After the preliminary negotiations, Everlasting became much colder towards Happy. They were already displeased with Happy, considering how Happy eliminated had been the reason for their disbandment. Even though competition and business were separate, the business they were trying to do between them was negligible; it wouldn’t matter if it never happened.

Team Everlasting hoped that another buyer would appear, but then one, two, three days passed quickly.　It was just three days, but Team Everlasting was already very anxious. It had been three days and no team had taken the initiative to contact them. Those who did were the workshops that wanted to take advantage of their misfortune. These guys didn’t want to buy anything for themselves, but just to resell, so they were doing their damndest to bargain for a ridiculously low price. Team Everlasting ignored these people who were even more despicable than Happy. Yet they began to feel uneasy: would their stuff all end up in the hands of these workshops? Why weren’t there any buyers apart from Happy? Were they doing this on purpose to mess with them?

There was only Happy, whose enthusiasm had not waned in three days. Lord Grim would come and chat with Wu Chen every now and then. They really did seem quite sincere. It was just that they didn’t have much financial power, so Everlasting didn’t think they were really worth it!

Today, Wu Chen saw that Lord Grim had sent another message to him upon opening QQ, and had managed to guess their situation in one.　"How are things; has anyone come over as a buyer?"　"Of course." Wu Chen wouldn’t dare admit the truth.　"Are you serious?" The smiley face Lord Grim sent made his confidence apparent. How was he so certain?

"Look." In the end, he didn’t even had to ask since the other had already started analyzing their circumstance, "Powerhouses wouldn’t need your assets, you admit that right?"

"Yeah," Wu Chen said.

"As for the teams that are of similar strength to you, their needs aren’t so urgent, so they can wait for you to give up and organize a clearance sale. Do they have a need to contact you so early in the game?" Ye Xiu asked.

"..." Wu Chen was speechless. This was similar to their own thoughts. Those clubs didn’t need anything of theirs urgently, so they weren’t going to be impatient, but instead just purposefully wait until Everlasting gave out.

"So those who do need what you’re offering and are sincere about it, would be those teams with bad foundations, especially those who want to fortify themselves as soon as possible," Ye Xiu explained.

"Yeah…" Wu Chen had to agree.

"These kinds of teams, to be honest, are more common in the Challenger League," Ye Xiu continued.

"The Challenger League… Normal teams wouldn’t have the backing to buy anything," Wu Chen said.

"Even if they did, they wouldn’t," Ye Xiu replied.

"Why?" Wu Chen was shocked.

"Because of Excellent Era," Ye Xiu answered.

Wu Chen was shocked again, but then came to a sudden realization. 　

Excellent Era, it was because of Excellent Era again. With Excellent Era being relegated, it caused a lot of people trouble. For example, the Challenger League had suddenly become rather meaningless. Under these circumstances, there was no point in using money to try and strengthen their teams this year. In front of Excellent Era, spending money wouldn’t do anything to change the result; they were still powerless.

In comparison, those like Happy who were also in the Challenger League but willing to spend money on strengthening their team seemed to have far more dignity and spirit.

"I think you guys can give up on a buyout. You should probably spend your efforts on taking a look into the pro teams that are willing to become your transaction partners, and start advertising what you have!" Ye Xiu suggested.

"..." Wu Chen was still speechless.

"But before that, can’t you guys treasure the teams that came to you to buy your equipment, like us?" Ye Xiu immediately added.

"As for now, you’re seen as the team that dealt the blow which landed us in this situation in the first place," Wu Chen replied with honesty. Though his boss had him contact Happy, it wasn’t possible that his boss had no negative feelings when it came to dealing with Happy. Upon seeing that Happy didn’t prepare to buy much and saw them as a supermarket they could browse, his boss immediately decided to give Happy the cold shoulder. This was probably because of that grudge.

"Is this really necessary…" Ye Xiu said.

"But after all your hints, I suddenly thought of another team that has a high chance of becoming a buyer!" Wu chen said.

"Are you talking about Team Heavenly Swords?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That’s right," Wu Chen replied. It wasn’t surprising that the other had managed to guess this. Anyone with some experience in the Pro circle would know that a team that had just applied to join the Alliance would be a good choice of buyer. Team Heavenly Swords wasn’t, as Wu Chen implied, a team he had just managed to think of. In reality this was the primary target they had been keeping an eye on.　

"Team Heavenly Sword… Not bad!" In the reply, there was another smiley face. Wu Chen immediately sensed the other’s confidence. What was this guy smiling about this time?

Chapter 849: A Straight Forward Collaboration

Wu Chen felt like there was some sort of deceit hidden within this smiley face, but he had no way of directly asking about it. Since he had just mentioned Team Heavenly Swords, he would obviously think about it from this perspective. Soon, he realized their relationship.

Not too long ago, Heavenly Swords borrowed the discussion on whether or not Lord Grim was Ye Qiu to attract attention. Now, in the Heavenly Domain, Lord Grim and Heavenly Justice as well as several other guilds had formed an alliance together to steal bosses, becoming more prosperous by the day. None of that was a secret.

Team Everlasting was fairly weak, but any team determined to take the professional route required a guild in the game as a foundation. Team Everlasting had a strong guild too and used any way possible to obtain any materials they could. Unfortunately, the Heavenly Domain bosses were battlefields of the highest level, and they didn’t have the strength to participate. They still paid attention to them though.

Wu Chen thought about it from beginning to end. Happy and Heavenly Swords didn’t have a shallow relationship! Even if they never had a relationship in the past, after these recent events, they definitely had some sort of relationship now. What’s more, Team Happy really did seem to be a grassroots team that came out from an Internet cafe. However, if you looked at their team roster, they had God Ye Qiu, ancient God Wei Chen, a former championship team member Qiao Yifan, and extremely talented new players, who had started playing in the new server and had already improved enough to be at the level of a pro player. None of them were easy to deal with. They didn’t seem like a grassroots Internet cafe team at all.

Perhaps Heavenly Swords was their true backer. Heavenly Swords executed a daring move, creating two teams at once. One would be joining the Alliance through the application process, while the other would join through the Challenger League. When the time came, two teams in the Alliance would be under their control. That would certainly be an unrivalled advantage!

Of course, that definitely violated the Alliance’s rules, but all policies had loopholes if you looked hard enough. Wasn’t Heavenly Swords trying to achieve their goal through underhanded methods right now?

He couldn’t even bear to think about it. The more that Wu Chen considered this possibility, the more issues popped up, but in reality, did Happy really have such a complicated relationship with Heavenly Swords?

Everlasting had hopes for Heavenly Swords. That was a fact. In these past few years, new teams would join the Alliance every year, but very few were as daring and overbearing as Heavenly Swords. Right after they confirmed their addition to the Alliance, they came out with all sorts of publicity moves. They even dared to ridicule the top teams. Heavenly Sword’s confidence could be seen from these actions alone.

Now that the Alliance walked the commercialization route, having lots of money was a formidable advantage. As soon as Heavenly Swords popped up, many teams actually closely followed them. They hoped that the owner was a stupid person with lots of money, who would brainlessly try to increase the team’s strength after joining the Alliance and wantonly buy useless trash at extremely high prices.

No one thought that Heavenly Swords, which had come out with such high-sounding speeches before joining the Alliance, would actually be so low-profile in the summer transfer market that it was scary. This year’s summer transfer market was quite lively. All sorts of God level players and characters were transferred around, but this new team actually made no movements at all. Let alone a team with such confidence, even previous teams would spend some money at the start of the season to close the gap in strength between their team and other pro teams.

Heavenly Swords made no such decision. They didn’t sign any famous players or buy any well-known characters. When they showed up on the competition stage, they appeared with the very same characters from their Guild Heavenly Justice. They had bought a few pieces of Silver equipment, but it only totaled to 20. In today’s Alliance, they were considered a poor team that brought down the competitiveness of the league!

Some experts even wrote articles questioning the investigations conducted on new teams applying to the Alliance. Are they not able to clearly distinguish a new team’s quality?

The current Team Heavenly Swords barged into the Alliance loudly. Three rounds later, their loud entrance attracted quite a bit of ridicule.

However, some people also considered Team Heavenly Sword’s later conduct as correct. It proved that the boss of Team Heavenly Swords wasn’t a stupid person with lots of money. They understood this point, so they lowered their heads for now. Moreover, for their first season, they didn’t have any overly ambitious goals. They had money, but they didn’t plan on throwing it around and instead focused on steadily developing.

This analysis was closer to Heavenly Sword’s real intentions.

But then again, if Loulan Slash had never met Ye Xiu, things might not have turned out this way. They might have been like what others had been hoping for, throwing out money, messing up the market, and then gathering a bunch of All Star players and characters.

At the same time, this time, Heavenly Swords desired the plate left behind by the dying Everlasting. However, they were also now more familiar with a certain Ye Xiu.

He An was the ace player and manager of Team Everlasting. In comparison, Lou Guanning was the core player and the boss of the team. His words held many times more weight than He An’s.

Lou Guanning trusted Ye Xiu very much. He even regarded Ye Xiu as their adviser. Happy had borrowed their equipment to bring down Everlasting. Lou Guanning wasn’t stupid. He was aware that Everlasting would definitely be sold away. After meeting Ye Xiu, who let them know not to aim too high, Heavenly Swords made every effort to walk the steady road. However, their current record was still disappointing. If they took Everlasting’s resources, their strength would certainly improve noticeably. Everlasting was just about to disband too. How could they let that opportunity go?

Lou Guanning desired Everlasting’s resources, but before getting involved, he asked for Ye Xiu’s advice, which surprised Ye Xiu.

Truthfully speaking, how could Ye Xiu not know that as Team Everlasting’s killer, rushing in to loot their corpse before they were even completely dead was certainly distasteful, but he didn’t dare to wait.

Don’t look at how everything seemed quiet at the moment. Who knew how many teams were waiting in store to snatch them up! In particular, Ye Xiu’s most troublesome competitor was actually Team Heavenly Swords.

Because Team Heavenly Swords needed these resources as urgently as their Happy. In addition, the other side had money, while Happy did not. Heavenly Swords could buy everything all up at once, but that wasn’t possible for Happy…...All kinds of markers indicated that Happy’s competitiveness was very weak. Ye Xiu was even worried that if Heavenly Swords really did make their move, there would only be slags left for Happy.

Who would have thought that Lou Guanning would actually run over to ask for his advice before making his move.

Of the two windows on his screen, one belonged to Wu Chen, an opponent they had just killed off, while the other belonged to Lou Guanning, who was a competitor that could steal away all of the meat in an instant. Ye Xiu was feeling all sorts of things right now.

Lou Guanning’s trust in Ye Xiu was quite moving. It was a feeling of a sincere friendship. The two sides would not only be doing things for their own benefit. From now on, any collaboration between Happy and Heavenly Swords would be placed above their own interests.

In the beginning, Ye Xiu had borrowed Heavenly Justice’s strength to suppress other guilds. On the other hand, Heavenly Justice utilized the suspicion of Lord Grim being Ye Xiu to hype up their team’s arrival in the pro league... all the way until the two sides worked together to fight for wild bosses in order to strengthen their own teams, borrowing each other’s strength.

Lou Guanning came over to ask a question, which was for his own purpose, but Ye Xiu felt like this sort of trust wasn’t easy for him. Lou Guanning definitely wasn’t an idiot and knew about Happy’s situation better than many others. He would certainly know that Happy would also be very interested in a dying team.

Even under this kind of background, Lou Guanning still asked Ye Xiu for advice. Ye Xiu wouldn’t avoid the topic. He wouldn’t conceal his team’s intentions. The two would open up their gates and speak frankly because any ill-feelings that might be involved in this competition was finally eliminated.

Their intimate collaboration made things very difficult for Everlasting.

Team Heavenly Swords was a sincere and rich team, but right now, even Team Heavenly Swords wasn’t reaching out to them. What else could they hope for?

Team Everlasting’s core members were discussing this issue for the past few days. They had no idea if Team Heavenly Swords had any intention of reaching out to them.

And now, once Wu Chen thought about the relationship between Happy and Heavenly Swords, he felt like he had grasped the crux of this issue.

In order to grab the money mountain Heavenly Swords, they might not be able to ignore Happy’s request! The two teams may or may not be one, but right now, they were advancing and retreating together. Everlasting could not ask to sell their goods because then they would be in a disadvantaged position in the negotiations. Everlasting also didn’t want to stretch out their necks and let them behead them. The two sides were lacking someone behind the scenes who could put up a bridge and this someone might be Happy.

Don’t look at the value of this someone. This someone would be a kind of mediator between the two sides, allowing both sides to negotiate from equal positions. If not, the two would continue remaining on the side, refusing to move. In the end, it might end in losses for both sides.

This mediator didn’t come out of nowhere either. It was artificially designed. From what Wu Chen reckoned, if it wasn’t for Happy sticking their hands in the matter, Heavenly Swords might have started offering prices already. Happy stopped Heavenly Swords from buying. At the same time, they couldn’t get Team Everlasting to come to sell to them. As a result, they were able to set themselves up in this clever position.

Even worse, even if you discovered the other side’s plans, there were no other options because it was only by walking this path could everyone’s interests be protected, unless Team Everlasting let their emotions decide things.

Wu Chen brought his thoughts into the discussion. After a moment of shock, Everlasting’s boss sighed: "A scheme. A true scheme….. Let’s trade with Happy then. We don’t need to shut our mouths too tight. Afterwards, have them bring in Heavenly Swords. If what you say is right, we don’t need to ask for them. They’ll come to us."

Chapter 850: Do You Want To Leave Glory

After seeing the crux of the situation, Team Everlasting’s negotiations went smoothly. Wu Chen immediately changed the cold attitude he had been using to communicate with Team Happy and started to actively ask what Happy’s needed.

What did Happy need?

No matter if it were equipment or materials, Ye Xiu had taken care to consider them. Every RMB they spent had to be done cautiously. That was the style Ye Xiu had taken to ever since his return. The two million RMB worth of materials they had gotten from Samsara had been a nightmare to take inventory of, but Ye Xiu had still personally typed out that list after carefully considering all the information and stock they had.

Team Happy was stronger than most other grassroots teams. A profit of 20 million would shock a street of people to death. However, they couldn’t compare to a pro team. Actually, there was a very interesting situation in Happy, and that was that none of the team members had asked for any payment.

That’s right, payment.

Pro gamers weren’t volunteers. As the Alliance thrived, the paychecks of pro players swelled. A yearly income of several million was just the income of first-string players. The income of those gods at the top had to be judged by their respective clubs. Though there were pro players who didn’t make a fuss about how much they made, those who seemed to have forgotten about it entirely like the members of Team Happy were nonexistent.

The members of Happy might not have mentioned it, but their boss, Chen Guo, hadn’t forgotten at all. It was just that, as a Glory fan, she had a vague idea of how much the pro circle made. She hadn’t purposefully forgotten, she was just a little afraid of trying to bring it up. If she really ran Happy like a pro team, there was no way she could afford to pay a God like Ye Qiu with just her internet cafe to support her.

This problem, Chen Guo even went to discuss with Ye Xiu. And then Ye Xiu discussed it with everyone else. It was more or less just since their team was just starting out, they didn’t have much, they had to work together as a team, and not fuss over individual losses and gains, but there would be bread to eat and eventually a championship.

In the end, everyone even looked at these words with contempt, especially Wei Chen, who put up both middle fingers at Ye Xiu, saying, "You think I care about what little money you have with my 1.8 million?"

As for the others, Tang Rou smiled, saying that she had an income. Steamed Bun casually asked her how much and Chen Guo hastily covered Tang Rou’s mouth. The income Tang Rou got was the income of an Internet cafe counter receptionist, saying it out loud would be an insult to pro players.

No one really seemed to care, not even Little Cold Hands An Wenyi, who had asked about it in the beginning. Now that he understood Team Happy’s situation, he didn’t worry about it. For entrepreneurship, in the beginning, it was formed of ideals and aspirations; it was a little inappropriate to talk of money in front of these beautiful hopes.　

"Very good, continue to work hard. If everyone can maintain this attitude, our boss will definitely be very happy," seeing how there was no chance of them being serious anymore, Ye Xiu started to mess around as well. The problem of everyone’s payment was somehow resolved just like that.

In the end, this was their own problem, so if they didn’t care about it, then let them! However, buying equipment and materials were transactions between them and outsiders. They might be willing to carelessly go over it, but their transaction partners weren’t. So, Ye Xiu always took care to consider every detail. Every RMB had to be spent in a meaningful way.

Ye Xiu had never planned on buying much from Team Everlasting when he contacted them; he was just after what he needed. The Warlock’s equipment was his primary target, but any sort of materials they might need, they could also check if Everlasting had them or not.

Everlasting started to warm up to Happy, thanks to their powerful supporter, Heavenly Swords. Ye Xiu didn’t reject their enthusiasm either, responding with even more enthusiasm in getting a gauge of Everlasting’s current assets.

Wu Chen was, after all, the commander-in-chief of the team, the captain, so, everyday, he had monotonously been forced on looking over all the team assets. He had thought he was clear on what they had, but when Ye Xiu started asking for so many details, Wu Chen’s most common reply was, "One second, let me check…."　After struggling for a while, Ye Xiu eventually decided on three of the seven pieces of Silver equipment Leopold had: cloak, belt and shoes.

Of course, it might be Ye Xiu saying this, but the one who made the decision was Wei Chen. Wei Chen was an experienced veteran, so he knew what he was doing and didn’t need Ye Xiu’s advice. Wu Chen had thought there was only Ye Xiu on the other side, and would’ve never thought that old sly fox, Wei Chen, was also there. Facing the two of them alone, it was impressive that these few days of negotiations hadn’t given him white hair yet.

"How come you only want these three pieces, the other four are rather impressive as well! In fact, Leopold is a very good character too; he had 4840 skill points, which is already very good in the pro circle!" Wu Chen earnestly advertised. He had submerged himself into his assigned role completely. Since they had realized that Heavenly Swords was the big fish hiding behind Happy, Team Everlasting’s recent efforts had been focused on researching Team Heavenly Swords and keeping an eye on their characters in order to estimate their needs and better understand the bargaining chips they held. This was understanding your opponent to better understand yourself.

Heavenly Swords didn’t have a Warlock, so they probably didn’t want Leopold’s Silver equipment. That was why Wu Chen hoped that he could sell all of it to Happy. It would be best if they bought the character as well.

"Eheheh, 4840? Our Windward Formation has 4920 skill points, do you think we would go around telling people about that?" Ye Xiu asked.

"4920!!!" Wu Chen was struck dumb by this information. 4900 had long since been thought of as the unbreakable limit for skill points that no character had managed to rise above. However, in last season’s playoffs, Samsara’s impressive performance made people realize their character’s had improved. Then, Samsara had personally admitted that all their characters had over 4900 skill points.

The limits had been broken, but that was by last year’s champions. For a grassroots team like Happy to have a character with 4920 skill points, there had to be something wrong with this team!

"That’s right, 4920, so you see, your character is useless to us. Could you please stop hoping that we’ll buy your characters? We just want the cloak, belt, and shoes, the three of them," Ye Xiu said.

"Ok… I’ll take a note of that; let’s move on!" Wu Chen was already feeling a bit helpless. They had been going back and forth for three whole days just about the Warlock equipment, but this wasn’t Happy’s only intended purchase; there were others!

"The list of materials you gave me, we had a look over it and think there are some problems…." The whole fuss over negotiating always started from "there are some problems".

After an entire week, Everlasting finally came to an agreement with Happy. Three pieces of Silver equipment on Warlock Leopold: the Hood of Sins, the cloak Endless Sorrows, Soulful Short Boots, were all sold to Team Happy for a final price of 500 thousand.

Apart from that, there was also the list of materials that Ye Xiu had given them. In the end, Everlasting didn’t have everything that Ye Xiu asked for, so after several adjustments, they completely a transaction of 200 thousand in value. That finished Happy’s round of benefitting from Everlasting’s misfortune, spending a total of 700 thousand and gaining a satisfying prize. The three pieces of Silver equipment could be used immediately, and the 200 thousand RMB worth of materials were many pieces of gear in the making.

"It’s unfortunate that what you have is too different from what we need," Ye Xiu told Wu Chen regretfully after they came to an agreement.

Wu Chen, having gone against two ancients of Glory, was utterly exhausted and sent a random emoji in reply.

"What now; what plans do you have?" Ye Xiu sent.

"I think it’s time for lunch?" Wu Chen glanced at the clock in the bottom right corner of his screen.

"I’m talking about your future in Glory; what plans do you have?" Ye Xiu explained.

Wu Chen startled. The sudden and very personal question from Ye Xiu made him uncertain of what to do for a moment.

All of Team Everlasting’s members seemed to already have plans for the future. Especially He An. Wu Chen had heard that some pro teams were interested in him!

But as for himself? Wu Chen really had no idea. His entire career in Glory had been alongside Everlasting. Where Everlasting went, that’s where you’d find him. He had never thought there would be a day where Everlasting was no more, and what he would do then. Until now, when it actually happened, Wu Chen realized that he had been avoiding this problem the entire time. His enthusiasm to keep himself busy was also an attempt to distract himself from these thoughts.

What was he to do without Team Everlasting? As he thought, his gaze wandered around the familiar room. It wouldn’t be long before he had to leave this place and, possibly, never return.

"Are you going to continue being a pro player?"

Such a message appeared on the screen.

A pro player, huh? Wu Chen suddenly remembered, he had never had plans for his own future. When Everlasting was relegated, he didn’t leave, he just wanted to return to the Pro League with his team and happily play for another season before retiring.

He was already 25 years old by now, considered quite old by eSports standards. The longevity of pro gaming careers in the Glory were increasing, and at 25, he could still continue, but Wu Chen wasn’t some big shot; he knew his worth. Originally, his ability wasn’t anything impressive, so now that he was older, his reactions were getting slower, and his hand speed fell. He probably couldn’t rely on pro gaming to put bread on the table anymore.

It was unfortunate that he simply wasn’t any sort of famous character. Many of those retired All Stars had found a home in the Glory circle, but for him, his interaction with Glory would be nothing more than a way of relaxing after a long day of work while recalling those good memories he had made back in the Pro League.

That sort of life sounded really monotonous...

Wu Chen was lost in thoughts, so it took him a while to notice that there was another message in the chat window: "If you don’t want to leave Glory, you don’t have to walk the path of a pro player!"

"What else can I do?" Wu Chen couldn’t help but respond.

"Our guild is currently quite lacking in manpower," Ye Xiu replied.

Guild? The online guild?

Chapter 851: Good Luck

After a pro player retired, the pro player would often be recruited into an internal section of the club. Often times, these opportunities would be given to hardworking and loyal individuals, or someone very competent at that sort of work.

Wu Chen originally had these sorts of hopes for his future. He had sincere feelings for Team Everlasting and hoped to never leave or abandon it, but now everything turned to nothing. Everlasting was on the brink of disappearing. What work opportunities could there be?

Wu Chen’s last stand was no longer only a part of his duties as the team captain. As a pro player, if he chose to leave at this moment, the team wouldn’t object to it either. However, where would he leave to? Wu Chen was at a loss and didn’t want to think about it. Now, Ye Xiu had given him a choice.

The guild…...

Wu Chen obviously understood that although the guild was established inside the game along with other player founded guilds, it was an important foundation for a team to be successful. Those in charge of the guild were definitely a core part of the club’s management. Their importance was no lower than any other manager in the club.

But truthfully speaking, Wu Chen had hoped to continue developing alongside Team Everlasting. If he had to switch to a different team, he wouldn’t be as interested. He was used to relating all of his experiences in in Glory to Everlasting.

But he could no longer relate those two together anymore. This was the cruel reality of things. He had to seriously consider this choice. In comparison, if he could continue in the pro scene to fill up his desire for Glory, that would still be his top priority. However, Wu Chen was only a small character in the scene. The top pro teams most likely wouldn’t give him this kind of opportunity. Only a new team like Happy would consider it.

But Happy was the main culprit for Everlasting disbanding. Even though Wu Chen was a rational person, he found it difficult to accept suddenly going over to serve Happy.

Just when he was about to refuse, another message in his chat window popped up: "Building up a team from nothing together is a very good feeling!"

Wu Chen’s heart suddenly began to thump. Not long ago, Team Everlasting had been like this: starting from nothing, establishing players and characters bit by bit. Even though their win record had always been pitiful, they had never given up. Even though they failed in the end, those memories were still as beautiful to him as ever.

He was kind of looking forward to it!

Wu Chen was moved. He understood that another similar opportunity wouldn’t come easy with his age and reputation. He just happened to have chanced upon one. If not, as a nobody, no one would think of him.

"Think about it!" Wu Chen hadn’t replied yet. The other side didn’t press him or ask if he was still there and simply left this message there.

"I will..." Wu Chen finally replied. The other side sent a bye bye emoji and then left.

Wu Chen began thinking about his future. After Everlasting completed the trade with Happy, Heavenly Swords joined in and their negotiations began.

These were the negotiations that Team Everlasting had been hoping for. Everlasting’s boss personally went out to battle. All of the employees were working together on this issue.

Day by day passed. Team Everlasting and Team Heavenly Swords had finally reached an agreement. Heavenly Swords did not completely buyout all of Everlasting, but for 10 million RMB, they bought around 50% of their goods, which made Everlasting feel quite satisfied.

Compared to the normal market, it was indeed on the lower side. However, their disbanded team had to sell everything off for cheap. Being able to sell so much for 10 million RMB was already quite satisfactory. Everlasting wasn’t some brand name. For a powerhouse team, let alone the resources, it would be hard to say if that amount could even buy a player on the team. That was the brand name effect!

Once the trade with Heavenly Swords was complete, the large stone in Everlasting’s heart had finally dissolved. For the rest of their resources, they wouldn’t argue and began taking the initiative to sell them to other places. The termination of the internal employees of the club had begun as well. Employee after employee left. Pro player after pro player left too. In the end, only Wu Chen remained. Everlasting’s boss personally handled his termination.

The grand strategy meeting room was empty. Only the boss remained. When Wu Chen entered the room, he saw the boss staring in a daze in front of the projector screen. His head was raised, looking up at the emblem of Team Everlasting hanging on the wall.

Wu Chen didn’t say anything. He quietly walked over. The boss sensed his arrival and didn’t give any polite greetings. The two were already good friends.

"Don’t you think this team emblem is a bit crooked?" The boss didn’t turn his head and spoke to Wu Chen.

"How could that be? It’s been fastened tightly. It can’t be moved." Wu Chen didn’t even look and replied. When their team moved here, he had personally put up the team emblem, so he couldn’t be any clearer about it.

"Oh, really?" The boss heard his reply and looked at it from a tilted angle, "Then I guess my eyes are just bad."

Wu Chen didn’t reply. The boss turned around and walked towards the table. He asked: "What plans do you have for the future?"

"I’m still not sure. You?" Wu Chen asked.

"Me? If another chance comes, I still want to form another team." The boss said.　　

"Would you still call it Everlasting?" Wu Chen smiled.

"Of course." The boss said.

"Then you will have to remember to leave a spot for me." Wu Chen said.

"Certainly." The boss also smiled. Team Everlasting’s history wasn’t long, but it had gone through numerous changes. The only things that never changed was their team’s name, their team’s emblem, and their most loyal member, Wu Chen.

"I’m just afraid that when the time comes, I won’t be able to play competitively anymore." Wu Chen said.

"Don’t worry. The team doesn’t only need pro players. With your capabilities, you can contribute to the team in many other ways." The boss said.

"Mm..."

Wu Chen replied pensively. The boss noticed his expression and suddenly guessed: "Did a team already invite you to do something like that?"

"Yes." Wu Chen nodded his head. He didn’t need to hide the truth any longer.

"What do they want you to do?" The boss asked.

"Probably guild related matters." Wu Chen said.

"Go then! It fits you well." The boss nodded his head in affirmation. He obviously knew of Wu Chen’s talent in this area. If he hadn’t respected Wu Chen’s decision, he would have been the club manager.

"It’s Happy who invited me." Wu Chen forced a smile.

The boss’s smile froze. He clearly hadn’t expected that response. His brows wrinkled: "Happy... that’s not too good. They’re a Challenger League team, but this season, there’s Excellent Era! If they fail to make it out, would their team be able to continue? I feel like you should clear this up first."

The boss only discussed matters with Wu Chen from Happy’s future prospects, but he didn’t mention anything about what Happy meant to their Everlasting. Wu Chen instantly understood his boss’s attitude. Although what he said was clear, what he didn’t say was equivalent to telling Wu Chen: you don’t need to care about anything else.

"Okay. I’ll think about it well." Wu Chen smiled.

"Then that’s good." Everlasting’s boss nodded his head and smiled back. He understood that Wu Chen had realized his intentions.

"The team’s matters have been pretty much been settled." Everlasting’s boss switched the subject and began talking about his current situation, "The current offers that we’ve received will just be that. Negotiating any further would be pointless. The amount of time and effort needed wouldn’t be worth it, so I think that if there’s anything remaining, you can take them!"

"Me?" Wu Chen was surprised.

"Find a good team and do a good job." Everlasting’s boss patted Wu Chen’s shoulders

At this instant, Wu Chen understood again. The boss’s words about establishing another team one day had just been talk. His final gift was to have Wu Chen bear the weight of Everlasting’s final belongings and continue on in the Glory scene. 　

"I’m leaving everything to you." Everlasting’s boss extended his hands. Wu Chen reached out and grabbed his hands. The boss shook it firmly and nodded his head: "I have somethings that I need to do still, so I’ll be going. The things are over there... good luck!"

The boss left. Wu Chen went over to look at the items on the meeting room table. Apart from the papers involved in every player’s termination, there were two fine card cases. Each of the cases had a word carved into them. One had an "Ever", while the other had a "Lasting". When he opened the two card cases, they were filled with account cards. The card on top was one he recognized. It was the one he had used for all these years, which he had returned to the club a few days ago: Launcher, Dawn Rifle.

As for the other account cards, besides the pro characters that had been sold off, the remaining were all from the guild. With the team gone, the guild’s existence was meaningless as well.

Is this my only choice?

He watched as the boss left. The door was left half open. Wu Chen looked at the team emblem that hung on the wall over there and gave one last sigh.

Two days later. City H, Happy Internet Cafe.

Wu Chen carried his luggage in one hand. On the other hand, he had a piece of paper. He looked at it carefully one more time and after confirming that it was the correct address, he walked in.

The Internet cafe was bustling with noise and unusually busy. After Team Happy beat Team Everlasting and made it onto the the Esports Home, Happy Internet Cafe’s business instantly exploded. And this time, the new customers weren’t face slappers or anything. They were truly curious about Team Happy and looked forward to their future.

With a new atmosphere in the Internet cafe, Chen Guo often strolled around happily. With her personality, she was able to instantly form a tight group with customers who looked forward to Happy’s future prospects.

Che Guo was currently at the front desk checking this month’s business records. She was happy at the team’s outstanding record. She was also happy at the Internet cafe’s booming business. While she was in high spirits, she heard someone speak to her.

"Is this where Team Happy is? I’m Wu Chen. I said that I would be coming today."

Chapter 852: Let’s Grow Stronger Together

When Chen Guo heard, she lifted her head. Both were stunned, as this was not the first time they had met. When Wu Chen came with He An to visit Happy last time, Chen Guo received the visitors along with Ye Xiu.

"Hello." Chen Guo nodded as she greeted Wu Chen. As the boss, she obviously knew that Wu Chen would come and join them today.

Thanks to Chen Guo’s fast and furious way in completing her job, Wu Chen was soon introduced to everyone.

"This is Wu Chen, the one we fought before, the former captain of Team Everlasting." Chen Guo introduced to everyone. Recently, Wu Chen was constantly in contact with Ye Xiu online, but for other people, it was kind of something in the past. Now that the third match in the Challenger League finished, Team Happy was able to eliminate a normal player’s team with ease. Happy was able to attract even more peoples’ interest in them. Furthermore, the Weekly News for eSports had reported a word or two about them twice in a row after their match, the treatment was comparable to Excellent Era.

"Hi everyone..." Wu Chen greeted the people, who stood up from behind their computers. Apart from Ye Xiu, he didn’t recognize any of them, Wu Chen was trying to mentally work out who was who.

Of course, Wei Chen was the one whom he determined his identity at first glance. After all, his abnormal and outstanding age seemed marginal and extreme among the group, so his identity was confirmed. As for the others, Wu Chen wasn’t able to grasp accurately. But before he could ask, Ye Xiu took the lead in applauding while shouting. "Everyone, let’s welcome him!"

Clap clap clap clap…...

Everyone responded, and the applause was quite warming, but because of this, Mo Fan, who didn’t clap, seemed like an outsider. Even though Wu Chen wasn’t the type to be bothered by this kind of thing, he couldn’t help but take notice of this guy. But that guy wasn’t even looking at him! He could use his computer without guilt even when he was left out and everyone else was clapping.

"Welcome, comrade Wu Chen!" Ye Xiu came up to wave at Wu Chen.

"God Ye Qiu..." Wu Chen was in between tears and laughter. He had constantly been in contact with Lord Grim on QQ for the past few days. At the start, he couldn’t be sure, but now. he could be certain that this person was Ye Qiu, but if this guy was Ye Qiu, then who was controlling Lord Grim in the competition? If it was still him, then he would be breaking the rules! Then Team Everlasting shouldn't be eliminated!

But Ye Xiu already gave him an answer in the next second. "Uh, I’m called Ye Xiu here."

"Ye Xiu?" Wu Chen was at loss.

"It’s a long story. I’m explaining this because I don’t want you to think that I substituted in to play Lord Grim. In fact, I’m the one who registered for Lord Grim, but I’m not actually Ye Qiu. Do you understand now?" Ye Xiu said.

"I don’t understand at all!" Wu Chen’s tone was unusually certain.

"You will understand sooner or later, let’s not talk about it for now. How about introducing you to everybody first." Ye Xiu said.

"How about telling me first!"

"This is Wei Chen - the former captain of Team Blue Rain many years ago. You might’ve heard of him. He’s currently using the Warlock Windward Formation." Ye Xiu said.

"It's an honor to meet you... hey hey hey!" Wu Chen was deeply troubled. He didn’t want to be impolite when he was introduced to someone, but on the other hand, he wanted to return to the previous topic.

"This is Tang Rou. She’s Soft Mist." Ye Xiu seemed as if he didn’t hear the three hey’s at all.

"Hello..." Wu Chen couldn’t help but divide part of his attention when he was before a beauty. Before he could continue to struggle with that question, Ye Xiu had already moved onto the next person.

"This is Bao Rongxing, we all call him Steamed Bun. He’s Steamed Bun Invasion."

"You beat me before." Steamed Bun said magnanimously.

This immediately caused Wu Chen to think that this guy took the matter to heart, so he felt the need to say something. "There’s always wins and losses in a competition..."

"This is Qiao Yifan, One Inch Ash." Ye Xiu already moved onto the next person.

"Hello." Qiao Yifan was very polite.

"Hello." Wu Chen looked at Qiao Yifan. Was this the youth who came from the champion team Tiny Herb?

"And that one’s Mo Fan." Then Mo Fan was introduced, who Ye Xiu merely pointed at and didn’t bring Wu Chen over to greet. Wu Chen then understood that he was quite strange. When he glanced across, he saw Mo Fan turn around to look at him due to being called. Wu Chen nodded and greeted his "hi", but that guy already turned his head to his previous position.

What a strange person….. Wu Chen mentally thought, and temporarily forgot to ask about the Ye Xiu-Ye Qiu matter.

"There’s two more too, An Wenyi and Luo Ji. They’re our Cleric, Little Cold Hands, and our Summoner, Concealed Light. Both are university students, so they’re not currently living with us." Ye Xiu said. Soon after eliminating Team Everlasting, An Wenyi returned to his school. After all, it wouldn’t be right to be absent from school for a long time.

Everyone had been introduced, but Ye Xiu’s mouth ceased to stop. He continued by introducing Wu Chen’s job. "As for the guilds, even though our results from snatching wild bosses from high-end places like Heavenly Domain have been quite good, our basic foundation is still very, very poor. Among the normal servers, the only bit of power we have is in the tenth server. We’ve just begun in the Heavenly Domain, so the burden on your shoulders isn’t light! What sort of useful advice do you have for opening up our phase as soon as possible?"

Since Ye Xiu asked, Wu Chen could only follow by replying. "I have a bunch of account cards with me."

"Account cards?" Ye Xiu was startled.

"From Team Everlasting." Wu Chen said.

"Oh, are they empty accounts whose equipment have been sold?" Ye Xiu guessed.

"Some are, some aren’t." Wu Chen said.

"Hm?"

"For example, we have an account card for each of the ten servers." Wu Chen added. "The guild leader accounts for Guild Everlasting."

When he said so, Ye Xiu was stunned for even longer. This opening phase was rather tyrannical! A batch of ready-made guilds were directly delivered into his hands. Something as wonderful as pie falling from the sky actually happened?

Possessing these guild account cards was equivalent to possessing a batch of guilds. Furthermore, those were the guilds left over by a professional team, so their system was definitely fully complete. The main job Happy had to do was to exchange the guild members, so all of the members were supporters of Happy. Then, the guild could begin to operate proactively.

Due to this, they were quite frustrated over having 10 guilds all at once. Who would they hand this over to be in charge of? For clubs, the status of every normal server’s guild leaders weren’t low at all. After all, the normal servers would also export large amounts of original materials for the team. Especially for the fact that Heavenly Domain didn’t have any materials below Level 55! Some were only produced in the normal servers.

"There’s also two guild leader account cards for the Heavenly Domain." Wu Chen continued to add to Happy’s frustrations.

But no matter how one looked at it, those frustrations were blessings. When Ye Xiu recovered his senses, Chen Guo had already figured out what wonderful things Wu Chen had brought along, but because those things were of such high value, it seemed neither suitable nor realistic to accept them easily. Chen Guo still asked with caution. "Are these all for us to use?"

"How about telling me about the Ye Xiu-Ye Qiu matter, God Ye Qiu?" Wu Chen finally managed to bring this topic back to light.

"Sigh, you really are... Alright! To put it simply, Ye Qiu is fake, and Ye Xiu is my actual identity, do you understand now?" Ye Xiu said.

It was finally Wu Chen’s turn to be stunned. Even though the words were few, but the information was too great! How many secrets or details were involved in this? Wu Chen didn’t know if it was suitable for him to keep asking. but because of this, he at least knew that there was no violation in the rules for Ye Xiu or Ye Qiu to control Lord Grim. Even though there was the suspicion of him finding a loophole in the rule, Happy had Ye Qiu, a strong presence indeed. Even if he directly used Ye Qiu’s name to sign up, it wouldn’t have violated any of the rules. So there was no point in finding a reason for Team Everlasting’s loss in this aspect. In addition, Everlasting had already been disbanded for good.

Wu Chen was no longer troubled over this matter, so he returned to the problem of bringing so many account cards. Wu Chen didn’t speak, instead, he opened his luggage and seriously brought out the two card containers labelled with the words ‘Ever’ and ‘Lasting’. Inside those two card containers, was everything that Everlasting had left. They were finally able to find its final home.

Chen Guo grew nervous because she already realized what Wu Chen was about to do. She looked on as Wu Chen placed the two card containers before them.

"Let Happy continue to grow stronger!" When Wu Chen spoke those words, his gaze stopped on the card containers, it stopped upon the words on the container.

Chen Guo was able to somewhat understand Wu Chen’s mood. This was some kind of entrustment for Team Everlasting’s incomplete ideals. Chen Guo didn’t receive the two containers, instead, she pushed them in the opposite direction, so they were returned to Wu Chen. "Let’s continue to make Happy grow stronger!"

Wu Chen was stunned. It appeared that he didn’t expect her to say and do such things. He was baffled and a bit moved.

"Yes, let us, together….." When Wu Chen spoke those words, he felt as if he went back a few years in time. At that time, he and his friends had built Team Everlasting under the matching support of Everlasting’s boss. During the very summer that year, they also said the same thing: "Let’s grow stronger together."

Wu Chen wouldn’t have thought that, on that day and moment, he would once again work hard to strive for these words with another group of people.

Everything was expressed in the lack of words, unnecessary declarations were no longer needed.

"We are still in short of manpower, so everyone will have to work hard." What Ye Xiu said was quite factual.

"Haha, this kind of hard work is better than being poor and blank." Wu Chen had the experience of building a team from scratch, so he was extremely positive towards the current condition.

"Well said, one can just tell by the looks that comrade Wu Chen is very trustworthy. According to the rules of Challenger League, even though Team Everlasting has been eliminated, their players have one more chance to register. Before the next round, you will register for the application to become one of the members of Team Happy, right?" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh sure. I can." Wu Chen was slightly lost in thought, but still nodded and agreed. His skills were more than enough to deal with a majority of the opponents in the Challenger League. Even though his character Dawn Rifle was almost an empty account, with his skill, he could bully his opponents without needing to rely on equipment.

"Then there will be two Launchers on the team." Wu Chen didn’t forget Chasing Haze’s existence.

"There’s going to be an even better one in the future!" Chen Guo smiled.

"Oh? Who?" Wu Chen doubted.

Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu, who replied without the slightest hesitation. "Dancing Rain."

Chapter 853: To Do More Than What’s Required

Dancing Rain…...

Wu Chen was deeply astonished. Let alone a grassroots Internet cafe team, even when Team Everlasting had been doing well in the pro scene, they didn’t even dare to hope to obtain an All Star character of that level. Wu Chen only had one thought in his mind right now: regarding Team Happy as a grassroots Internet cafe team was very wrong. Not only did everyone on the team have extraordinary backgrounds, just daring to think about getting Dancing Rain put them on a higher domain than Team Everlasting.　　

Having observed Happy directly, Wu Chen finally relaxed. He soon began organizing the account cards that he had brought with him from Everlasting.

Team Everlasting had already been officially disbanded. For many loyal supporters, the news broke their hearts. There were naturally quite a few of these kinds of players within Everlasting’s guilds. When Wu Chen logged into these accounts one by one, several players had left messages for the guild leader. Wu Chen read these messages and couldn’t help but let loose a regretful sigh. These loyal players still didn’t know that although these guilds still held the name Everlasting, the name would never signify Everlasting anymore.

Wu Chen didn’t stay melancholy for too long. He logged onto these account cards for proper business. Soon, the ten guilds in the the normal servers, as well as the two guilds in the Heavenly Domain, for a total of twelve guilds with the name Everlasting, had a new announcement: Team Everlasting had disbanded. Guild Everlasting will be inherited by a new owner. The name will change, but the guild storage system will not. Everyone can continue playing the game with ease　

Wu Chen was experienced. He didn’t immediately get rid of every single guild member and look for Team Happy supporters.

Because he understood the fundamental significance of a guild’s existence, which was to utilize the strength of the guild members to contribute to the team. During the early stages of the guild, players might have contributed to support the team, but long-term contribution mainly relied on the guild storage system.

As long as a reasonable guild storage existed, even if players in the guild did not support the team, the guild could still actively and effectively operate.

Guild Everlasting had been an important part of the club and had operated for several years. The system was absolutely fair. The current guild members had completely accepted it. Under these circumstances, Wu Chen obviously had no need to forcefully removed players. However, in the end, Wu Chen also announced that the new owner of the guild would be Team Happy.

Team Happy was the main reason for Team Everlasting’s disbandment. In the eyes of Team Everlasting’s loyal fans, this would obviously be extremely reprehensible. The guild was actually going to be handed over to their enemy. Numerous players would certainly have trouble accepting it, but Team Everlasting no longer existed, so it’s not like the attitude of their former fans mattered. Wu Chen released the information because he didn’t want to lie or cheat the loyal fans of Everlasting. Even though he knew that hiding this fact would save him a lot of trouble, the truth would have to be announced someday. When that time came, the players would have contributed a lot to Happy. Helping the enemy unknowingly would certainly hurt the players a lot more than telling them now. Wu Chen couldn’t bear to hurt them like that, so he might as well release the information now. After announcing this reality, he allowed them to freely leave.

As soon as the announcement came out, it played out as Wu Chen had expected. None of the other previous points mattered much, but once they saw that their new owner would be Team Happy, a huge commotion exploded. The loyal fans reminiscing Everlasting’s demise instantly became furious. They could understand the team disbanding and selling off their property, but handing over the guild to the enemy was too heartless. It was an affront to their many years of support. They couldn’t help but feel bitterly disappointed.

At the heart of the struggle, Wu Chen firmly stood out. New information came out with another guild announcement. Wu Chen revealed his identity and admitted that he had joined Team Happy. In the end, he acknowledged that having the guild become a part of Happy was his own decision. It had nothing to do with Team Everlasting.

This was more than what was required. Everlasting had already disbanded. Any slander to Everlasting’s name didn’t matter, but Wu Chen took the blows himself…...

"Is this guy a masochist?" This was Wei Chen’s comment when he heard the news.

Even Team Everlasting’s boss contacted Wu Chen after hearing the news, telling him that this really hadn’t been necessary.

"You still have a future! But Everlasting doesn’t anymore."

"It’s because Everlasting already has none anymore..." Wu Chen replied.

The boss sighed. Wu Chen’s feelings towards Team Everlasting was even deeper than he had imagined. As the boss, his final actions were all business. His conduct when he decided to disband the team had been extremely callous. How could he not understand the feelings of the fans? But in the end, he didn’t care anymore. To put it more cruelly, since he had decided not to step into the Glory scene again, the fans no longer had any value to him.

He might not care, but some did. Even if Everlasting no longer existed, Wu Chen still wasn’t willing to slander Everlasting’s name.

The boss couldn’t say anything more. At this moment, he felt ashamed to face Wu Chen despite leaving many valuable things for his loyal friend. In terms of materialistic goods, he had done a good job, but in terms of spirit, he had been thrown to the streets by Wu Chen. Wu Chen truly loved Glory and Everlasting. And he had only been a businessman chasing after money.

The rebellion incited by Wu Chen’s announcement didn’t need to be said. That day, numerous players from all of the Everlasting guilds vented their anger and decisively left the guild.

The words said the most were that they had made an error in judgement. They would not be a supporter of the new owner that Wu Chen ran to. Only a few players realized: if Wu Chen truly hadn’t cared about them, wouldn’t not saying a word be better?

Wu Chen had to spend a lot more time and effort to organize these guilds because of this "unnecessary" announcement. The twelve Everlasting guilds had begun recruiting under Happy’s name.

Even though the amount of attention that Happy received wasn’t low, there were still very few loyal fans. This was because the players attracted to Happy’s name couldn’t compare to the players who were attracted to a max leveled guild and a fair guild storage like Everlasting’s.

Even so, Guild Everlasting belonging to Guild Happy still made many uneasy. This was a huge step from a grassroots team to a professional team. No one understood the significance of a guild’s influence expanding rapidly better than those within the circle.

After Chen Yehui confirmed the news, he practically ran looking for manager Cui Li.

"Are we just going to allow them keep growing?" After Chen Yehui summarized the report, he began describing his thoughts: "Because of the Challenger League tournament format, we have no way of knowing when we’ll encounter Team Happy, but there’s one indisputable reality, the later we meet them, the more disadvantageous it is for us. They still have a lot of room to improve, but we’re already at our peak, so our room for improvement is fairly small. If we look at it from this perspective, the gap between them and us is constantly closing. When our team finally meets theirs, who know how things will turn out."

"Are you suspecting that Team Happy is actually a threat to us?" Cui Li said.　　

Happy is a threat.

Excellent Era did not deny this point. However, their worries hadn’t been towards Happy, but Ye Qiu. To Excellent Era, Happy was a threat because of Ye Qiu’s existence. It was because they understood Ye Qiu’s capabilities all too well. If not, they wouldn’t have forced Ye Qiu to retire. They were already worried about Ye Qiu in an Internet cafe team, let alone if Ye Qiu had gone to Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Samsara…...

If they couldn’t use him, they needed to destroy him…..

Ye Qiu’s strength frightened Excellent Era.

But now, Chen Yehui looked to discuss matters with Cui Li, not just for Ye Qiu alone, but the entire Team Happy and the threat that Happy as a whole posed to them.

"From Happy’s development, this isn’t a groundless fear." Chen Yehui continued, "In the Heavenly Domain, Happy hold the advantage in wild boss hunting. In one night, they now have several guilds under them. They’ll soon have a good amount of low-end materials. Along with Ye Qiu and the old God Wei Chen, how fast will their equipment improve? I dare to bet that the later we encounter Team Happy, the more Silver equipment they will have. Even if they won’t be able to have three All Star level characters, we at least won’t have an overwhelming advantage against them."

Cui Li fell into silence after listening to his words. For a moment, he didn’t say anything.

"There’s also one more point." Chen Yehui continued.

"What is it?" Cui Li asked.

"When we fight against Happy, do you dare to let Su Mucheng on stage?" Chen Yehui asked.　　

Cui Li was surprised.

It was the responsibility of the team captain to choose which players went on stage, but higher ups like the boss or manager could influence the captain’s decision. Whether or not to let Su Mucheng face Happy was something they could easily reach an agreement on.

Su Mucheng’s professionalism could not be picked at. After Ye Qiu was forced out last season, not only was Su Mucheng not in a bad mood, but she worked even harder on stage and was even more imposing than she had been in the past. However, against Ye Qiu? Would Su Mucheng still act professionally?

Chen Yehui was clearly doubtful. Cui Li also had a big question mark towards this question.　　

This was truly concerning!　　

If Su Mucheng didn’t go on stage, it would mean losing an All Star player. If they allowed Su Mucheng go on stage, if she didn’t take responsibility, it would mean losing a player, which would be even worse than losing an All Star.　　

This was truly a big issue!

Cui Li could feel his head begin to hurt. It seems like ever since Ye Qiu left Excellent Era, he would often have headaches.

Chapter 854: Two and a Half Months

"Then what are you trying to say?" With such a headache, Cui Li asked for Chen Yehui’s opinion.

He obviously knew that when they had forced Ye Qiu out, Chen Yehui spared no efforts to be at the front line.

"I don’t think we should let Happy grow freely. We have to suppress them." Chen Yehui said.

"Are you talking about in the game?" Cui Li said. That wasn’t hard to guess. The players on Happy would undoubtedly keep improving. They couldn’t do anything about that. The only thing that they could do was strike at the competition between guilds. This was also the main point of contention outside of the pro scene. The competition for wild bosses and dungeon records had lasted since the even before the Alliance. In the beginning, it had been especially intense because in those days, the various teams didn’t have anyone in particular responsible for the guild. The pro players directly charged into battle, so the level of competition back then was actually even higher than nowadays.

"Yes….. Happy urgently needs to improve their equipment. If we can make obtaining materials more difficult for them, then that would naturally inhibit their growth." Chen Yehui said.

"Just tell me the important points!" Cui Li was starting to get impatient at how Chen Yehui was beating around the bush. Chen Yehui didn’t need to look for him. As the person responsible for the guild, Chen Yehui could arrange for all of their guilds to move against Happy. If he had come to look for Cui Li, he must need the club’s support for something.

"The majority of our opponents this season are weak. Our players don’t need to go all out to face them. So what I’m thinking is if we can arrange for some of the pro players to participate in guild affairs, not only would this be an effective way to strike Happy, but it would also help us accumulate materials for our return to the Alliance next season." Chen Yehui finally revealed his purpose for being here. It was an old habit of his to look forward to others helping him.

"This... you’ll have to give me some time to make a decision." Even though Cui Li was the manager, he couldn’t directly make such a big decision. In the current contract, the pro players didn’t need to assume any such responsibilities. Pro players could participate in these matters to help the team, but because it wasn’t required, the most they could do is hope that they would.

As for Excellent Era, it was even embarrassing to ask their players of this request.

As a relegated team, being able to keep the majority of the main roster and even bringing in the All Star Xiao Shiqin and his character Life Extinguisher was mainly because of their 100% confidence in clearing the Challenger League, but now in order to ensure their victory in the Challenger League, they needed to beg their pro players to participate in the in-game competitions. When they asked for players to stay or recruited new players, it would appear like they had no confidence. Making the players not feel confident in the club wasn’t a good thing. Perhaps Chen Yehui hadn’t thought about this, but as the manager in charge of recruiting and maintaining players, he immediately realized this issue.

Chen Yehui also saw Cui Li’s hesitation. Afterwards, he added: "Right now, the reason that Happy and their alliance have such a major advantage in the Heavenly Domain is because Ye Qiu is frequently playing in the game. Our guilds have trouble contesting against them with just our level of strength."

As soon as he said this, Cui Li couldn’t help but look at Chen Yehui. He was starting to feel doubtful at whether or not this guy was actually worried about Happy expanding or because he was looking for an excuse for the guild’s poor performance.

"I really don’t need that many players. As long as a strategist like vice-captain Xiao can help us out every once in awhile, that would be enough to make things difficult for Ye Qiu." Chen Yehui said.

Cui Li nodded his head. After being in touch with Xiao Shiqin for awhile, Cui Li felt like Xiao Shiqin was someone who looked at the big picture. If he explained this situation clearly to him, he felt like Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t feel dissatisfied with the team. However, having Xiao Shiqin frequently run to the game definitely wouldn’t work.

"Gather more information. When it becomes necessary, I’ll contact the team to consider it." Cui Li finally gave Chen Yehui an answer that was neither an approval nor a refusal.

Chen Yehui understood the division of labor in the club. He was satisfied with this response. After nodding his head, he left.

At Team Happy, with Wu Chen’s addition, the guild and team stepped onto a new stage.

Wu Chen’s Launcher, Dawn Rifle, was soon fully equipped. Even though he only wore a set of Orange equipment, with Wu Chen’s skill level, he could easily sweep through a majority of the Challenger League. The addition of such a skilled expert made Happy’s journey through the Challenger League go even more smoothly. The maturation of the guild had to be mentioned. After this type of mechanism was established, everything could be conducted routinely. The manager didn’t need to closely keep an eye on them all day and all night. This would only allow for it to continue operating normally though. For wild boss hunts, the manager often needed to be there. As a result, the current wild boss situation in the normal servers had yet to be opened up by the Everlasting guilds belonging to Happy. In the Heavenly Domain, Ye Xiu’s side of the alliance no longer just consisted of him and his pitifully small group. An elite group was formed according to the classes and equipment of the newly joined players and old players of their guild.

However, Happy’s home guild was still in the tenth server.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had become famous there. Guild Happy had also been created there. From Lord Grim getting hundreds of answers with a single call to Lord Grim leaving to the Heavenly Domain to Chen Guo personally managing it and establishing the guild storage, the tenth server Guild Happy had also walked a healthy path towards development.

Compared to the other club guilds, their strength might be slightly weaker, but they were definitely above normal player guilds. Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, Thousand Creations... these players who had become friends with Ye Xiu in the tenth server now made up the core of Guild Happy. Ever since they left the Heavenly Domain to start in the new server, they didn’t plan on returning to the Heavenly Domain. Old players starting over in the new server mostly did it to acquire a certain advantage over the others with their greater experience, but because of how the Heavenly Domain was set up, their advantage in the new server would disappear as soon as they entered the Heavenly Domain…...

And now with the addition of Guild Everlasting in the tenth server, Happy’s strength increased even further. Seven Field’s group had already begun arranging teams. After a bit more preparation, they would actively compete for wild bosses. These few formerly Heavenly Domain players had just been run-of-the mill players in a mid-sized player guild like Full Moon Guild. Now they were rulers in the tenth server, leading other top players around in the tenth server.

Time passed quickly. In the blink of an eye, two and a half months of season nine passed by. Five and a half rounds of the Challenger League had been finished. Over ten thousand teams had joined the league. After every round, the numbers would be reduced by half. Now only a few hundred teams remained. In the Alliance, eleven rounds had finished. The new season’s ranking advanced one step further.

Those threatening new teams and new players at the beginning of the season all received setbacks to different extents.

For the new players, Team Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen was the representative. His recent performance was no longer as sharp as it had been before. The various top teams had begun studying him and had come up with strategies in order to deal with him. What was remarkable was that, although Lu Hanwen’s breakout performance had been suppressed, the spirit of this youngest player in the Alliance’s history was the same as ever. He never expressed a crestfallen expression. In the eleventh round of the season, Blue Rain and Tiny Herb fought against each other. Lu Hanwen was the deciding factor. His early death led to Team Blue Rain losing in the team competition.

However, no one blamed Lu Hanwen for this loss because his death had been because he had to face Team Tiny Herb’s God Wang Jiexi, and talented Gao Yingjie alone. This season, Team Tiny Herb’s dual Witches had become the new highlight of the Alliance. Let alone a rooke like Lu Hanwen, even the Gods still hadn’t figured out how to deal with this new dual class playstyle.

In the press conference, reporters who liked Lu Hanwen planned on using this point to console Lu Hanwen, so he wouldn’t feel too bad, but those who harbored evil intentions spoke first and naturally asked about his feelings towards Lu Hanwen leading to the team’s loss in the match.

Lu Hanwen didn’t appear dejected at all. He replied to the question seriously: "I feel like for something like this, it’s because I’m just not good enough, so I wasn’t able to win more time. Also, Senior Shaotian was a bit too far away and wasn’t able to rescue me immediately. Also..."

"F*ck, you little demon, you actually dare to blame me? Don’t you know that at that time, I was carrying out our actual plan? But the other side saw through our intentions and even found a gap in our pathing. You getting killed instantly like that was too ugly too look at. Even if you add up the ages of all of your opponents Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie, the sum is only three times your age. You shouldn’t have died so quickly. Next time, remember that at as long as you can give me an opportunity to launch a sneak attack, we’ll turn the situation around." Before Lu Hanwen could even finish his reply, Huang Shaotian interrupted him and started chattering away.

"Hm? From what senior is saying, could it be that our plan had a problem?" Lu Hanwen said.

"What? When did I say that?" Even though Huang Shaotian said that, the two had already turned their heads to look at their captain, Yu Wenzhou.

"Ahem." Yu Wenzhou coughed, "Let’s just leave our answer at that!"

The reporters looked at one another. This….. It sounded like the players were pushing the blame onto each other! But if they wrote this, wouldn’t it be treated as a joke?

All of the reporters had this type of feeling.

Chapter 855: Heavy News

Anyone with eyes could see that, in this loss for Blue Rain, Yu Wenzhou’s tactics were very reasonable, and Huang Shaotian’s Blademaster, as always, waited patiently for an opportunity to attack. It was Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Clouds that had been over eager to engage. He had said Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was too far from him, becoming a little out of sync, but the reason for this lack of synchronization was because his Flowing Clouds had ran off too quickly. He failed to coordinate with the rest of the team.

A veteran like Wang Jiexi wouldn’t not notice this mistake. Tiny Herb immediately came on with a sudden wave of attacks. Three people went to cut off any reinforcements while the two Witches, Vaccaria and Kind Tree, mounted a vicious offense. Blue Rain was just a tad too slow, resulting in Lu Hanwen getting wiped out by this wave of attacks. They fell into a passive role, and eventually lost the fight.

In the end, at the post-match press conference, Team Blue Rain didn’t take the mistake seriously at all, jokingly pushing the blame around. The mistake that caused their loss was just vaguely touched upon before being passed over . This was one of the ways they would protect Lu Hanwen, but it was also something that showed how big the heart of the youngest member of the Alliance had.

Even Team Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi didn’t mention the mistake Lu Hanwen made in the press conference, but instead praised his composure afterwards, openly declaring that this was something all pro gamers could learn from him.

Even at Happy, Lu Hanwen became an exemplar to learn from.

"It seems that the old are losing to the young in keeping their composure*!" It was only after seeing Wang Jiexi’s praise for Lu Hanwen that Ye Xiu started to lament loudly.

"You bastard, who’re you talking about, huh!" The words instantly provoked someone to jump up ready to fight.

Wei Chen, of course it was him that Ye Xiu was referring to, because he had been rather touchy recently. It was because of none other than the fact that they were already in their fifth round of the Challenger League. There were only eight hundred teams left. After this point, there would only be four hundred. Happy and Excellent Era were, of course, still within these four hundred and the chances of them meeting now was far higher than it had been back when there were more than ten thousand teams. So, Wei Chen became uneasy. For Happy, it was too early in the game for them to face Excellent Era.

Seeing how composed the 14 year old Lu Hanwen was, Ye Xiu wouldn’t miss such a great chance to poke fun at Wei Chen. This was especially effective, too. After jumping up in a rage when realizing who Ye Xiu was talking about, he immediately decided that he couldn’t lose to this youngster who was his junior. With an expression like gathering storm clouds, he sat down on one side to compose his emotions.

Lu Hanwen’s mental fortitude became something people admired even more than his technical skill. More and more people were admitting that he really was an impressive kid.

Another who had hit the Rookie’s Block hard like Lu Hanwen was Team Wind Howl. It wasn’t a certain person who had hit a block, but rather their entire team. They might have taken a strong lead in the beginning of the season, but starting from the eighth round, their scores began to fluctuate. After getting their then lowest score of 4 points in the eighth round, they managed to score a measly 2 points for the ninth and tenth rounds. As for the eleventh round, they only managed to earn 5 points.

Tang Hao was without a doubt a god-level player. In the early stages of assimilating into this team that revolved around a Brawler, the results had been very impressive. However, after several rounds, some of the problems in their teamwork gradually began to show, and the experienced powerhouses easily began to step on this tail that they had managed to grab. Team Wind Howl was unable to adjust within these four rounds, instantly slipping from the upper echelons of the ranking ladder.　Under the same circumstances, the veterans of Glory managed to become a shining exemplar for everyone in their line of work.

Team Tyranny, round after round of stable point earning, stood at the top of the rankings. Also having new team members and a new team, Team Tyranny seemed to have no problems getting used to it. After eleven rounds, what everyone was talking about was no longer if Tyranny could manage to keep their place, but if their good, stable performance could break the record that Team Excellent Era had set in the second season with a total of 314 points, and an average of 8.26 points per match, in the regular season. Currently with 97 points in 11 rounds, Team Tyranny’s chances of beating this record seemed good.　

As for Team Hundred Blossoms, who also had quite a few eyes on them, finally managed to reach the sweet moment after bitter defeat. After a disappointing beginning, they finally managed to find their feet. The new Blossom Duo slowly matured, especially Zou Yuan. Handling his new Spitfire character Blooming Blossoms, he managed to enter a peak state of performance. This made people think Zou Yuan’s use of the god-level account Dazzling Hundred Blossoms after Zhang Jiale’s retirement wasn’t such a fruitless decision. After obtaining a character tailored to his own style, Zou Yuan’s performance improved with each passing day. With him, Team Hundred Blossoms also managed to struggle out of the swamp of relegation, steadily climbing up in the ranks.

Speaking of that, there was another team that had been continuously at the bottom that had to be mentioned: Heavenly Swords.

Heavenly Swords was in the same situation as Happy. With thinner foundations, their strength was unimpressive, but it also meant that they had plenty of room for improvement. With Lou Guanning taking a hold of Everlasting’s assets, Team Heavenly Sword’s strength improved by leaps and bounds. The original 20 pieces of silver equipment had increased to 41. Though many of them didn’t really match, or would even be better for a different class, everything that could improve their character's strength was equipped. In addition, their research team that Ye Xiu wasn’t even familiar with was obviously putting in a lot more effort into the development of silver equipment. In every round, it seemed that the characters of Heavenly Swords had different equipment on.

With the continuous improvement of their strength, their scores were also seeing an improvement. In the eleventh round, which had just finished, Team Heavenly Swords received 301 Degrees on their home field and managed to take a 7 to 3 victory. This was the first time they managed to gain over half the points in a round, and stepped out of the relegation zone. They’re opponent in that round was Team 301 Degrees, which was a mid-tier team with a fairly stable performance. Occasionally, they would even step foot into the playoffs for a quick while. However, after their Knight player, Xu Bin, left during the summer, their performance had been constantly slipping. The all-star Assassin, Captain Yang Cong, seemed to be having trouble keeping the team afloat on his own.

With a passive and inelegant style, Xu Bin, who had held the title of "Grind King", never had much popularity even among the fans of his own team. It was only after his departure that his importance became evident. However, it was too late for the fans to regret now. Xu Bin’s talent was fully being utilized in Tiny Herb now, having accepted the all-star Knight account Angelica. The success of Tiny Herb’s Double Witch tactic was in large part assured by Xu Bin’s efforts.　All the drama happening in the ninth season made the Glory fans very happy. Yet after the 18th of November, the Monday of the next week, Glory officially announced another oncoming change that shook the entire Glory circle.

This year’s anniversary of Glory’s launch would, as always, signify the opening of a new server, the eleventh one, but there would also be a massive update added to the game. The level limits, that had not been touched in three years, was going to be increased to level 75. There would be new stories, new skills, new equipment, and even new maps...

For those who enjoyed the online game, this was amazing news. However, for those currently in the Pro League, this huge change would bring about unpredictable consequences. The already rather lively ninth season would become even more confusing.

For the characters in Pro Teams, increasing their level to 75 wasn’t a problem at all. However, the changes in stats, skills, and equipment would lead to huge adjustments in strategy and playstyles. This would need to be figured out as they continued to play. The seemingly stable situation of the ninth season might collapse into chaos once more.

Pro teams, of course, didn’t like these sorts of changes. However, since Glory’s competitive scene was inseparable from the online game, they couldn’t escape such changes. However, it was a little too disgusting that they would implement these adjustments, not in the summer holidays, but a third of the way through the regular season. Between matches, they not only had to rush to level up, but also had to research and test out new skills and new equipment. If they were a little slow about it, then they might be left behind in the competitive scene. This season was fated to be a very busy one.　Even so, the experienced veterans weren’t unfamiliar with this situation. Glory had only stopped quite long at level 70, but the updates from level 50, 55, 60, 65. and then 70 came one after another.

The Pro League was only in its ninth season. Of the eight seasons prior, three years had been at level 70, and the five years before that experienced an annual period of chaos with each new update. After the notice of the newest update came out, the veterans, who had been fighting since that era, all reminisced about those wild years.

Glory may have stopped at level 70 for the past three years, but who would believe that it wouldn’t renew its limits? So, even though there hadn’t been an update after hitting level 70 until now, all the Pro Teams had long since been preparing for this moment. At the very least, they had to stock up on all sorts of materials for silver equipment. As soon as the level 75 update came out, they immediately began researching new materials and charged over to level up their silver equipment.

Following the announcement of the update, the Alliance also made an announcement: on the week of the update, the fourteenth round of the League would be delayed by a week.

This was, of course, to prepare for the update and to allow all the pro teams extra time to adjust. At the same time, the Challenger League would also pause for a week.

And it was this notice that made storm clouds gather once more over the now-clear skies above Wei Chen’s head.

It was apparent that this wasn’t a good thing for Happy. Team Excellent Era had long since made preparations for an update like this, and had stocked up on materials over the years, but Team Happy didn’t! All of Happy’s material were carefully and specifically obtained by Ye Xiu. They couldn’t afford the cost in materials from failure. Under this circumstance, Happy couldn’t afford to charge into the unknown that was level 75!

Chapter 856: Meeting Change

The news of the level limit update didn’t send the pro circle into a panic, but also didn’t ignite a wave of excitement like it did with the normal players. The pro players still continued with their business as usual. However, the other departments of the clubs had to work a lot harder. For logistics, they had already begun to start taking inventory of their rare materials. Since all their silver equipment had to be upgraded, taking them to unknown heights, the consumption of materials could instantly deplete the stockpiles that they had been building up for years.

The guilds of their respective clubs also put more time and effort into team dungeons. Though this last minute effort might not be of much help, it was a matter of attitude that showed their boss just how much everyone cared!

Dungeon materials were easy to guarantee; it was the rare materials from wild bosses that were hard. Especially in the Heavenly Domain, it had come to the point where the big guilds didn’t seem to care any longer about their usual order and mustered all of their members to show how serious they could be. At this moment, it was a matter of headcount and the grounds were filled with corpses. Ye Xiu and his alliance were less successful under such circumstances. It was far too chaotic and lacking in method. The competitiveness of the big guilds were getting absurd and all they had in mind was one word: charge.

Charging recklessly all over the place, no one was certain how the Bosses even managed to fall into one guild’s hands or another.

This chaos continued for a week. It was probably because the guild leaders felt that they had done their part in this act, and decided to restore order.

Rare materials were very valuable, but after so many years it wasn’t possible to not have stockpiled any. In reality, everyone knew that what really would influence the bigger picture was going to be the new level 75 dungeons and wild Bosses.

The level 75 materials that would come from these sources were the real deciders. And for these new dungeons and Bosses, they had to first figure out how to beat them before they could even think about planning on how to snatch them. What sort of chaos would the release of the information on these bosses and dungeons lead to? It was something everyone could imagine. Even Esports Home weekly had decided to focus on publishing articles on the release of the information. Of course, they analyzed it according to how it might possibly affect the pro scene.

As for the specifics, they were being slowly leaked to the public through official channels.

First, they announced that the normal servers and Heavenly Domain would all be expanded. There would be six more areas in each server. These six areas would, without doubt, become the most active areas for players for the following year.

Six areas naturally meant at least six new dungeons and six new wild Bosses. So far, the Glory company had leaked the specifics of one area each for the Heavenly Domain and normal servers. Of course, the Heavenly Domain’s area caught the most attention.

Barrier Mountains. That was the name of the level 75 area announced for the Heavenly Domain, appearing in the north most section.

Among these endless mountains that seemed to form a barrier, was the main city of this area, Thousand Peak City.

Thousand Peak City wasn’t particularly large in area, but it was a crucial point in the defense of the mountains. Now, there were a pile of problems, both internal and external, awaiting a warrior to solve them or something similar. This sort of background was a must have in the game, but it wasn’t something the pro circle would bother to care about knowing.

In the pro circle, they paid attention to the other information released about Barrier Mountains.

In the Barrier Mountains, there would be two small five player dungeons, a ten player dungeon, a twenty player dungeon and a hundred player dungeon.

Shadow Tactician Sandy was the wild Boss of the Barrier Mountains, crafted from the storyline and background. Of course, the story behind the boss wasn’t something the pro circle cared about. What they cared about for Sandy was what class it was, what skills it had, what it would do at red-blood, and what good stuff you could get from killing it.

This information wasn’t leaked yet. All they received was a minute and forty-seven second long video that showed how powerful Shadow Tactician Sandy was.

The one minute and forty-seven second video was researched over and over again by the powerhouses. They came to the conclusion that Sandy was a Nightwalker, and the skills Sandy used in the demonstration spanned across the Warlock, Ninja, and Assassin classes.

The wild Boss was immensely powerful, but that wasn’t what normal players would pay attention to. Those who had experience in Glory knew that such a difficult challenger was beyond normal players already. It was something for the big clubs.

What the players cared about was things like dungeons that they could experience for themselves. The background stories that the pro circle didn’t bother with was something the players enjoyed. Not long after the information was leaked, people had already started making comments on the story. Some were lamentful, some were shocked, and some had already started writing fanfictions.

The game, of course, cooperated with all the publicity, launching all sorts of offline events to interact with players. Suddenly, the entire Glory circle was bustling with activity, celebrating the long-awaited update. The high end pro circle suddenly seemed more like onlookers. The normal players were excitedly celebrating, while they were busy making preparations to try and grasp future victories.

Club Excellent Era.

As soon as the announcements were made, Cui Li, Chen Yehui, and the others were all elated. Like how Wei Chen realized this was a terrible situation for Happy, they realized that this was another insurance bolt for Excellent Era. Cui Li didn’t waste any time in calling a meeting with all of the department heads. Of course, that nonsense about preparing for the release of information on Bosses and dungeons had to talked about. After that, he directed his words to Chen Yehui’s guild department, telling them to muster their people, and prepare for the new dungeons and Bosses.

As Cui Li spoke to Chen Yehui, his gaze was very meaningful. Chen Yehui and him were old partners and knew each other very well. With Cui Li’s speech concluded, he immediately started speaking, first speaking for his own department before beginning to analyze their current situation.

"I think this is a very big opportunity for Excellent Era," Chen Yehui said, "Although we’re in the Challenger League, I trust that none of us present have limited their sights to a barren land like the Challenger League. Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Samsara… Although we might not be on the same stage as them this season, they are our true rivals and always have been. However, this season, they not only have the pro matches to worry about, but also the upcoming information on the new update, so they’ll be feeling a lot more pressure than we will. In comparison, being in the Challenger League means that we have more time to expend our efforts on researching the new information. We can take this chance to make preparations for our return to the Alliance next season, and overwhelm them. This opportunity is like a blessing in disguise*. Though valuable, I trust that no one is willing to try and recreate it. So, I think that everyone should put in their best efforts and see how much we can improve with this opportunity."

Chen Yehui said this mildly, but as he spoke, his gaze often shifted to the captain and vice captain, Sun Xiang and Qiao Shiqing, sitting opposite him.

Everyone present was a higher up in the club, a core member, so they weren’t dumb. Seeing where Chen Yehui’s gaze kept falling and hearing his words, they instantly understood. This guy wanted the pro players to help out in game!

They were in the Challenger’s League this season, but in these departments it was business as usual. Only the team, despite still having one match per week, felt like they were on holiday; since all their opponents were insignificant, they didn’t have to give it their all. In the Pro League, pro players wouldn’t go into the game at all, afraid of messing up their mood and rhythm, which might affect their match performance. However, since Excellent Era was in the Challenger’s League, they didn’t have to worry about all that.

It was just that this wasn’t a part of their responsibilities, so the club couldn’t force them to help out. So, Chen Yehui could only hint at it in his speech like this and hope that the two captains would understand and willingly take up his suggestions.

Everyone’s gaze turned to the two. Cui Li, seeing this, made it clear that it was their turn to speak. "The team should also put effort into preparing for the update!"

Seeing this, Captain Sun Xiang realized it was his turn to speak! He cleared his throat. "That’s true. The new information released will be followed by new level limits, changing the stats and skills of our characters. If we were in the League, we would have to figure it out as we compete, so there will inevitably be some things they can’t cover while focusing on the match. We, on the other hand, have the chance to carefully research and test it. It’s just a little unfortunate that our opponents in the Challenger League are too weak to be lab rats. We will need to watch more professional matches to figure things out!"

Sun Xiang looked lamentful as he finished, but the other heads in the room all felt as if there were black lines on their faces.

This guy really is a newbie! He completely misunderstood what the manager and Chen Yehui were trying to imply. He was even seriously analyzing how the team could prepare for the new update.

Though your analysis was rather good, unfortunately, you’re way off topic!Everyone could see that when Sun Xiang ended his little monologue with triumph, Xiao Shiqing, who was next to him, revealed a little of his awkwardness in his expression. It was clear that he had figured out what the club wanted the pro players to do. It was unfortunate that Sun Xiang didn’t get it at all, getting off topic in all seriousness. Now, he had to go and fix this blunder. This sort of captain wasn’t even as good as Zhou Zekai, who only ever expressed his thoughts with "um… ah… oh…"

Xiao Shiqing was, after all, an experienced veteran, so he didn’t fuss about having to make up for this blunder, immediately adding, "If it’s just through the Challenger League, then we really can’t do much and there aren’t many chances anyways. I think we can find other places to help us test our strength."

"Oh? You mean to organize invitationals with other teams? But we’re in the middle of the season, would they even accept?" Sun Xiang said.

You… There’s really no saving you! Xiao Shiqing was instantly speechless.

Chapter 857: Charging Up

On stage, Sun Xiang was undoubtedly a God. No one would argue against that. However, outside of the stage, Sun Xiang made everyone feel embarrassed again and again.

Although his words weren’t necessarily wrong, they were very ill-timed. His thoughts were on a completely different track than what was going around the table.

Sun Xiang’s behavior suited his age. What could they do though? The responsibilities that came with his position needed him to be mature. Unfortunately, while Sun Xiang’s skill in Glory was constantly improving, his growth outside of the game over the past two years in the pro scene was disappointing.

He didn’t understand what Chen Yehui was hinting at. Xiao Shiqin once again reduced the scope, but he still didn’t understand what they were hinting at.

After he raised the topic of an invitational, everyone in the room was speechless. However, this guy actually looked quite pleased with himself. He felt like he had accurately pointed out the problem, leaving no room for doubt.

"Ahem... it would be very difficult to invite any high-level opponents for an invitational during this point in the season." Cui Li had no choice but to speak up at this moment.

"The update is about to be released though. In order to obtain the new resources, the environment in the game will certainly be abnormally intense. It might even be a perfect smelting furnace, a place where we can try out the new skills and new equipment." Chen Yehui didn’t beat around the bush this time.

"Test equipment in the game? Is that okay?" Sun Xiang was doubtful.

Chen Yehui really wanted to slap himself! He had blurted out new equipment without thinking. In reality, they definitely wouldn’t be able to test their new equipment in the game. The game was a very dangerous place. If one of the pieces of equipment dropped on accident, who would be held responsible?

Sun Xiang clearly recognized this issue. As a result, he only looked at the surface and didn’t understand the purpose of those words, so he immediately grabbed Chen Yehui’s slip of the tongue and raised an objection.

"New equipment doesn’t necessarily mean Silver equipment!" At this moment, Xiao Shiqin quickly made up for the mistake. In terms of theory, it appeared true, but was actually false. It still made it seem ambiguous though. Everyone looked at Sun Xiang. What was their captain thinking now? Could you please have a bit of depth to your thoughts? If not, today all we’ll be doing is attempting to instruct you, and you won’t even graduate at the end.

Sure enough, after what appeared to be a moment of serious thinking, he spoke with a bit of hesitation: "In the game?"

And then, there was no after. Sun Xiang stopped here. Everyone wanted to pull out their hair: bro, what are you even asking?

Cui Li couldn’t bear it anymore. He directly stated his intentions: "That makes a lot of sense! We’re not having any trouble in the Challenger League. If it doesn’t interfere with practice, having you guys go into the game and familiarize yourself with the new update is a good suggestion. We have ample time to prepare for next season. From this point of view, we have the advantage over any other team in the Alliance!"

Although Cui Li had completely revealed the main point of their conversation here, he still covered up a few things. If Sun Xiang still didn’t understand, then he was way too stupid. Sun Xiang didn’t understand what was being implied in the beginning, but he seemed to understand their words now.

This time, he didn’t say anything. Sun Xiang had a shadow in his heart! It wasn’t like he had never run to the game to be a helper, but what had been the result? He led Team Excellent Era’s main roster to fight against some randoms led by Ye Qiu and lost. It had been a miserable defeat too.

Sun Xiang wouldn’t admit that he was above that, but now that someone once again hoped he could go to help out in the game, he couldn’t help but think about it more carefully.

Everyone in the room waited for him to make his decision. Finally, Sun Xiang nodded his head slightly: "That’s reasonable."

Everyone let out a sigh of relief. Cui Li immediately seized this chance to speak up. He didn’t look for Sun Xiang, but Xiao Shiqin instead: "Vice-captain, keep an eye out from the sidelines and keep in touch with the guild department. If there’s a suitable opportunity, please bring everyone together to the game to practice."

"Okay." Xiao Shiqin nodded his head. He completely understood Cui Li’s intentions. Familiarizing themselves with the new release had been established as the reason. However, these few knew that the end goal was to borrow the pro players and rise during this period of time. Of course, the purpose was to strengthen the team. In addition, the Challenger League wasn’t as stressful for the players, so Xiao Shiqin didn’t have any objections to this arrangement.

After this topic, the other departments stated how they would face this new release. The meeting ended shortly afterwards.

The various teams were also holding similar meetings. Happy also needed to discuss their plans for the release.

　

"The battle against us is about to officially begin..." Ye Xiu started the meeting with these words.　　

As the various teams actively made their preparations, the last week of November passed.

The first match of the sixth round of the Challenger League had just ended. Happy had yet to encounter Excellent Era and easily defeated this week’s opponent. In the Pro Alliance, the rankings hadn’t changed much after the thirteenth round. However, everyone knew that this would be their final moments of peace. For their future matches in December, they would need to face the new Glory update. The Pro Alliance would pause for one week. In the second week, on 12/14, the fourteenth round would start and the effects of the new update would appear in the pro scene.

12/3 was Glory’s anniversary. The contents of the update had already been publicly released. As soon as the clock hit midnight on 12/3, the new update would be released and Glory’s eleventh server would open.

Including today, there were 11 days until the match on the 14th.

During these 11 days, the various teams would first force all of their characters to level 75 before anything else. If there was a character level difference in the match on the fourteenth, it would definitely be a deciding factor.

How many levels they could get during these 11 days depended on each team’s leveling methods, but at this point, getting even a one level difference wouldn’t be easy.

Apart from that, during these 11 days, the club guilds would work hard to find ways to improve their team’s strength through the new content. Perhaps some Level 75 Orange equipment would be better than their Level 70 Silver equipment. The company didn’t release any information on the newly released equipment. The players had to find out for themselves. During this period of time, the company only announced the new level 75 areas in the normal server and Heavenly Domain.

In the Heavenly Domain, there was also New Weir Peninsula and Weaving Silver Lake.

New Weir Peninsula was located on the east side of the Heavenly Domain’s mainland. It was a peninsula that extended from the original coastline. The background for it was a place where pirates engaged in battle. The main city in New Weir Peninsula was called New Weir City. In the area was a 5 player dungeon, a 50 player dungeon, and a 100 player raid. The wild boss was called Ruila, Daughter of the Sea.

The other new area, Weaving Silver Lake, took a part out of three other areas in the Heavenly Domain to form a new section of the map. Weaving Silver Lake was the smallest of the six new areas. This lake, which suddenly popped out of nowhere, naturally had a mysterious story behind it. As before, no one in the pro scene cared for it.

Weaving Silver Lake only had a 5 player dungeon and two 20 player dungeons. The wild boss was Silver Lake Guardian Frederica. Even though there wasn’t much information released on her, in the pictures of Silver Lake Guardian Frederica, it was very easy to deduce the boss’ class: gunner.

That was all the information that had been given. Even the pro clubs had no way of making too many preparations based on this info. Everyone could only keep a close eye on the calendar and wait for the update to drop.

At 10PM on 12/2, Glory’s servers temporarily shut down to prepare for the update. However, this didn’t affect the excitement of the players. Happy Internet Cafe was packed with people. The majority of them had even reserved their seats for an overnight stay.

As for the clubs?

The pro players had to restrain themselves from their curiosity and had to rest. All of the pro player account cards had been collected by the club and then given to the guild deparment for the employees to level up.　

These powerful characters appeared very ordinary because the self-made equipment created for them had been replaced with temporary equipment. The guilds had already arranged for guard teams to protect the levels of these pro characters.

This sort of protection was necessary! It was rare for pro characters to appear in the game. Let alone regular players crowding around them, if the players surrounded and started attacked them, it would be very troublesome. The pro characters that had logged on to the game to level up would not only not gain levels, but lose levels instead. When match time came, they might as well not even appear on stage.

Happy didn’t have the same conditions as those clubs, who had people appointed to leveling these characters. Their characters had to be leveled up on their own. In light of the amount of hostility towards them in Glory, their safety was also an issue that had to be considered. Their characters had been escorted by their guild troops to the northern parts of the Heavenly Domain mainland ahead of time.

The update notes had stated that Barrier Mountains would be merged into the Heavenly Domain over here. When midnight struck, Ye Xiu’s group would appear here and head directly into the Barrier Mountains.

Ye Xiu’s intent was to directly enter the dungeons. This was an undoubtedly bold move. In the new area, although the monsters in the levelling areas were between level 71 and level 75, every monster in the dungeon was level 75. It was supposed to be for max-leveled players to challenge, but for Happy, in order to have an environment safe from other players, they decided to try this five-level-higher dungeon.

The Heavenly Domain consisted of players from all ten servers. It could be imagined just how much more pressure there was in these six Heavenly Domain areas than in the normal servers. It was also why the Heavenly Domain was so vast. Heavenly Domain areas were much larger than normal server areas. These six new areas were no exception.

Chapter 858: Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout

December 3rd, at midnight 00:00:00, Glory timely released the new content. Tens of millions of players fought to log in at that exact moment. Even though it wasn’t a weekend, the loyal players wanted to start exploring as soon as possible.

Every account’s friend list was now lit up more than ever before. The quality of the Glory servers that they took pride in weren’t famous for nothing. Even with so much traffic, it was still running as usual. However, while the servers might be enough, the space in the maps in game weren’t. As soon as the new content was released, all the level 70 players, no matter if they had only gotten there or had long since hit the limit, flooded into the new areas.

So what if there were only six new areas? There still wasn’t enough space for the players. Especially the three areas that were first announced, even more players wanted to check them out. Ye Xiu and co had last logged out with their characters prepared to enter the new areas. Even so, all they could see were people when they logged in. It seemed that a lot of people had parked their characters before logging off!

Ye Xiu and others then realized that, at this special time, there was no need to worry about their characters’ safety. The players had never been so eager to talk with NPCs; Why would they bother with PKing? That was a waste of precious time!

This was a rare chance where everyone had been pulled back to the same starting point, so none of them wanted to lose before the race even began.

The crowd flooded into the new maps. Under these circumstances, doing quests and killing monsters was an extravagant luxury to have. So, many players realized that at a time like this, the only way to separate yourself from the crowd and get your own quiet space to practice was to run dungeons.

Unfortunately, the dungeons were all level 75. With a whole five levels of difference, normal players wouldn’t be able to handle it. However, no one cared about that now. If they went to experience the dungeon, then that was rather worthwhile, wasn’t it?

As for the big guilds, they immediately ran to beat the dungeons. New dungeons meant that there were chances to get First Kills, and dungeon First Kills, as well as records, gave out rewards that were as good as those obtained from wild Bosses. With the three year pause at level 70, all the records were broken to the point of being unbreakable. With the new dungeons, the long unseen race for First Kills and dungeon records was once again revived.

With Happy.Lord Grim, Windward Formation, Steamed Bun Invasion, One Inch Ash, Chasing Haze, Dawn Rifle, Little Cold Hands, Concealed Light, and the Battle Mage Forest Landscape, who had turned on Excellent Era for Happy with Chen Guo and became a core member of Guild Happy, made a perfect ten. Mo Fan had been hanging around Happy for three months now, but was still like a stranger, using free food and board but still didn’t greet anyone. However, with the new update released, he was pushed to be a part of their pioneering team. In the end, he didn’t reject Ye Xiu’s summons and quietly joined their party.

Ye Xiu was skilled and brave, with this ten person party, he headed directly for the officially announced ten-person dungeon in Barrier Mountains: Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout.

In the background story of Barrier Mountains, the Sealed Mountain Thieves were a group of criminals that caused chaos across the Barrier Mountains. The rebellion happening in Thousand Peak City was partly thanks to the rebels allying themselves with the Sealed Mountain Thieves. So, in completing the storylines in Barrier Mountains, there would naturally be an event where players would have to destroy the Sealed Mountain Thieves.

Apart from running around the map and fighting as part of the plot, the harder quests would all be completed through dungeons.

But anyone who was at this part of the storyline was probably not far from level 75. Ye Xiu and the others weren’t heading for the dungeons to complete any quests, they were going for the experience points and hopefully a First Kill.

The location of the dungeons had long since been leaked. After the update, it could be easily seen on the map. Heading over, the entire place was already filled with players. There were no monsters whatsoever in the Barrier Mountains because it didn’t take more than a few seconds after they respawned for them to go extinct. Many of the players were just like headless flies, wanting to do something, but not being able to find anything to do. The quest NPCs were completely surrounded and it didn’t seem to be possible to speak to one without waiting for upwards of an hour. Among the mountains, there were more players than monsters, so many people started to explore in an attempt to find a place with less people.

As for those who headed directly for the dungeons, it wasn’t just the big guilds; there were plenty of normal players as well. They would find a few friends, make a party, and start exploring the dungeons.

But wanting to explore level 75 dungeons at level 70 was a courageous move to make, especially a ten person one. When Ye Xiu and the others arrived at the entrance to Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout, they saw many people already outside. Clicking into their profiles, the stats were all red. Ye Xiu and co had rushed to the dungeon as soon as possible, but by then there had already been many teams who had been wiped out and respawned already; what sort of efficiency was this?

There were plenty of sightseeing parties at the entrance. In reality everyone knew that for new dungeons, even groups formed of friends, let alone random wild groups, had to struggle and research them for a while before they could even have a chance of getting through. So that’s why no one said they were here to run dungeons, but just to sightsee….

Ye Xiu and co didn’t dawdle, going inside as soon as they reached the entrance. After being transported inside, the scenery didn’t change much. They had only moved through the entrance. It looked like they were still in the Barrier Mountains map, but actually they were in an isolated space already.

In the areas around the entrance, there would be a safe space where you couldn’t be attacked. As soon as the ten of them entered, they started looking at the situation of the dungeon and quickly found that at each side of the door to the hideout stood a tall watchtower. Each watchtower had a Sealed Mountain Thief, holding a rifle and watching from afar.

"Should we blast them down?" Chen Guo asked, already controlling Chasing Haze to heft her rocket launcher onto her shoulder.

"Be patient, let’s observe for a moment. We’re not here for speed, just to get through the dungeon safely," Ye Xiu said. In a completely unknown dungeon with a five level suppression, they couldn’t be too careless, even if they were fighting for a First Kill. Under these circumstances, getting through the dungeon was already a win.

"A patrol is coming," At that moment, Wei Chen spoke up. Everyone looked forwards and saw a five-man patrol coming their way under the lead of a small ringleader, holding steel knives.

"Can we avoid the patrol?" Wei Chen’s Windward Formation shifted back by two steps. He couldn’t move any further, or else he’d exit the dungeon.

"Who knows," Ye Xiu, of course, didn’t know either. Who knew how close the patrol would get to them? "Prepare for battle!"

"I just want to ask," An Wenyi hurriedly spoke up, "Who’s the MT?"

"Me." Just as Ye Xiu said this, he noticed Luo Ji’s Concealed Light already summoning creatures, clearly because of Ye Xiu’s order to "prepare for battle." Ye Xiu hastily gave him an order, "Concealed Light, limit your summons to four or less."

"Ah?" Luo Ji startled.

"Uh… If you don’t exert good control over them, you might accidentally pull more mobs," Ye Xiu said.

Luo Ji went red, but he knew it was the truth. With his skill, pulling out at all stops would just be too chaotic for him and a mistake could release a summon from his control. Four summons was the most he could exert flawless control over. Luo Ji knew it wasn’t time to be prideful, so he obediently summoned four.

The patrol came closer and closer, as if they really were going to walk straight to the entrance of the hideout.

"Let’s snatch the initiative!" Chen Guo couldn’t stay calm any longer.

"Don’t panic." Ye Xiu was still very calm. "If we enter their aggro range, Chasing Haze shoot the left thief down, and Dawn Rifle go for the right."

"Ok," the two replied together.

"Everyone, be careful!" Ye Xiu quickly said, seeing the patrol come closer and closer. Though these were new monsters from a level 75 dungeon, he could still estimate the aggro range from experience.

"Fuck, it’s just a wave of normal monsters; don’t make the atmosphere so nervous," Wei Chen said.

"You’re nervous just from a group of normal monsters? How strange," Ye Xiu mocked.

"I’m just worried you’ll make the other youngsters nervous," Wei Chen said.

"Heheh, the youngsters nowadays are stronger than you." Ye Xiu was, of course, hinting at his junior in Blue Rain, Lu Hanwen.

"Can you two shut up!?" Chen Guo yelled. She was the only one who was truly nervous.

In the end, just as her words fell, the patrol turned and left without entering aggro range.

"A false alarm," Ye Xiu said.

"Once they’re far enough, shoot those two down," Wei Chen said.

So everyone watched as the patrol gradually walked further away, eventually turning at a crossroads and leaving their sight.

It had already been over a minute since they started the dungeon, and all they had really done with pose and look around. This showed what caution was necessary for exploring a place levels above you.

"Ok, fire!" Finally, the battle began. At Ye Xiu’s orders, with Chasing Haze on the left, and Dawn Rifle on the right, the rocket launchers on their shoulders opened fire, missiles heading straight for the watchtowers.

The smoke from the explosions hadn’t even dispersed when they heard the two NPCs start to yell, "Intruders! Intruders!"

In an instant, the patrol that had disappeared around the corner flew right back.

"So it’s like that! Seems like we should’ve assassinated them first?" Ye Xiu wondered aloud.

As for Chen Guo, she had long since started panicking, asking Ye Xiu, "Where do I shoot? Where do I shoot?"

Tang Rou was far more ferocious. Seeing that the commotion had already begun, she had already charged forth to meet them.

"Slow down, Soft Mist!" Ye Xiu hurriedly shouted. "We’ll kill them here. If we charge forwards, we don’t know if we might pull other monsters or not." Ye Xiu was experienced, after all.

Hearing this, Tang Rou had Soft Mist stop her charge. The two Sealed Mountain thieves that had been shot at, were knocked down by the blast and were currently not a threat. The patrol of thieves running over had two gunner class members that raised their weapons and started shooting.

Bang bang! Two gunshots rang out, but the victims weren’t Chasing Haze and Dawn Rifle.

"Ai, this patrol’s aggro is quite unusual!" Saying this, Ye Xiu knew it was time for him to step up to do his job as the MT.

Chapter 859: Aggro Chain

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim led the way forward, but the patrol team had two long-ranged gunners, so they wouldn’t run to the front to attack.

Ye Xiu had just stopped Soft Mist from running too far. Naturally, he did the same too. As a result, the two gunners were difficult to control. At this distance, only a Qi Master’s Cloud Grasping Fist could pull them over. Team Happy didn’t have this class. It was a skill that could only be learned after class advancement. The unspecialized Lord Grim and the brawler Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t learn it.

In this situation, other skill effects needed to be used in order to get the desired effects. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim jumped high into the air and lobbed a grenade. The grenade arced down behind those two gunners.　　

Boom!　　

Dust clouds rose from the explosion. The two gunners were thrown forward. At the same time, Lord Grim forced his way back down with a Falling Light Blade. The other three dagger wielding Sealed Mountain thieves ate dirt from the blast too.

Ye Xiu was pleased with the NPC’s courage. A normal player would have easily dodged the grenade thrown out from such a far distance. Only NPCs would so stupidly ignore the attack and facetank the damage. No matter the level gap, NPCs fundamental patterns never changed. Only advanced NPCs, otherwise known as bosses, would pay attention to avoiding damage.

The grenade pushed the two gunners closer, but the power of the skill was still fairly weak. At this moment, a missile descended from the sky and landed behind the two Sealed Mountain thief gunners.

Boom!

This time, the shockwave’s AOE was far more powerful than the grenade’s. The mushroom cloud shot up into the sky. If that still didn’t push the two gunners in front of Lord Grim, it would be an outrage to the visual effects.　　

"Beautiful!"

Amidst the chaos, the MT didn’t forget to give a big thumbs up behind him to whoever did that.　　

Chen Guo felt jealous! If only she had that kind of skill! Unfortunately, she didn’t have the ability to guide the Heat Seeking Missile to the desired location in such a short amount of time. It was Team Happy’s newest member, Wu Chen, who had shot the missile. Wu Chen’s skill level couldn’t be considered top tier in the pro scene, but his fundamentals were still solid. What Chen Guo liked was that when this brother came, he didn’t hurry to discuss about wages and what not. He was like the others and just got by with what they had. What a great helper! Chen Guo couldn’t help but think at this moment.

"First look at the target I’m attacking. Don’t aggro enemies randomly." Ye Xiu shouted. After all, his unspecialized character wasn’t a Knight. He didn’t have the stats to hold too many enemies. His main method of pulling monsters was through damage. As a result, the level of coordination necessary to make this work was fairly high. If the DPS classes only cared about themselves, the aggro would quickly turn into a mess.

Of the people here, he obviously didn’t need to worry about Wei Chen, Qiao Yifan, or Wu Chen. Steamed Bun and Tang Rou had played with Ye Xiu for a long time now, so they were familiar with Lord Grim’s MT style. They wouldn’t make simple mistakes. As for Little Cold Hands, he wouldn’t be healing the monsters. Apart from them was Chen Guo, Luo Ji, and Mo Fan.

Chen Guo had experience and knew her skills well. She knew that with her skill level among this team, let alone helping them, it would be good as long as she wasn’t a burden. In a chaotic situation like this, she might as well not do anything, so she wouldn’t mess anything up. That side had turned into a mess. For a moment, she had no way of having Chasing Haze accurately attack the correct target, so she simply did nothing and acted as a spectator.

As for Luo Ji, if he did his usual summon of everything at once, the team’s killer would certainly be him. Fortunately, Ye Xiu had reminded him, so he only summoned four creatures, which Luo Ji could adequately control.　　

As a result, the person who could be a problem would be Mo Fan. This guy actually used a high-level Ninja skill, Shadow Dance. This skill was always used as a group attack. Once this attack came out, wouldn’t he be the one generating the most aggro?

Chen Guo became anxious when she saw this scene. She jumped out and yelled: "What are you doing?"

Outside of the game, Chen Guo was already glaring at Mo Fan. She could endure Mo Fan’s usual behavior because, even though he hadn’t helped them at all, he wasn’t a burden either. Chen Guo wouldn’t mind his trivial matters like eating and living here every day. She knew Ye Xiu’s intentions were to have him slowly get involved in this lifestyle, so Mo Fan would wholeheartedly want to join, but in this crucial moment, Mo Fan actually didn’t listen to orders and acted on his own. It crossed the line for Chen Guo.

"Calm down!" Mo Fan ignored her, but Ye Xiu’s voice came.

"This guy..."

"It’s fine." Ye Xiu interrupted Chen Guo and told her to take a look at the screen.　

Chen Guo glanced at it and was stunned.

After Mo Fan’s Deception used Shadow Dance, clones were scattered all over the place. The aggro wasn’t messed up though, because his Shadow Dance had been controlled very well. His attack target was still the one that everyone was focusing on. He wasn’t attacking anywhere he wanted to, like Chen Guo had originally thought.

"This guy..." Chen Guo knew she had blamed Mo Fan wrongly, but that guy completely ignored her. Apologizing to him was pointless! But after sitting down again, Chen Guo still mumbled as if she were talking to Ye Xiu: "I blamed him wrongly."

"That’s not entirely true. He wants to mess things up." Ye Xiu said.

"What!"

"He wants to take the aggro away from me!" Ye Xiu said indifferently. Through the in-game voice comms, everyone could hear his words.

"Don’t mess around." Wei Chen was very displeased.

"Haha, if you want to mess things up, you’d better try harder!" Ye Xiu said. His hands continued to move. Chen Guo stole a glance at Mo Fan. His expression was very serious. This punk probably still harbored resentment against Ye Xiu. If he could steal away the aggro, it would mean that he was superior to Ye Xiu. As for the chaos that followed, he probably didn’t care. Did he have any sense of teamwork in his heart?

In any case, Chen Guo didn’t get involved, so she didn’t make any mistakes. Ye Xiu took Lord Grim and assumed the MT role. It wasn’t an easy task. A 5 level difference meant that his skill effects wouldn’t be completely effective. In addition, he pulled seven monsters at once. There was no way he wouldn’t handle all of damage. In a ten player dungeon, when pulling so many monsters, the main tank and secondary tank usually acted together. Right now, not only was Lord Grim not a tank class, Ye Xiu could only rely himself.

"Don’t just focus on attacking. Pay attention to the patterns of these Sealed Mountain thieves." Ye Xiu reminded everyone.　　

There could only be so many different types of dungeon NPCs, which appeared again and again. As a result, the first wave was considered the most difficult because only this battle would be completely unknown. After his first battle, they would start accumulating knowledge on the new dungeon monsters and their progress through the dungeon would become smoother.

The battle with these seven Sealed Mountain thieves lasted three minutes long. After Ye Xiu took control of the pace, the old veteran Wei Chen didn’t need to strictly follow the arrangements. He started displaying a playstyle that suited him much better, thus decreasing the pressure on the team. In the end, the first wave ended smoothly. They were just minions. There wasn’t much suspense to it at all. After a bit of adjustment, the team followed the path to the stronghold and continued forward.

At the same time, those guild teams, friend groups, or just random passerbyers were having trouble with these seven aggro-linked monsters at the entrance.

It wasn’t so tragic that all of them wiped out, but getting past this part without any casualties like Team Happy did was truly a bit difficult for these players.

Take Blue Brook Guild. Their guild’s most elite members were personally led by Chen Yehui to start this dungeon.

There was a suppression of five levels. Starting with a ten player dungeon was the limit. Attempting a dungeon that required more people would be underestimating the game too much. Hundred player dungeons didn’t even need to be mentioned. Even now, those top guilds didn’t dare claim that they could get through the Level 70 ones with certainty! A hundred players going in and ninety players coming out was already an impressive achievement.

Facing these seven Level 75 dungeon monsters were the Five Great Experts of Blue Brook Guild. It took the sacrifice of two of their members to eliminate these seven monsters.

"How difficult...." After the battle ended, Chilling Nightfall had lingering fears.

"We probably won’t be able to clear it will we." Flying Brushstroke said.

"Clear it? If the rest is like this too, it’s hard to say if we’ll even make it to the boss." Chilling Nightfall said.

"Let’s just take a look around..." Flying Brushstroke was gloomy. These two Great Experts of Blue Brook Guild had already lost the will to continue fighting. Of course, they couldn’t be blamed. They had already been mentally prepared for this outcome in a ten player dungeon five levers above them. However, they had thought that they would be killed by the boss. They didn’t think these little monsters would be an issue. Who would have thought that two of their guys would die after the opening battle?

"Probably only pro players can pass through this ten player dungeon right now." Chilling Nightfall said.

"There shouldn’t be any pro players on at this time." Flying Brushstroke said. Although they could see that in their Blue Brook Guild, whether it was Swoksaar or Troubling Rain or Flowing Cloud or Soul Speaker or any of the other pro characters, all of them were online. However, they knew that these characters weren’t being played by the pro players.The account cards had been handed to the guild department. During this period of time, they were being power leveled 24/7. At this moment, they sought after the fastest leveling speed. Coming to the new areas to level wouldn’t be a smart move. These Team Blue Rain characters were at the known areas, clearing Level 70 dungeons to level instead.

These characters were Level 70. The people leveling these characters had experience with Level 70 dungeons, which was why, in order to pursue the fastest leveling speed, this was the best method. Each and every character on a pro team was leveling in the Level 70 dungeons. During these 11 days, they would utilize the fastest leveling method to level up before doing anything else.

"There probably won’t be a First Clear tonight, right?" Right when Chilling Nightfall finished these words, a guy popped up in Blue River’s mind... Is he leveling or clearing dungeons right now?

Chapter 860: Vanguard Brother Wolf

The people Blue River was thinking of were naturally Ye Xiu and Happy. However, even though he knew that the other was very skilled at running dungeons, he had no way of causing any trouble for them. Blue River decided to not bring this up in fear of affecting their moods. The Blue Brook Guild expert party continued forth. The next two waves of monsters each had less than three. With seven people going against them, it wasn’t too difficult. However, while fighting the following wave, Flying Brushstroke was caught off guard by a Sealed Mountain thief and was sent flying, right into the aggro range if another wave of Sealed Mountain thieves.

One, two, three, four, five...

The new wave had five monsters. After Flying Brushstroke was sent flying, he never came back. The other six didn’t have time to come over and save him before he died and left the dungeon.

These five, in addition to the original four, made a total of nine Sealed Mountain Thieves, two more than the first wave. As for Blue Brook Guild? They only had six people left. After a furious life and death struggle, the six couldn’t hold protect their lives from these nine thieves. In the chaos, three of the nine thieves were killed and the six Blue Brook Guild experts were wiped out.

The creme de la creme of Blue Brook Guild’s experts managed to explore for a total of twelve minutes in the new dungeon. This record was much better than those parties who were swept upon entering. Next time, they knew that there would be seven Sealed Mountain Thieves in the first wave and would be prepared for it. The pioneering of a new dungeon was done through the stockpile of these attempts. Unfortunately, Glory’s rules were rather harsh. A character would be sent out of the dungeon upon dying, so they would be unable to experience the entire thing. In addition, there was an upper limit to the amount of times you could enter a dungeon per day. Each character only had one run at the ten person dungeon Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout per day. These members of Blue Brook Guild had, of course, used this chance.

Just as the Blue Brook Guild’s party was wiped out, Ye Xiu had already lead Happy’s party to a victory against the sixth wave, far outpacing Blue Brook Guild. They hadn’t even had a single casualty yet. This was thanks to Ye Xiu’s leadership, of course.

For example, where the Blue Brook Guild had accidentally pulled nine Sealed Mountain Thieves, Ye Xiu had thought of the possibility of these hidden dangers and told everyone to pay close attention. They then managed to avoid such a fatal mistake.

The characteristics of Sealed Mountain Thieves was something Ye Xiu was observing continuously. Whenever he figured something out, he would naturally warn everyone. Their methods became more and more refined, so the battles naturally became smoother and faster.

After a while, they finally arrived at the first checkpoint of the Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout, where there would definitely be a boss: Sealed Mountain Vanguard, Brother Wolf. They didn’t know if the name was the bosses actual name, or just some sort of title, and they weren’t interested in finding out either. The name wouldn’t affect the power of the boss, after all.

Against a boss they knew nothing about, they had to extremely cautious. The ten didn’t rush forwards, but instead got a good look at their surrounds from every possible angle to see if there was anything in the environment that might interrupt the flow of their battle. Then, they checked if there was anything special about the terrain and if they could use it to their advantage. Last but not least, they couldn’t forget to check out the boss itself. Though they couldn’t click into its profile and check its equipment it used like they could with a player, they could still figure out what sort of class it was from looking over its equipment and weapons.

In the end, Sealed Mountain Vanguard, Brother Wolf seemed extremely powerful from this point of view. A sword hung from his belt on the left, there was a gun in a holster on the right, and his right hand was clenched around a two meter long spear… Just from the weapons, this guy had crossed three major classes, continuing on with the shamelessness that were common among bosses.

"I doubt he can use magic attacks…" Wei Chen commented. Brother Wolf seemed to be a physical fighter. Casting spells while holding a spear was something only players did. NPCs were very loyal to their individual classes, proudly bearing the weapons of their classes.

"Hm, everyone keep your distance for now and let me test him out first. Ranged characters can provide the appropriate cover," Ye xiu began to order.

After looking over the terrain, Wu Chen had long since picked an appropriate point to attack from. For ranged fighters like Launchers, there wasn’t much of a need for movement in PvE. At most, they just needed a spot where they could get closer and back away when needed, ensuring maximum firepower coverage when the boss was pulled by the other players.

Chen Guo naturally knew this as well, but she wasn’t nearly as confident as Wu Chen. She was even worried about messing up when fighting normal monsters. Now that they were at a boss, she was even more nervous. Seeing Wu Chen pick a spot, Chen Guo wasn’t sure what to do. It was a good thing that Ye Xiu’s voice rang out, giving her a place to stand and helping her calm down.

For Wei Chen, there was no need for Ye Xiu to worry about him. Seeing everyone stand in their respective places, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim charge at the boss.

Brother Wolf had a wide aggro range, and his reactions were very fast. Just as Lord Grim stepped into range, Brother Wolf had already partly turned, lifting the spear in his right hand and swinging it despite the distance.

Ye Xiu saw this clearly and hurriedly rolled. Looking back, he didn’t see any hint of an attack. Brother Wolf had already straightened his spear and began to charge over.

So that action had been nothing but a feint, and not an attack. This small mistake didn’t affect his mood. They were pioneering, after all. This sort of mistake was better than getting killed outright for being reckless.

The spear held by Brother Wolf was a total of two meters in length. He held it by the base with one hand as he quickly rushed over. As soon as he was in range, the spear was swung down in an arc. This swing wasn’t a Battle Mage technique, and was probably just a normal attack. However, this was a boss’ attack, so Ye Xiu didn’t dare to assume anything. What Ye Xiu had Lord Grim do wasn’t the ingenious sidestep and counterattack that he would usually do when PKing, but a direct roll onto the ground, rolling three times and dodging by several body units.

This sort of dodge seemed extremely exaggerated, like he had been scared witless. However, as the spear hit the ground, everyone realized what a smart move Ye Xiu had made. When the boss’ spear hit the ground, there was a thunderous sound and an immense shockwave spread from the point of contact. The ground was instantly filled with cracks. If Lord Grim had just sidestepped it, who knew what would happen to him upon being struck by this shockwave?

However, being a punching bag wasn’t Ye Xiu’s style. As soon as the attack missed, he had already raised his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella and sent out three Anti-Tank Missiles with a resounding boom.

Bosses had better AIs than normal monsters, occasionally using some method of dodging. As the Anti-Tank Missiles approached, Brother Wolf didn’t dodge. Instead, he swung his spear and was immediately swallowed by the resulting explosion, having destroyed the missiles.

Yet, Lord Grim had already closed in with a Slide Kick at this time. Brother Wolf had swung his spear up, so his lower half was left open to attack, resulting in the Slide Kick meeting its target.

If one timed it right, a Slide Kick could knock down its target, but Brother Wolf wasn’t moved by the Slide Kick. Ye Xiu wasn’t too surprised. Lord Grim had already jumped up from the Slide Kick and separated his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella into two, setting it against his arms and throwing out a Back Throw.

Under level suppression, even grabs could easily be shrugged off. The current Lord Grim was unfortunately experiencing such a case. Luckily, Ye Xiu’s reaction speed was god-level. When the skill activated and had no effect on its target, he immediately realized it had been shrugged off and quickly cancelled the skill before retreating.

Brother Wolf reaction speed was boss level as well, sending his palm out with a step forward, in the style of a Battle Mage’s Falling Flower Palm. This Brother Wolf knew some Battle Mage skills, as expected.

Brother Wolf’s Falling Flower Palm had a wide range, and it seemed that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to dodge it. In that moment, a streak of white light fell; it was a pre-prepared heal from An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands.

Everyone silently praised this move from An Wenyi’s. Yet, who would’ve thought that this Falling Flower Palm never managed to strike Lord Grim. Upon contact, he had realized something was wrong and quickly retreated. This swift reaction of Ye Xiu’s allowed him to completely dodge Wolf of Season’s counterattack. An Wenyi’s seemingly perfectly timed heal was, strictly speaking, a misjudgement.

It was clear that in terms of judgement, An Wenyi was currently not at Ye Xiu’s level.

Having dodged, Lord Grim swerved to Brother Wolf’s side to attack. A level 70 character and a level 75 dungeon boss became entangled in a one on one fight just like that. If any normal player saw this, they would be surprised enough to eat their mouse. However, everyone in Happy was used to it. Even Chen Guo wasn’t worried.

After a few exchanges, everyone could tell that even Ye Xiu was struggling a little. Little Cold Hands’ healing had a few chances to shine soon enough.

Yet, Ye Xiu slowly figured out Brother Wolf through these exchanges and after observing for a while, Wei Chen and Wu Chen began to provide firepower as support. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was no longer where he had been before, but had instead gone to support with his Ghost Boundaries.

Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion had also gotten into a Brawler’s range, holding a brick and moving around in an attempt to get behind Brother Wolf. Finally managing to hit his target, he didn’t even have the chance to celebrate before Brother Wolf recovered from his dizziness. Bosses originally had a powerful resistance against status effects. Now, with the addition of this level suppression, what status effects they could manage were far too short to take advantage of. At most, it could only interrupt the boss’ attacks.

"Ok, that’s about good, prepare for battle everyone. Listen carefully to my commands. When I tell you to scatter, retreat in your own directions, at least four body units, and be quick about it," Ye Xiu ordered.

"Understood," Everyone replied. Tang Rou was impatient to get in on the action, already commanding Soft Mist to charging, but it was Mo Fan’s Deception who was even faster. Streaking forwards, a combination of attacks instantly slammed into Brother Wolf.

Chapter 861: Clear Calculation

Blood splattered out from Brother Wolf. Ye Xiu had already experienced this attack before. Even though it couldn’t be said that he had completely grasped the boss’s attack patterns, he had figured out the most crucial points. As for a few other issues, their team was good enough to deal with them.

The ones who had trouble, such as Chen Guo and Luo Ji, happened to be long-ranged classes who could attack from afar. As long as the situation was under control, as long as the two of them didn’t cause too much trouble, they wouldn’t encounter any problems.

Next, they needed to calculate whether their current team could deal enough damage to finish the boss or not.

According to general knowledge, during this period of time, the DPS would certainly be lacking. The team members needed to slowly accumulate new pieces of equipment and improve the strength of their characters before they could reduce the pressure. Right now, their team faced a five level suppression. In terms of DPS, it wasn’t possible for them not to feel the pressure.

For normal players, attempting to clear a Level 75 ten player dungeon at Level 70 was extremely difficult. Team Happy didn’t consist of normal players though. In the first place, the skill level of their team members far surpassed that of normal players. No matter the game, DPS depended on equipment and player’s skill. Glory was a game that paid particular attention to skill. The importance of a player’s skill didn’t need to be said. Under a skilled player’s hands, the damage output naturally couldn’t compare to a normal player’s.　

Another point was that Team Happy’s class composition could be considered extremely arrogant.　　

Take Blue Brook Guild’s dungeon team for example. Their team consisted of two main tanks, three healers, and only five DPS classes. Pioneering required caution, so Blue Brook Guild had brought three healers, but even when the dungeon became figured out, teams rarely brought a solo healer for a ten player dungeon, unless in some extremely rare scenarios where the boss could be handled with just one healer. A vast majority of the time, two or more healers were required.　　

But Happy? The main tank was Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, who relied on damage output to keep the aggro on himself. He was a tank that wasn’t actually a tank. In addition, the only healer was An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands. To succeed with this recklessness, they had to rely on superior skill. By having the team members defend against the boss’s attacks using their own abilities, the pressure on the healer would lessen significantly. Normal players wouldn’t be able to do this. When they dodged around, let alone if it was even effective, they might crash into each other and mess up their positioning.

But for Happy? Their melee classes left each other plenty of room to attack and dodge. None of them held each other back. The tacit understanding between them gained from practice could be seen. Everyone underwent professional level practice every day. This practice wasn’t just individual technical practice, but also team coordination practice.

The only outlier was Mo Fan. This guy still didn’t consider himself a part of Team Happy. Ye Xiu and the others usually didn’t call for him during their team practices, so at this moment, Mo Fan appeared to be off-beat. Everyone else acted as a whole, but he seemed to be an outsider. The switches between attack and defense were completely done by him. His pacing was his own. It seemed quite dissonant. Fortunately, he skill level was solid. Even though he wasn’t in tune with the others, he wouldn’t go so far as to cause trouble for them.

Ye Xiu had considered these problems earlier. When he formed the team to dungeon, he wasn’t just here to sightsee. However, there was no information on the boss, so he needed to make an evaluation when the moment came.　　

After observing their efforts for a while, he felt like there was hope.

"Our DPS is a bit lacking. Everyone pay attention to your pacing and timing." Ye Xiu said.

At this point, no one here was a noob, so these instructions were clear enough. In the past, Ye Xiu needed to give Tang Rou or Steamed Bun a more detailed explanation by what he meant by pacing or timing. Now, he just needed to communicate the general concept and everyone would know intuitively. In particular, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but sigh emotionally at the eye-catching performance of Tang Rou and Steamed Bun.　　

Under Ye Xiu’s guidance and ability to hold aggro, the ensuing battle went without mishap. Everyone understood that the situation had been stabilized. Next, they would need to carefully be on guard for when the boss’s health dropped into the red. After red health, bosses would always undergo a transformation. It was a feature in Glory. The transformation didn’t necessarily make the battle more intense. There were bosses that tried to run away when reaching red blood. For these types of bosses, if you ran farther away in preparation for the boss to go berserk, you would be the one to suffer. The other side’s big move was to run away. If you hid, wouldn’t it be the same as doing all that work for nothing? 　

However, it was currently their first time running this dungeon. Keeping their life was the much more important. Even if they had to let Brother Wolf escape, it would still count as passing this checkpoint, allowing them to continue advancing through the dungeon.

As a result, when Brother Wolf’s health was almost at 10%, Ye Xiu decisively ordered for all of the melee classes to temporarily withdraw.

"Pay attention to his health. Have a good understanding of your damage output!" After seeing Soft Mist and the other melee classes retreat, Ye Xiu reminded the long-ranged classes, who were still attacking.

"As long as your eyes don’t go blurry, we’ll be fine." Wei Chen said.

"Concealed Light, have your summons pull back for now too." Ye Xiu said.

Luo Ji carried out the order and immediately retracted his four melee summons.

"Get ready to place an Ice Boundary. When the boss reaches red blood, cast it." Ye Xiu instructed.

"Understood." Qiao Yifan affirmed.

"Chasing Haze, stop attacking for now." Ye Xiu calculated Brother Wolf’s health. His Lord Grim needed to maintain his grasp over Brother Wolf’s aggro, so he obviously couldn’t retreat like Soft Mist and the others. As a result, he needed to escape as soon as Brother Wolf’s health fell to 10%. Thus, once Brother Wolf’s health reached a certain point, they needed to calculate the damage so he could grasp the escape timing.

"Old Wei, prepare a Hexagram Prison.

"Dawn Rifle, are your high-level skills off cooldown? Use Satellite Beam as the final hit." Ye Xiu continued to arrange.　　

"Okay." Wu Chen’s grasp of the rhythm had always been very good. He checked his skill bar. Satellite Beam was already up.　　

"Get ready. Everyone run far away and scatter. Don’t group together. Get ready to use your life-saving skills at any moment. Little Hands, take care of yourself before healing anyone else." Ye Xiu gave his final words of instruction. Brother Wolf’s health had already reached a crucial point.　　

"Everyone stop attacking."

The battlefield instantly became empty. Only Brother Wolf was waving his spear, attacking Lord Grim. This guy had three weapons on him. Everyone initially thought that he was one of those shameless bosses with more than three classes. They had been prepared to guard against a sudden sword strike or a sudden gunshot.

But none of that ever happened. That sword and gun just seemed to be ornaments on the boss.

"Dawn Rifle!" After everyone stopped, Ye Xiu shouted.　　

"Understood." Wu Chen was prepared, but because he had to coordinate with Lord Grim’s escape, he needed to wait for Ye Xiu’s order. As soon as he heard the order, he immediately released the attack. In the sky, a mirror seemed to flash with light. The light grew bigger and bigger until a Satellite Beam descended on the ground precisely on Brother Wolf.

Ice Boundary!

Hexagram Prison!

One Inch Ash’s ice Boundary and Windward Formation’s control curse instantly appeared.　

Ice rose from the ground. Tiny pieces of shattered ice rushed towards Brother Wolf. Because of the level suppression, the damage and the effects were greatly reduced. In addition, boss’s had outstanding resistance, so many skills became ineffective. However, there was still a little bit of leeway. If not, wouldn’t bosses be impossible to kill?　

Vanguard Brother Wolf excelled at close combat. He had powerful attacks and outstanding defense, but his magic resistance was rather weak. Ice magic and control curses were the most effective.

These two skills chained one after the other to give Lord Grim more time to escape.

Ye Xiu wouldn’t be careless. The instant he yelled "Dawn Rifle!" Lord Grim jumped away using the shockwave from an Anti-Tank Missile to fly farther away from Brother Wolf. Then, he turned around and used Shadow Clone Technique. It still wasn’t enough, so he rolled several times, while adjusting his camera so he could see Brother Wolf.

What was that sound?

Ye Xiu wondered. When he ran, the instant that Satellite Beam descended, he seemed to have heard a clear sound. Was it from Brother Wolf’s transformation? When he looked back, Brother Wolf was still Brother Wolf, but the spear in his hands had broken. The tip of the spear was pierced into the ground. That clear sound was probably when the spear snapped or when the tip fell. Those were the only two possibilities.

"This is...." Ye Xiu was baffled by this weird move. Brother Wolf finally didn’t disappoint. He grabbed the weapons that everyone had been regarding as ornaments.

With a roar, Brother Wolf tore through the Hexagram Prison and trampled over the ice on the ground. He moved extremely quickly. His sword was pointed in Dawn Rifle’s direction.

When Ye Xiu saw this scene, he had pretty much figured out Brother Wolf’s Enraged mode.

Switching weapons was equivalent to switching classes. After falling to red blood, Brother Wolf’s attack patterns would be completely different.

Moving quickly meant that his stats had been buffed. This type of Enraged mode was very common among bosses, especially small bosses, which liked to have these simple Enrages.

He was pointing as Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle because his aggro had been reset. The reset was there to give trouble to players, testing their ability to react to sudden changes.

These three changes weren’t anything new. Everyone saw these changes and let out a sigh of relief. How could an aggro reset be a problem for a team at their level? Wu Chen calmly jumped backwards and fired. As he attacked, he had Dawn Rifle head towards Lord Grim, so he could bring the boss back under Lord Grim’s control.　

Who would have thought that, at this moment, a sword would flash and an extremely quick sword slash would fly out.

Dawn Rifle’s artillery shell exploded in midair. Blood splattered wildly from all over his body. Brother Wolf was behind him.

Chapter 862: First Kill!

Downwind Sword Slash!

It was only after Brother Wolf executed this attack did everyone regain their composure. They recognized this skill. It was the Blade Master’s Downwind Sword Slash. However, it wasn’t possible for it to be this fast in the hands of a player.

Dawn Rifle had used Aerial Fire and his attention had been focused on Brother Wolf in front of him. However, when this attack came, Dawn Rifle wasn’t able to react at all because the attack was just too swift. The sword light rose and fell, leaving only a straight line. As soon as the artillery shell was chopped down, he was also cut.

He was injured, but he didn’t die. An Wenyi immediately had his Little Cold Hands cast a heal. He reacted quickly, but his hands couldn’t keep up. In the end, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was the first to heal Dawn Rifle.

And at the same time, Lord Grim immediately rushed forward. Brother Wolf wasn’t finished with just one attack. He turned again to give Dawn Rifle another cut. Lord Grim didn’t have an aggro skill like Provoke, which made things a lot more difficult at dire moments. He could only use control skills to bring Brother Wolf away, so Dawn Rifle could escape.　

Unexpectedly, before Lord Grim rushed forward, someone else was even faster.

Tang Rou!

With a Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Soft Mist charged at Brother Wolf like lightning. Although her speed couldn’t compare to Brother Wolf’s Downwind Sword Slash, it was very prompt. When Brother Wolf’s sword fell, Soft Mist had already arrived. The fairly intelligent boss made a calculation. He turned around and blocked Soft Mist’s spear with his sword.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks had an extremely high priority, but a boss was still a boss. That simple slash was able to block Soft Mist’s spear.

Grinding sounds could be heard from the collision between the sword and spear. The spear may have been blocked, but the momentum from Dragon Breaks the Ranks hadn’t stopped. Brother Wolf’s feet didn’t move, but he was still pushed back by the assault. His two feet left two deep grooves in the ground.

Clouds of dust billowed. Dragon Breaks the Ranks was finally stopped. Both Soft Mist and Brother Wolf stood still. Suddenly, a person flew out from the clouds of dust directly towards Brother Wolf’s neck with a glint of light.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

This person was Deception, of course. However, NPCs could not feel fear or surprise. A normal player would have certainly had trouble defending against such a sudden attack, but for a boss, it was no different from an attack from his feet. Brother Wolf retracted his sword and blocked Deception’s ninja blade. Then, he pushed outwards and sent Deception flying backwards.

Mo Fan refused to give up. Deception used a Shadow Clone Technique in the air. His clones continued to fly outwards, while his real body moved to Brother Wolf’s side.

The effects of Shadow Clone Technique towards NPCs were different. Players could deduce the real one depending on the circumstances, but NPCs were different. NPCs that could distinguish between the clones were extremely special. Brother Wolf clearly didn’t have this capability. He was tricked by the Shadow Clone Technique and ignored the the real one behind him, which resulted in him eating Deception’s Bird Fall.

But for a boss, even if he was already at red blood, eating one or two skills didn’t matter too much. After taking damage, Brother Wolf turned around and slashed. Mo Fan reacted quickly. As soon as he saw that the situation wasn’t looking good, he immediately withdrew. Deception didn’t continue attacking and retreated instead.

During this time, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had arrived. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear and attacked three times followed by a Circle Swing, throwing Brother Wolf to the ground.

Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle was finally out of the danger zone. He still felt some lingering fear after recalling what had just happened. That attack had been too fast. Even if he had been on guard against that attack, Wu Chen didn’t have the confidence that he would have been able to dodge it.

Now, who knew if Brother Wolf would use that skill again. Ye Xiu hastily asked Wu Chen how much damage he had taken from that attack and then rearranged their formation. Those with the possibility of being instantly killed were placed outside of this attack’s range. As for those inside range, the Cleric would need to keep their health up.

As expected, after fighting for a bit, Brother Wolf once again used the same move. His sword light flashed in a straight line and blood blossomed from Steamed Bun Invasion.

This time, Steamed Bun Invasion took the attack. Steamed Bun also wasn’t able to dodge it, and from the looks of it, the target for this skill was random. It wasn’t according to who held the aggro.

But now that the team was prepared for it, they didn’t panic. Little Cold Hands cast an Emergency Heal onto Steamed Bun Invasion. The others rushed forward to protect him, blocking Brother Wolf’s attack.

They had now experienced that Vanguard Brother Wolf had to offer. Apart from a bit of trouble from this extraordinary Downwind Sword Slash, this boss battle progressed without any suspense. 10% health was quickly reduced almost to zero.

"He’s almost dead. Everyone pay attention to surviving. Heal everyone to full health. Little Hands, focus." Ye Xiu said solemnly. There were bosses which liked to explode in their final moments. If they were going to die, they would bring others with them. These bosses were especially disgusting, particularly in a dungeon because it directly affected a player’s progress.

"Understood." An Wenyi replied. He carefully healed everyone’s health back to full and prepared to use Emergency Heal at any moment.

"Okay, everyone retreat!" Just like when the boss was about to reach red blood, everyone withdrew ahead of time, creating a buffer for when the boss fell. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim faced it on his own, while Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle prepared to make the last hit.

"Get ready!" Ye Xiu yelled.

Wu Chen wound up his high-level skill.

"Release!"

As soon as the order came, a final Satellite Beam descended. Lord Grim hastily ran back. Everything was the same as before. Brother Wolf’s health fell rapidly from this Satellite Beam, but when his health fell to 1 hitpoint, it stopped.

It was unlikely for Satellite Beam to be a tad bit off. Everyone instantly understood the implications.

"Everyone, find cover! He’s about to make a move!" Ye Xiu shouted.　　

Everyone found a rock or a tree to hide behind. They had been on guard, so they were naturally prepared. Everyone instantly found cover. It only seemed dangerous for Lord Grim, who was still the closest among them. However, Ye Xiu was the most experienced and skilled among them.

On the verge of collapse, Brother Wolf dropped his sword to the ground and pulled out the gun on his waist.

Sure enough, everything on Brother Wolf had their uses. Was he going to use this gun for his final attack? What would the attack be like? Because they had no information on it, Ye Xiu chose to use this kind of defensive strategy. If not, he would need to figure out how to shrug off the boss’s final move.

Everyone watched Brother Wolf attentively. He didn’t seem to have intentions of chasing after anyone, letting them relax a bit. Then, they saw Brother Wolf struggle to raise the gun high into the air with his right hand and with a bang, a bright signal flare shot into the sky. The signal flare exploded into fireworks and Brother Wolf fell.

Before anyone could comment on it, a system announcement came: Congratulations to Guild Happy for the First Kill on Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout’s Vanguard Brother Wolf.

The system announcement wasn’t given to just the people in Team Happy. From the astonished expressions that popped up all over the global chat, they could tell that this announcement had been made in the global chat.

For a Level 75 dungeon, announcements wouldn’t only be made for just the First Clear. A system announcement would also be made for every boss, including minibosses. According to Glory’s rules, extra rewards would be given out for this achievement.

But players didn’t even have time to be envious of what these rewards were. It was only 1:21 AM. Only an hour had passed since the update. Because there were so many players, people were having trouble receiving quests and even hitting a new monster yet someone had actually complete a First Kill?

This... had to be the fastest First Kill in Glory history right? In the past, the entire dungeon needed to be cleared before a system announcement would be made, while this time it was just for killing a boss. Even so, no player thought that this had ever happened before.

Even for the elite club guild teams, they had entered the dungeon, but all of them carried with them a mentality of feeling out the dungeon and cherishing the cooldown for each run. No one actually thought that anyone could get through the dungeon or even kill a boss.

But now, such a bloody thing had happened in front of their eyes. A team had actually killed the first boss in one of the ten player dungeons already. An achievement that they had never imagined had been completed in front of them.

All of the Club guilds felt their faces drain of color. The First Clears and dungeon records had always been theirs. Normal players would never even think about touching them, but now, they had yet to even get a good grasp of the dungeon, when a First Kill had been achieved.

And it just so happened that Guild Happy had sent out a recruiting notice, which matched the timing of this system announcement, attracting many eyes.

The club guilds were so angry that their noses were askew.

If it was another team, then it was fine, but who didn’t know about Happy’s situation? Happy had Ye Qiu and was currently participating in the Challenger League, daring to face against Excellent Era. They had to be at a pro level, no? Pro-level players running to dungeon? Wasn’t that just bullying them? Their pro players were disciplined and didn’t stay online overnight to play the game! If not, did you think that if these dungeons could be beat by your team, then these dungeons would trouble top teams like Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Tyranny?

The club guilds were furious! They could do it too, but they had no way of doing so. And these guys did it without knowing their places and were actually using it to advertise themselves! It was just too improper!　　

The club guilds cursed silently, but they had no way of stopping players from discussing the matter fervently. The club guilds saw it as an improper First Kill, but the players regarded it as the most stunning First Kill in all of Glory history. The club guilds wanted to write all sorts of slander in order to vent their anger.

God, can you just deal with the Challenger League! Can you not keep running to the game and messing up the balance of things?

Chapter 863: DPS Chart

The club guild leaders assembled once more, but this time, they could only vent their frustrations. They had no way of solving the problem. Happy’s team was in the dungeon. Apart from the system itself, who could stop them from conquering this dungeon? Within the first hour, the first boss had been killed. What about two hours later? Three? Four... if this continued on unhindered, tonight would become Happy’s day of celebration. It was the busiest night of the year. Who knew how many people would remember Happy’s name?

Jealousy and envy!　　

The guild leaders gnashed their teeth. According to the recent reports, as soon as the First Kill record announcement and the recruit notice came out, Guild Happy, as well as their subordinates, Guild Everlasting, quickly reached the maximum guild member application limit.　　

To some players, the attractiveness of the First Kill could be considered as even more tempting than a beautiful performance by a team.　　

When a team performed well, players would at most be delighted in spirit, but when a guild claimed a First Kill, apart from pride, it also proved their guild’s superior strength. Being inside this kind of guild might provide opportunities for them to surpass other players. Even if they couldn’t squeeze into that level of a team, if that superior team obtained equipment from a dungeon and didn’t need it, it would be placed in the guild storage.　

It would take time for normal players to have the opportunity to challenge ten player dungeons. They needed to level and find level 75 equipment from five player dungeons. But with these conditions, they could directly get ten player dungeon equipment from the guild storage. The temptation was enormous for numerous players.

The main leaders of Happy were still in the dungeon. The recruit notice had been announced, but the work needed for accepting applicants wouldn’t immediately begin. A system announcement after killing just the first boss also surprised them at first. Afterwards, they remembered to check the boss’s corpse for the loot that he dropped.

Compared to a five player dungeon, the equipment quality in raids would always be better. Even for Purple and Blue equipment, the stats of raid equipment were more outstanding. In addition, five player dungeons had a higher Blue equipment drop rate, while raids had a much higher Purple equipment drop rate. As the number of participating players increased, if the equipment drop rate was too low, many wouldn’t get anything. As a result, the overall equipment drop rate in raids was far higher than in five player dungeons.

In ten player dungeons, it was normal for a boss to drop two pieces of equipment. In 20 player dungeons, every boss was guaranteed to drop at least three pieces of equipment. It was even possible to get four with enough luck. In 50 player dungeons, every boss could drop between six and eight pieces of equipment. In 100 player dungeons, if every boss didn’t drop twelve to sixteen pieces of equipment, how could a 100 player dungeons be worth the effort?

Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout was a ten player dungeon. The probability of a boss dropping two pieces of equipment was quite high.

After reflecting on the First Kill announcement, everyone realizing that they could check the loot that dropped, which was undoubtedly very fun to do. Chen Guo was already asking impatiently "Who’s going who’s going?" By her tone of voice, she was clearly waiting for someone to say "You can go." She prepared to immediately go forward and check.

But Ye Xiu wasn’t in a hurry. He suddenly posted a chart in the team chat.

Everyone took a look. It was the DPS chart for this section. In the past, these statistics could only be checked after clearing the dungeon. However, it seemed like Level 75 dungeons had made some changes to the base of the game itself. Not only was there a First Kill record for just the first boss, it seemed like the DPS chart could be checked at any time.

"The DPS chart can be checked in between stages!" Ye Xiu immediately brought up the topic. It couldn’t be checked at any time, but in stages after a boss was killed.

"Everyone, take a look." Ye Xiu said, "Usually, I would tell everyone to learn from whoever’s first, but today, I don’t need to say anything further."

In first place, it was obviously Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. He relied on DPS to establish aggro, so how could his DPS not be the highest? Lord Grim’s current Level 55 Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was equivalent to a Level 60 Orange weapon. The stats were ten levels lower than everyone else’s weapon. Unspecialized didn’t have any single hit high-damage skills. Under this condition, Lord Grim still being number one was simply a display of his skill.

After Ye Xiu, number two was Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle and then Wei Chen’s Windward Formation.　　

In terms of equipment, Wei Chen’s Windward Formation was number one. He had a Level 70 Silver weapon and three pieces of Silver equipment from Everlasting. In the Challenger League, he could be considered a cockroach. However, Warlocks weren’t high DPS classes to begin with, so in the DPS charts, he couldn’t compare to a pure DPS class like Dawn Rifle’s Launcher. 　　

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion followed next.

There was a fair gap in the DPS of these two compared to the three in front. Because of the team composition, melee classes needed to dodge attacks in order to reduce the pressure on the healer, so they naturally couldn’t focus purely on dealing damage like the long-ranged classes. Ye Xiu could dodge while outputting damage, but Tang Rou and Steamed Bun didn’t have the skill.

　

At sixth place was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. He wasn’t far behind Soft Mist and Steamed Bun. For a supportive Phantom Demon, that was quite impressive.

These three were in the second group of the DPS chart. The players in the third group appeared as if they were leechers. Then again, Concealed Light and Chasing Haze were sandbagging in order to coordinate with the team. Ye Xiu had instructed Luo Ji to only use four summons to deal damage. Under this command, no matter how skilled the player might be, his damage would definitely be limited. As for Chasing Haze, Chen Guo was scared of messing up the team’s rhythm, so she often took the initiative to sandbag, so her performance was naturally subpar.

The most surprising was Mo Fan’s Deception. This guy’s skill was solid. Deception’s equipment wasn’t bad either, but he was actually in the third group along with the sandbaggers Concealed Light and Chasing Haze. Everyone stuck their heads out and looked at him. They wanted to see what kind of expression this usually cold and indifferent guy had.

Especially after Ye Xiu said in a serious tone: "Ahem. For those with a low DPS and without any particular reason, try harder!"

These words were obviously directed at Mo Fan because Luo Ji and Chen Guo had "particular reasons", but for Mo Fan’s Deception, with his skill and eagerness, it was quite surprising to see such depressing damage output.

Everyone looked at Mo Fan. Sure enough, Mo Fan’s expression was especially gloomy, but he still didn’t say anything. His two eyes were filled with confusion though. He wasn’t sure why his DPS was so low.

Mo Fan was the only person sitting alone. No one could see what he was doing. After Ye Xiu said these words, he didn’t expand on it and asked: "Who wants to check the loot?"

"Me me!" Chen Guo eagerly jumped up. Chasing Haze ran over. She quietly prayed to herself, even though she didn’t really know what equipment this dungeon dropped.

"Two pieces!" Chasing Haze crouched and searched the body. Chen Guo could already see what the equipment was and first reported the number.　　

"One purple, one blue!" Then, she reported their quality.

Even though it was a raid, it still wouldn’t be easy to get Orange equipment to drop.

"What are they?" Everyone was already getting impatient and started asking questions one after the other.

"Uh, not good..." Chen Guo could see what had been dropped and said gloomily. Then, she posted the stats of the two pieces of equipment in chat for everyone to see.

The pieces of equipment were obviously Level 75. Getting a Purple one was already quite lucky. Chen Guo said not good because none of these pieces of equipment suited any of the classes on their team.

"It’s no big deal. We can just throw it in the guild storage!" Ye Xiu didn’t care. Their team all had a set of Orange equipment. Level 75 was a higher level, but the color mattered. Level 75 Purple equipment was at the same level as Level 70 Orange equipment. So for Level 75 equipment, they needed Orange ones for them to be upgrades. For Purple equipment, it would depend on the stats. As for Blue equipment, there was no need to look at it at all! To normal players, Blue equipment just passed the minimum standard. For competitive teams, it was definitely too lacking.

"Okay, let’s continue! Everyone, work hard at dealing more damage!" Ye Xiu announced loudly. Everyone heard his words. Wasn’t he still pointing at Mo Fan? After all, apart from him, everyone else had performed quite well. Chen Guo and Luo Ji had certain restrictions, yet they were still on the same level as Mo Fan’s Deception.

As a result, everyone couldn’t help but glance at Mo Fan again. This quiet guy looked very determined now as if he were holding back a burst of energy.

The ten players advanced deeper towards Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout. Before the second checkpoint, more Sealed Mountain Thieves that hadn’t been seen before appeared, but with the team’s skill level, they quickly figured it out and passed through it. The more they got used to these monsters, the easier it became. Only An Wenyi was nervous. He had never healed an MT like Lord Grim before! This guy kept dodging around. He did evade large amounts of damage, but the problem was that even so, An Wenyi had to watch him attentively. What if he suddenly made a mistake?

The path to the second checkpoint progressed faster than the path to the first checkpoint. Around thirty minutes later, the group reached the second boss.

Defense Commander Sand Leopard.

This boss was once again unfamiliar, so the team employed the same strategy as before. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim went forward to probe it out. After everyone observed the boss’s patterns, they would immediately swarm it.

Mo Fan’s Deception was positioned towards the front of the pack. Compared to before, he was a lot more active. He clearly wanted to use the second checkpoint to prove his worth. In the path towards here, he had been especially diligent, but everyone knew that in dungeons, the hardest part was the boss. The stats for DPS mainly came from the boss. The damage dealt to small monsters wasn’t much. It wasn’t possible to deal enough damage to small monsters to become part of the team’s main force.

Even though Mo Fan operated alone, it wasn’t like he had never dungeoned before. There was no way he didn’t understand this reasoning.

Chapter 864: Defense Commander Sand Leopard

The second boss, Defense Commander Sand Leopard, didn’t have three different weapons hanging on him to make players worried like Brother Wolf. Sand Leopard held a sword in one hand and a shield in the other, a typical set of equipment for a Knight.

This class was one of the most annoying NPCs for players to deal with.

For one, Knights were very tanky, and their Spirit wasn’t shabby either, giving them a well-rounded defense. For another, a Knight’s aggro pulling skills, like Provoke and Roar, was an immense disturbance on the field. Uncontrolled attacks and movements while working in a team could easily cause the situation to slip from their grasp. In addition, bosses often had more than one class, and the Healer classes Cleric and Paladin were both under the same class type as Knights. If the boss had healing skills, that would be even more devastating for players.

It was especially so under the current circumstances. It was already very difficult since it was a new dungeon and they were coming in with very little knowledge and a large gap in levels. This kind of boss put a lot more pressure on their DPS.

After having Lord Grim go up to try the boss out, it was evident that this Sand Leopard was definitely a Knight class. Lord Grim’s attacks seemed to do nothing, especially when that shield was used to defend.

"We’ll have to take this one slow." Though it might be hard to deal with, with Ye Xiu’s skill, he easily found a solution. "Compared to the last one, we’ll have to carefully note the quality and efficiency of our DPS; we can’t let our guard down for a second."

"One Inch Ash has a large responsibility this time. Stat boosts should be precise to get the maximum effect; try to not waste even a moment." Ye Xiu began to order.

"Understood," Qiao Yifan agreed.

"Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion should take care to cooperate with the support from the Ghost Boundaries."

"Chasing Haze has to be more open with her attacks. As for Concealed Light, summon some creatures with powerful offensive capabilities, but considering efficiency and mana consumption, limit your summons to five or less. Otherwise, it might cause unnecessary waste."

"Don’t worry, we’re going slow. Efficiency is key. We must be efficient," Ye Xiu emphasized in the end.

"What if he has healing skills? We would need rapid DPS to suppress that. If the pace is too slow, we might not be able to hold on," Wei Chen asked.

"Let’s see if we can interrupt them first! If we can’t, then we’ll cross that bridge when we get there." Ye Xiu had obviously not missed that point, but only just estimated a possibility. If there was a possibility, then they should prioritize interrupting his heals.

"You’ll do the interrupting?" Wei Chen asked.

"I’ll do it." Ye Xiu accepted the responsibility.

Soon enough, the battle officially began. When Ye Xiu was testing the boss out with Lord Grim, Sand Leopard had only revealed his immense defensive capabilities. As for aggro and healing skills, they never appeared so far, probably because it was just a one on one and there was no reason to use them. Now that everyone had joined in, the situation might change.

Aggro skills could only be dealt with via a character’s spirit or a counter-skill. This sort of skill wasn’t something that Team Happy’s current line-up possessed, so there wasn’t much to say. If he really used an aggro skill, then they’d deal with it once they figured out who the victim was.

In the end, the situation was better than Ye Xiu had dared imagine. Aggro skills never appeared, and heals did, though they could be interrupted. With Ye Xiu’s skill, Sand Leopard’s heals might as well have been nonexistent. The biggest problem Ye Xiu ran into was steadying the aggro through DPS while attacking from the front, where Sand Leopard held his shield.

This sort of DPS method of pulling aggro would put great pressure on him if the boss OTed. Since they didn’t have any aggro skills, they would have to create another OT if he wanted to force the aggro back onto himself. However, OT situations had requirements. It wasn’t as if an OT would follow immediately once one character had pulled more aggro than another. If that actually happened then all they had to do was use similar DPS to control the aggro and then just see-saw. If two ranged characters attacked one after another with this sort of pace, then they would be able to get the boss to just run around aimlessly between them.

So under normal circumstances, to cause an OT, one needed to pull a certain percent more aggro than the current target. If you wanted to use an OT to negate an OT, you would need quite a while to accomplish it, even if the OT target stopped attacking. Ye Xiu’s caution was because he didn’t want something like that to occur, otherwise who knows what would happen during the chaos.

Everyone took their own role seriously, attacking according to the instructions Ye Xiu had given. Ye Xiu controlled the situation very well, too, holding the boss’s aggro steady. Seeing the boss’ health fall and everyone’s mana consumption, Ye Xiu was a little apprehensive. It seemed that it might be a bit of a stretch.

"Keep an eye on your pace of mana potion usage," Ye Xiu said. Unlike the Arena, the best thing about dungeons was that item usage was only limited by their cooldowns. With a good rhythm, potions could give an immense boost to their endurance in battle. Knowing that they were going into an all new dungeon levels above them, Ye Xiu and co had naturally prepared well for it, stocking up on potions for everyone. Now, chugging them down without hesitation wasn’t an option; they had to watch the efficiency of their potion usage as well.

Time slipped by and Sand Leopard’s health was also slipping away. This sort of endurance match was a test of the players’ stability and focus. After everyone had focused calmly and efficiently dealt damage for almost forty minutes, Sand Leopard’s health finally approached ten percent.

"As always, temporarily scatter, everyone. Dawn Rifle is going to be responsible for the last hit again." Facing an equally unknown Enraged State, they would naturally have to use the same tactics.

Seeing Sand Leopard’s health about to hit red, everyone retreated. As Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle landed the last hit, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had to swiftly retreat as well.

It was the Satellite Beam just as it was before. Sand Leopard raised his shield to block, but this defensive move had already been considered. Even with the shield reducing its damage, the Satellite Beam would still deplete Sand Leopard’s health to under ten percent.

Crack!

The sound of something shattering rang out.

The Satellite Beam had somehow managed to shatter the shield after hitting it. Everyone watched on, dumbstruck, recalling how the first Boss’ spear had also shattered upon reaching red blood. Was this dungeon using signals like this to tell the players that the boss was about to enter an enraged state?

What would Sand Leopard’s Enraged State be like?

Everyone’s eyes widened and saw Sand Leopard roaring. His now empty left hand gripped the hilt of his sword with his right hand. Red light flashed in his eyes as his body also glowed with red light; even his hair seemed to be lit up.

"Berserker?" Wei Chen’s experience wasn’t just for show. He had already made a judgement upon seeing the pose. This state seemed akin to the activation of the Berserker’s passive skill, Blood Awakening, when a Berserker’s health was low and entered a berserk state."I want to test it out first." Ye Xiu didn’t rely solely on this estimation, playing safe once more. After Lord Grim charged forward, what met him was a Sand Leopard whose speed and attack had been greatly boosted, as expected. With a few wild slashes, even Ye Xiu had to hurriedly get Lord Grim to roll around, becoming especially passive.

Ye Xiu was unphased, continuing this for a while. Seeing that Sand Leopard really didn’t have any other tricks up his sleeve, he immediately called for the others, "It’s a Berserker. Don’t hold back, everyone!"

Under this sort of circumstances, a Berserker’s offensive capabilities would be greatly improved, but their defensive capabilities would immensely suffer. This second boss had gone from one extreme to the other. At first, his defense was immense, but after reaching red blood, his offense had exploded.

Though they never encountered anything like Season Wolf’s last Downwind Sword Slash, this second boss was much harder to beat than Season Wolf. However, since most of the problems were dealt with by Lord Grim, the others weren’t too hindered. If it was someone else who was the MT, Sand Leopard would be tough enough to make someone’s heart stop.

With the boss’ defense greatly reduced, Sand Leopard’s wild style didn’t allow it to live very long. Under everyone’s furious attacks, his health was quickly depleted.

"Careful, hold your attacks!" Ye Xiu hastily yelled. Everyone simultaneously stopped, but Mo Fan’s Deception didn’t manage to, landing two skills on Sand Leopard and ending the battle.

Seeing Sand Leopard’s health empty, everyone let out a breath of relief. This boss luckily didn’t have any dirty last resort moves. Even so, Mo Fan’s mistake wasn’t overlooked. No one really liked this guy in the first place, so when something like this happened, not many showed sympathy, only scorn.

Mo Fan was clear about this as well. When everyone threw scornful looks his way, he didn’t look back at them, but he could feel it. He lowered his head subconsciously and his expression became a little awkward.

The system announcement rang out again, declaring that the second boss Defense Commander Sand Leopard had been defeated. The global chat exploded again and the heads of the big guilds gritted their teeth once more, cursing wildly, but helpless to change reality.

Chen Guo took the initiative in going forward to collect the dropped equipment. Once again, it was a blue and a purple piece, but they were of classes they could use. However, after checking their stats, they didn’t seem to be very worth it, compared to the Orange Equipment they already had anyways.

"Ai, why is there never any Orange equipment!" Chen Guo lamented, clearly knowing that this equipment wouldn’t help them increase their strength.

"We’ll get an Orange equipment soon enough," Ye Xiu chuckled.

"It’s not that easy!" Chen Guo rolled her eyes.

"We got two First Kills! For these types of rewards, orange equipment and rare materials aren’t uncommon," Ye Xiu said with a smile.

Chen Guo immediately realized what he was saying. Wild Boss rewards were a level above dungeon Bosses, or even Hidden Bosses, but dungeon record rewards were on the same level as Wild Boss rewards. Now that each Boss had a First Kill record, the real rewards would come when they cleared the dungeon!

Chen Guo was excited, but Ye Xiu didn’t linger on the thought any longer. He sent out the DPS Chart again, calmly saying, "Let’s have a look at the DPS chart for the second section."

Chapter 865: Tactician Snow Eagle

The DPS Chart could be viewed according to each specific sections. Usually when using this to estimate ability, it would be focused on the Boss fights, and disregard the damage dealt to normal mobs. If the normal monsters in the section were rather difficult to deal with and required some level of teamwork, then they might pull it out for a look as well.

The DPS Chart Ye Xiu had pulled up was in regards to the Boss fight against Defense Commander Sand Leopard. On the chart, Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle held the lead with Tang Rou’s Soft Mist following and then Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim who had been pulling aggro with DPS was, in the end, only ranked fourth on the chart.　　Under these circumstances, these three hadn’t caused an OT, clearly because despite their high DPS, their aggro wasn’t enough to cause an OT. As for Ye Xiu, if he could raise his DPS he would. However, since this boss hid behind a shield for a majority of the battle, he had met some problems facing the boss head on. Yet, these problems didn’t affect his aggro pulling at all, so he didn’t tell the others to hold back. With the chart in open view now, Wu Chen felt a moment of worry. His DPS was almost at the point of causing an OT. He hadn’t watched out for it and Ye Xiu hadn’t said anything either. Was it because he had carefully calculated that an OT wouldn’t happen? This god’s calculation and awareness was just too terrifying.

Ye Xiu didn’t care about this and didn’t say anything about it. After a glance, he said, "Ahem, what’s this? Deception, your DPS is even worse than last time!"

It was truly worse. This time, not counting the Cleric Little Cold Hands, Deception was ranked second to last, only above Chasing Haze by a little and somehow slightly worse than Luo Ji’s Concealed Light.

Everyone was clear on Luo Ji’s skill. No matter how bad Mo Fan was, it shouldn’t be this bad. With the chart out, everyone was shocked. Wei Chen, who was always willing to see the worst in Ye Xiu, even sent Ye Xiu a private message, "What did you do?"

"F*ck off!" Ye Xiu replied without hesitation.

"That’s not possible!" The ever silent Mo Fan actually yelled out with disbelief.

"You can take a look for yourself." Ye Xiu didn’t elaborate. The DPS Chart was something the game had built in and calculated by the system, so it wasn’t like Ye Xiu was the only one who could see it. Everyone opened the DPS chart and clicked on the section for the Boss battle against Defense Commander Sand Leopard, seeing how it was exactly the same as the one Ye Xiu sent. Deception was ranked second to last, not even above Concealed Light. Though the difference was minimal, he had been a league above Concealed Light and Chen Guo in the first Boss battle, despite all three of them seeming to be relying on others to carry them. This time, he had taken notice to improve, yet he hadn’t managed to improve at all, and had fallen to their level! No wonder he was so incredulous.　However, this was the system’s calculations and a harsh truth that they could only accept.　

"You can’t continue like this, loner! You gotta find a way to improve," Ye Xiu said with a hint of mockery. However, anyone with a brain could hear the hint given. Loner? Was this saying that Mo Fan’s Deception was unable to keep with the team?

Thinking of this, an experienced veteran like Wei Chen immediately understood what was happening. The reason he hadn’t noticed before was because he wasn’t paying attention to something like that. Now hearing Ye Xiu mention it, he immediately understood what had been happening.

"So that’s how it is," Wei Chen sent Ye Xiu another private message.　"That’s indeed how it is," Ye Xiu said, not bothering to clarify what they were saying.

Mo Fan wasn’t stupid. Hearing Ye Xiu insult him with the word "loner", he paused. Was that the reason? Was it because of this that no matter how hard he worked to deal damage, his output was still crap?

"Let’s continue." Ye Xiu didn’t say anymore, not willing to waste anymore time on him, and led them further into the Hideout.　They met nothing but normal monsters along the way and soon arrived at the third boss without much suspense. It was the Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout’s Tactician Snow Eagle.　Snow Eagle’s long cloak fluttered, his hands empty and not giving a hint at his class. However, looking at his attire, it seemed more likely that he was some sort of Mage.

Everyone knew the routine by now. They didn’t need Ye Xiu to order them, standing their characters to the side and waiting for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim to go up and feel out the boss.

Ye Xiu, of course, did as expected. As soon as Lord Grim entered the aggro range of the boss, Snow Eagle immediately welcomed him warmly. He flicked his sleeve, not even showing his hands, and a star appeared in midair, shooting forth with a streak of light.　A Witch skill, officially known as Magic Ray, that would create a star when fired, causing players to nickname it "Star Ray".

A mage, just as expected.

Ye Xiu was already on guard when Lord Grim stepped into aggro range. Though the Magic Ray was fast, it didn’t damage him. Lord Grim turned his body and the Magic Ray missed.　

Sprinting forwards, Lord Grim was already closing in on Snow Eagle. Yet, Snow Eagle’s next actions were shocking. He flicked his sleeves again without exposing his hands, seeming to grab something from under his cloak, but then his feet left the ground, having perched on a broom.

The broom sparkled, showing that this wasn’t any ordinary broom, but a Witch’s most important tool.

Leaving behind a trail of sparkles, the third Boss Snow Eagle, turned and left.

"What the hell?" Everyone gathered over, asking.

"It’s just as you see," Ye Xiu said.

"Are we still in combat?" Wei Chen asked.

"We are."　"Something’s fishy," Wei Chen commented.

"Of course," Ye Xiu responded.　　"What do we do?"　"This is the most shameless thing about dungeons. They’re bullying players by forcing them to walk into what they know to be an ambush so that they can clear the dungeon," Ye Xiu said.　"You go first, we’ll provide support," Wei Chen was blunt with his words.

Ye Xiu agreed to this blunt suggestion and had Lord Grim chase after Snow Eagle. The other nine kept their distance as they followed behind.

Not long after, Snow Eagle appeared once more. The area around him was filled with forestry, an obviously good place for an ambush. The system was using the fact that players had to advance, making these schemes so rough and inelegant. Snow Eagle turned his head and, seeing Lord Grim, flicked his sleeves once more, sending up magic fireworks. Hollering came from the forestry around him and a group of thieves ran out.

Ye Xiu hurriedly had Lord Grim back away. He didn’t want to fight all these thieves alone. As he used Aerial Gun to back away, he counted ten thieves! A total of ten Sealed Mountain Thieves was more than any wave they had previously encountered. The class lineup was very reasonable as well. There were close ranged and long ranged units, a leader with a shield. and even a devout looking Cleric, cross in hand.

A Cleric being a thief… It sounded absurd, but it was just a class in the game so no one argued over the logic.

A healer was always an important part of a team, no matter if it was PvP or PvE. Even without Ye Xiu issuing an order, the others had caught up immediately and set their sights on the Cleric.

For PvE, there was no need for Ye Xiu to waste brainpower on thinking up battle tactics. What was more important was giving commands to improve the cooperation and teamwork between team members. Though they hadn’t dealt with a wave of ten monsters before, the skill of Happy’s members was evident. Knowing their limitations, they wouldn’t take it on if they didn’t have the means to*, so the team worked in harmony. Mo Fan’s Deception might’ve been an outlier to this, but he was a Scavenger and staying safe in a chaotic battle was his forte, so no one had to worry about him.

"Soft Mist, go engage those two gunners; Steam Bun keep those two swordsmen busy; Old Wei give us a Death’s Door; Concealed Light summon two summons and keep that ranged unit occupied; One Inch Ash release an Ice Boundary; Launchers suppress them all from afar; I’ll go grab that Cleric," Ye Xiu organized rapidly, his Lord Grim already wheeling around and striking back. Against a ten monster team, pulling all the monsters alone was too tedious. So, Ye Xiu decided to utilize their party’s advantages to its fullest, that being that most of their members could take perfect care of themselves, so they didn’t need a specific MT to pull all the aggro. Anyone who had the ability could act as an MT and pull a few monsters. As for his Lord Grim, he would go directly after the Cleric.

After a few skills, the Cleric monster was thrown out from the formation, exposed and isolated from support.

In an instant, the Cleric was quickly killed under everyone’s focused fire. After that, the most troublesome one to deal with was the ranged Sealed Mountain Thief. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim charged forward again, throwing the two ranged thieves back to his team. With these two gone, the other seven didn’t need to be killed in any particular order. Whichever was more convenient to fight was whichever they would land a few strikes on. After a while, the ten monster team had been wiped out. Seeing this, Snow Eagle once again mounted his broom and flew off with another whoosh. They hurriedly chased after the boss and Ye Xiu took a look at everyone’s statuses, reminding everyone, "Keep an eye on your endurance, don’t waste anything."

No one knew what would happen next in this battle against the third Boss Snow Eagle. If the ambushes continued like this, then their consumption in this battle might even be worse than the battle against Sand Leopard.　"Do you think this has something to do with the signal the first boss sent out before he died?" Wei Chen asked.

"Yeah, that’s logical, but it might also just be a set event," Ye Xiu said.

What they meant by a set event was that the signal sent by the first boss before his death was protected by the system, and it wasn’t something the players could stop to change the progression of the dungeon. This sort of event was there to make the dungeon fit in with the storyline.

Every dungeon had something to do with the quests and storylines in the world of Glory, and not just a bunch of monsters that were there for you to kill. However, many players were willing to see it that way, not bothering to take note of the underlying plot.

Ye Xiu and co were these kinds of players. The reason for their analysis wasn’t because they had any interest in the plot, but because they wanted to know if the dungeon progression and layout could be changed by preventing that signal. Logically speaking, preventing the signal from firing would lower the difficulty of the dungeon.

T/N: There’s a sentence here that refers to an idiom: 没有金刚钻别揽瓷器活. What this means is that if you don’t have the tools to fix your ceramics, you shouldn’t try, ergo, if you don’t have the means, don’t try.

Chapter 866: After the Ambushes

As they pursued Snow Eagle, what met Happy was ambush after ambush. These sorts of battles weren’t really hard, but they weren’t really easy either. Since there were so many people fighting, the situation was usually rather chaotic and demanded a high level of cooperation between teammates.

This sort of thing couldn’t stop Ye Xiu and co from progressing. Their entire pursuit was mostly smooth going. Snow Eagle’s ambushes were dealt with one after another. After wiping out four consecutive ambushes, the path came to an end and Snow Eagle charged into the courtyard at the end of the road.

Seeing this, they realized that this was most likely the place where the battle against Snow Eagle would take place. Since they were constantly in combat, they couldn’t really take a real break. Using food and similar methods to restore health and mana was something you could only do out of combat. However, if they left combat now, the system would probably deem them to have failed everything starting from the moment they entered combat with Snow Eagle and they would have to start over.

They couldn’t allow themselves to make such a low-level mistake. All ten of them charged into the courtyard and, as expected, elite monsters came out from different rooms in the courtyard. However, this no longer seemed like an ambush set by Snow Eagle. The Boss was yelling and crying out in a panic. It was evident that after the four ambushes had been wiped out, he was at the end of his line. This wave of monsters was made up of the reinforcements he had called out for.

This wave of reinforcements was more powerful than the ambushes from before. The Sealed Mountain Thieves that came out from the room in the courtyard amounted to a total of 12, more than any of the previous ambushes.

However, after clearing out all the ambushes on the way, Ye Xiu’s group became used to these sorts of battles. Among the 12 Sealed Mountain Thieves, there were two healers that immediately became their primary targets. As for Snow Eagle? Now that he couldn’t find any other way out, he flew onto the roof and began to lob attacks at Happy with the other thieves.　Yet, this Snow Eagle’s offensive ability really didn’t live up to his title of boss. He wasn’t much more of a threat than the individual thieves. However, a Boss definitely would have far more health than these normal monsters, so everyone put Snow Eagle to the side for now , focusing on clearing out the normal monsters.

Seeing Snow Eagle’s appalling strength, everyone relaxed. The 12 Sealed Mountain Thieves were quickly dealt with, being just normal monsters with a little more health than usual. There wasn’t much to it.　After a chaotic battle, all 12 of the Sealed Mountain Thieves were killed. Everyone was prepared to turn their attacks on Snow Eagle, who was still perched on the roof, but then they heard the Tactician yell out again. Everyone could clearly hear that the Tactician had yelled out a title: Vice Chief.

Then, they saw the doors to the large room facing the main entrance to the courtyard open, and a burly man walked out, stretching. It was another Boss, Vice Chief Brown Bear*.

The progression of events was more than shocking for everyone present. If this Tactician had called another few waves of mobs, it would be much better than just directly calling for a Boss. This strapping man, who held the position of Vice Chief, was evidently not a weakling like Snow Eagle. Having experienced five battles without break, and now directly going up against two bosses, this battle seemed to be a grim one for their little team.

Ye Xiu clicked with his mouse, bringing up Brown Bear’s health. It became clear that they wouldn’t be able to finish this quickly; they couldn’t afford the consumption. They had to slow the pace down and forcefully drag the battle out.　　But what was this Brown Bear’s fighting style? Could they afford to draw out the match into one of endurance? Looking at his burly figure, he probably wasn’t a defense-oriented Boss like Boss number two, Sand Leopard. If he was an offense oriented boss, then a slow paced match would be far more dangerous. This was especially true with their opponents being not one, but two bosses working together. Though Snow Eagle was rather weak, this was only in comparison to what should be expected from a boss. With his health bar, defeating him wouldn’t be a swift job either. With a slippery guy like that causing chaos at the side, this would be frustrating to deal with, indeed....

Brown Bear’s appearance was very unexpected. Everyone was still inside the courtyard, not having the time to retreat so that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim would have the chance to figure the Boss out.

By the time everyone had managed to process their current situation, Brown Bear had snapped out of his sleepy state and reached behind the door next to him, pulling out a spiked steel club**.

That’s right, a spiked club… A weapon that didn’t exist among any of the 24 classes. It was impossible to figure out this guy’s possible skills using his weapon. Using a heavy weapon like this to do sword techniques wasn’t beyond the shamelessness of bosses.

"Keep your distance, everyone!" Same strategy as ever, Ye Xiu would test out the boss’ abilities first.

However, this time everyone was in combat already, so if they could retreat or not wasn’t up to them. Snow Eagle, who was still on the roof, had finally stopped his wretched behavior of hiding his broom between his legs. Now he held it in his hands, finally looking ready for battle. Using his advantage of the higher ground, he waved his arm and threw a Lava Flask at them.

Ye Xiu’s eyes were sharp and his hands were quick; Lord Grim raised his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella and with a bang, destroyed the flask in midair. The lava in the flask sprayed out, like it was raining fire. Though everyone still had to scatter to avoid it, it was better than if the flask shattered on the floor and turned the courtyard into a sea of flame.

Wu Chen couldn’t help but admire Ye Xiu’s skill. When the Lava Flask had been thrown, he had the awareness to try and shoot it down as well, but by the time he was aiming, a gunshot had already rung out.

As for Chen Guo, there wasn’t much to say. When she saw the Lava Flask, she had wanted to get Chasing Haze to jump up and run for it.　The Lava Flask had been destroyed, but Snow Eagle swept his broom again and swept out a cloud. The Boss was too fast and everyone was too far from him to interrupt the skill. This time, he managed to complete a Hail. Blue drops and snowflakes fell from above and everyone hurried to rush out from under the cloud.

"Be careful, everyone!" Ye Xiu yelled.

Brown Bear finally struck, roaring wildly. He raised his club up and behind his head, jumping into the courtyard from the room and swinging his arms up in a 180 degrees arc. With a massive thud, the club smashed into the ground and the tremors from it caused everyone’s view to shake. Those who were unlucky enough to still be within range of the attack had been knocked to the ground, rolling.　

"It’s a Collapsing Mountain!" Wei Chen cried out.

"Or it might be an Earth-Shattering Slash," Ye Xiu suggested.

"Just as low as expected!" Wei Chen shouted.

"That’s right!" Ye Xiu agreed. Using a sword skill with a club... that was definitely a new low for swordsmen.

"Whirlwind Strike!! Everyone get out of the courtyard!" Seeing Brown Bear’s movement, he made a quick judgement. Everyone had their characters run for the door, or flip over the wall, instantly escaping from the courtyard like wild animals. Then, Brown Bear returned to his room and Snow Eagle looked around before jumping from the roof and disappearing.

"Whoops…" Wei Chen was a little embarrassed. It was evident that they had escaped combat. That battle seemed to be limited to the courtyard. With all of them fleeing from the courtyard, they had left the combat zone and the system judged that as escaping from combat. So, everything was returned to its prior state and the trouble they had just gone through was all for naught.

"At least we know what’s going to happen now." Wei Chen attempted to gain everyone’s forgiveness with a smile full of cheek. He hadn’t thought of this possibility just now, so he had given the order to get out of the courtyard. In the end, everyone had charged out and the system didn’t give them any chance to regret, directly viewing them as escaping from combat.

"Well, this isn’t bad. When we do this again, everyone should keep in mind that what awaits us at the end are two bosses. We need to keep an eye on our mana consumption," Ye Xiu said.

Everyone nodded.　Five waves, each with a large number of normal monsters, ending in two bosses and not given a break, that was something only a team like them could handle.

"Or maybe we can just ignore these two and see if we can skip to directly take on the final boss?" Wei Chen suggested. In some dungeons, you didn’t necessarily need to kill every Boss before the final one. When breaking dungeon records, people would definitely skip every skippable Boss. In this Sealed Mountain Thieves’ Hideout, it seemed that they might even be able to skip this Tactician and Vice Chief, so Wei Chen had come up with such a suggestion.　　

"I don’t think that’s necessary! After all, these two have First Kills that need to be taken, which will give us better rewards!" Ye Xiu said.

"In reality… I think this battle is pretty tough. I mean, we have to deal with all these ambushes and we might not be able to endure to the end with the amount of mana and whatnot it might consume," Wei Chen said.

"Let’s give it a try first," Ye Xiu said, "If the situation goes south, then we’ll escape combat to stay alive. I noticed that we only left combat when five people had left the courtyard. It seems like it’s necessary for only half or more party members to stay inside.

"Yeah, I noticed that, too," Wei Chen said.

"Heh," Ye Xiu laughed lightly, not bothering to continue the conversation and turned to address everyone, "Ok, everyone, let’s head back and try again. This time, keep the pace slow to minimize consumption."

The ten player party then returned to where Snow Eagle had first appeared. As expected, the boss had returned to its original position.

"Hey, how’s about we try and see if we can prevent this guy from running and kill him here?" Wei Chen came up with a new idea.

"We can try. Everyone scatter, surround him," Ye Xiu ordered, making everyone stand around in a circle just out of aggro range, encircling Snow Eagle.

"Attack together, including the ranged characters, siege him to death!" With Ye Xiu’s order, everyone lunged for the Boss. Snow Eagle was very decisive. Before, when only Lord Grim had charged forwards, he had sent out a Magic Ray. Now, seeing how many people were targeting him, he didn’t bother to do anything and simply got on his broom and shot into the sky.

"F*ck, so shameless!" Everyone could do nothing but watch as Snow Eagle flew off. This was because the height at which Snow Eagle was flying was one set by the system that players couldn’t reach, no matter if it was with a Witch’s broom or a Mechanic’s Rotor Wing. This was obviously the system wanting Snow Eagle to get away successfully. Wu Chen and Chen Guo’s Launchers fired a few unfruitful blasts.

"Let’s give chase!" Ye Xiu didn’t reveal any sort of disappointment; he just once again led everyone in a chase after Snow Eagle.

T/N: *Brown Bear is written as 人熊 here in Chinese, which can be translated by each character to Man Bear, but refers to just a brown bear.**Literally “wolf fang club,” 狼牙棒 is an ancient weapon made from a long, wooden hilt and a cylindrical metal head with spikes like a wolf’s fangs on it, having a total length of four to five feet, usually. One can liken it to a spiked mace or spiked club.These bosses are annoying ;-; forcing me to write so many translator’s notes and do so much research...

Chapter 867: Isolation

Knowing what was coming, their progression was smoother and more decisive than their previous attempt. After swiftly wiping out the four waves of ambushes, the ten of them arrived once more in the courtyard. They killed the reinforcements, heard Frigid Eagle yelling for help, and saw the Vice Chief Brown Bear walk out lazily, just as he had before.

This time, would they still be given the chance to strike first? Of course not. Frigid Eagle hadn’t even managed to whip out his broom when with a "clang clang" sounded out with two flaming lighters landing at his feet.

Bosses weren’t dumb. Upon seeing these lighters, Frigid Eagle didn’t bother taking out his broom and tried to run. He hadn’t even managed to take three steps when the falling Heat-Seeking Missiles hit, creating a mushroom cloud. With his arms outstretched in a flawless line, Frigid Eagle was blasted off of the roof.

He hadn’t even landed when, with a stab, a spear had already arrived. The immense force from the spear nailed Frigid Eagle to the door of one of the side rooms in the courtyard.

It was Tang Rou, not Ye Xiu, who had struck.

Knowing what they would have to face, Happy had obviously devised plans on as they made their way over. Frigid Eagle’s offensive capabilities weren’t the best, but if they allowed him to jump about on that roof above their heads, he would become a very annoying distraction, so they eventually decided to deal with Frigid Eagle first.

However, they still had to be careful about Brown Bear when dealing with Frigid Eagle. Currently, all they knew was that this guy’s skills were probably from the Swordsman classes, but they didn’t know anything specific.

The responsibility of figuring out these specifics fell on Ye Xiu. Lord Grim didn’t wait for Brown Bear to jump into the courtyard before charging over. As for Frigid Eagle, he was under everyone else’s focused attacks.

With Ye Xiu’s ability, everyone knew that he could last a long time when facing any Boss one on one. In addition, Frigid Eagle wasn’t particularly powerful, so everyone hoped to take this chance and kill Frigid Eagle first.

This strategy wasn’t a bad one, but who would’ve thought that their plan would be thwarted just as they started? Brown Bear ignored the attacking Lord Grim, and with a swing of his club, he jumped directly at the formation around Frigid Eagle."Watch out!" Ye Xiu yelled hurriedly.　Everyone turned only to see Brown Bear’s club slam into the ground. They hastily jumped and dodged to avoid the attack. Brown Bear’s offense was abrupt, standing there and swinging his club once more...

Tang Rou had no way of getting the currently airborne Soft Mist to dodge such a big guy. She was quickly slammed against the wall of a room on the east side by Brown Bear’s club, as if retaliation for how she had just nailed Frigid Eagle to the door with her spear.　"Aggro Sharing!" Ye Xiu suddenly yelled out this Glory term. Everyone immediately understood what had happened when they heard this. They wanted to deal with Frigid Eagle and Brown Bear separately, but these two Bosses shared aggro.

Aggro Sharing was when two or more monsters had the same aggro target, and would advance and retreat as one. Under these circumstances, it was impossible to separate this battle into two.

"It seems like they at least have some sense of honor!" After saying this, Wei Chen had Windward Formation raise his Death’s Hand and a Hexagram Prison fell from the heavens, aiming to entrap Brown Bear. He had never expected that the weakling they believed Frigid Eagle to be would swing his broom then, seeming to throw the dust on the ground up and negating Windward Formation’s Hexagram Prison.

"What the hell is this? Dispersion?" Wei Chen was dumbstruck.

Witches had a skill called Disperse Powder, which would could get rid of a buff on its target. However, they hadn’t heard of a powder that could disperse curses that had yet to hit its target like this. Of course, there would always be some original skills given to Bosses. Yet these original skills were always so wretched, making players incapable of maintaining their cool.

Windward Formation raised Death’s Hand again and began to cast the power Death’s Door. Yet it was then that Frigid Eagle and Brown Bear both turned on him as one.

"Aiyou!" Realizing that something was wrong, Wei Chen didn’t care about the CD and wasted mana, hurriedly cancelling the skill and dodging as he yelled, "The aggro is really chaotic! Hurry up and stabilize it!"

Without a specialized MT class, wanting to save the situation at times like this became a chore.

If they couldn’t save the situation, then they would just have to leave the situation be.

"Ice Boundary, now! Gatling Gun to suppress!" Ye Xiu ordered.

"I’ll handle Frigid Eagle, you go for Brown Bear!" Wu Chen gave a shout, naturally directed at Chen Guo. The two Launchers immediately activated Gatling Gun, wildly firing at their respective targets.

Frigid Eagle’s small build was weak, getting pushed back continuously by the Gatling Gun. Brown Bear was completely different. With a level suppression of five levels, the momentum from the Gatling Gun seemed nonexistent against him as he continued to charge forwards, raising his club.

Pah!

With a soft noise, Brown Bear’s feet were suddenly frozen to the ground. The ice continued to creep upwards and, not long after, Brown Bear had become an ice sculpture.

One Inch Ash’s Ice Boundary had arrived just in time. Seeing Brown Bear frozen into an ice cube, everyone was delighted. He had been completely frozen even under a five level suppression. It seemed like Brown Bear’s resistance to ice was probably negative. This was a great opening to take.

Yet Ye Xiu didn’t even have time to make plans to utilize this when with a bang, Frigid Eagle threw a Lava Flask directly at the ice sculpture of Brown Bear. The lava ran down the sculpture, instantly melting a good portion of the ice. Brown Bear struggled for a moment, cracking the ice, and swiftly escaped his frozen state.　"These two assholes!" Everyone yelled out in shock. These two Bosses not only shared aggro but were also so united and cooperative, knowing how to support one another. The difficulty of this battle had just risen again.　"Take Brown Bear into the room, isolate them from each other," Ye Xiu immediately found a solution. It was only a team of two, so how hard could it be? In the pro scene, they would have to face five players at once who were as close as they could get, and fought in sync.　

"Get the aggro off me!" Wei Chen was still jumping around anxiously, because the two Boss’ aggro had been locked on him after his failed Hexagram Prison and had yet to switch targets. With their line up, Windward Formation would have to stop attacking to get the aggro pulled away. Wei Chen currently couldn’t even use control skills to protect himself and was under immense pressure, being chased by two Bosses.

"Hold on for just a moment longer," Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already started to attack. Since they shared aggro, he didn’t target Brown Bear, but just focused on bullying Frigid Eagle.

Under Ye Xiu’s focused attack, the two Bosses’ attention finally switched to him. After checking the positions of the two bosses, Ye Xiu didn’t hesitate to head into the room at the front.

The two Bosses gave chase. Knowing the plan, no one went after Brown Bear, and all focused on Frigid Eagle instead.

"Are you certain that you can hold the aggro?" Wei Chen then asked.

Ye Xiu’s plan was that he would keep Brown Bear busy inside the room while the others stayed outside to give beat Frigid Eagle up. Under these circumstances, the aggro of attackers outside would accumulate quickly and easily overtake Lord Grim’s aggro. After all, Frigid Eagle was much weaker and there were so many people focused on killing him.

"Whoever OTs comes inside and keeps Brown Bear busy," Ye Xiu said.

"It’s that a bit too dangerous?" Wei Chen said. It was ok for Ye Xiu with his skill, but if it were Chen Guo or Luo Ji who had to go inside and keep Brown Bear busy, then it would be equal to sending them to their deaths.　"Whoever has the greatest DPS shouldn’t be too weak, right?" Ye Xiu resolved the problem with a single retort. Whoever OTed had to be the fiercest attacker. For those of Chen Guo and Luo Ji’s skill level, they wouldn’t possibly become that person. Wei Chen’s worry had been for nothing.

"But it might still be a little troublesome for ranged characters. Dawn Rifle, hold back on your DPS a little!" Wei Chen added.　　

"Right," Wu Chen agreed. It wasn’t a very good idea for his Launcher to go into that narrow room and keep a powerful melee Boss busy. He had always had the highest DPS as they progressed, so it seemed like he would have to hold back now.　

With Wu Chen holding back, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist’s offense became even fiercer. Frigid Eagle wanted to charge into the room to support Brown Bear, but was locked in place by a whole group of people, so he could only make supercial counterattacks. Poor Frigid Eagle’s health was falling with a whoosh and, not long after, his superficial attacks changed and gained focus. Two rapid magical attacks sped towards Soft Mist.

"Switch!" Ye Xiu had also realized Brown Bear seemed to want to leave the room and that someone must have OTed.

Tang Rou’s movements were swift. Soft Mist darted through the doorway with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks, throwing Brown Bear’s attention back to room that he was about to leave. At the same time, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim sped out of the room. Frigid Eagle was about to enter when Lord Grim flew directly at him, blasting him back with a palm to the chest.

"Little Cold Hands, stand under the doorway and keep an eye on the situation inside," Ye Xiu ordered the healer. After all, Tang Rou’s skill wasn’t quite as good as Ye Xiu’s and would be hard pressed to stay inside without injury.

"Be careful to not OT, Little Hands!" Ye Xiu’s only worry now was Little Cold Hands. With their strategy, the aggro would switch between them as they dealt damage. With that, the continuously healing that Little Cold Hands did would make his aggro accumulation the most stable.

An Wenyi might have improved greatly as of late, but, facing a boss alone, he would have no chance.

"I know." An Wenyi had evidently also considered this, and made sure to not use any high level heals that would accumulate a lot of aggro.　"Hold on, I’ll switch with you soon!" After giving Tang Rou those words of encouragement, Lord Grim ran up to attack Frigid Eagle.

The situation inside the room was far more dangerous than the situation outside. Frigid Eagle wasn’t very strong anyways, so they were more or less just bullying him. Meanwhile, Brown Bear was powerful, and it was a one on one as well, so the difficulty was immense. After Soft mist had entered the room, Little Cold Hands became exceptionally busy. Fighting a Boss alone inside a room was a definite challenge for Tang Rou.

"We can’t hold on like this for long, hurry!" Calculations were An Wenyi’s forte. Seeing Tang Rou’s situation being completely different from Lord Grim’s while inside, he had to heal continuously. A little longer and it might be him who had to rush inside. If he went inside, that was equivalent to walking to his own death.

"Give me space!" Ye Xiu called out and Lord Grim retreated to squish next to Little Cold Hands. Frigid Eagle, wanting to enter the room, followed after without prompting. Lord Grim continued to give Frigid Eagle a beatdown while occasionally turning around to cast a heal on Soft Mist. This way, he not only took some pressure off of Little Cold Hands, but also gained more aggro for himself.

"Can your mana hold on like this!?" Wei Chen yelled.

Chapter 868: Combo Kill

"It won’t be like this forever!" Ye Xiu replied to Wei Chen, continuing to take care of the situation on both sides. Seeing how her situation had made the battle more difficult, Tang Rou was determined to work even harder. She decisively abandoned her extremely offense-oriented style and focused on avoiding damage from her opponent, immediately taking a lot of pressure off the healer’s shoulders. With this, it wasn’t long before Lord Grim’s aggro went over the the standard and the long-awaited OT finally occurred once more. Lord Grim turned, stepping into the room. At the same time, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist brushed by and exited the room, swinging her spear at Frigid Eagle.

The battle inside the room against Brown Bear made Tang Rou feel extremely constrained. She had been forced to abandon her offense-oriented style for the team, but this went against her usual habits. Now that she didn’t have to hold back anymore, Frigid Eagle immediately became the target of her katharsis. Soft Mist’s spear swung like a windmill, releasing all sorts of skills and beating Frigid Eagle away from the doorway all the way to the edge of the courtyard, almost throwing him outside.

With Tang Rou leading a vicious offense, the others could be a little more open with their attacks as well. Those who had classes that weren’t appropriate for going inside the room and keeping Brown Bear busy had been sandbagging. Now that Soft Mist was mounting such a vicious offense, they didn’t have to hold back as much, only so much so that their damage output wouldn’t surpass Soft Mist’s.　Their damage output increased greatly and when it next came for Tang Rou to switch with Lord Grim, Frigid Eagle’s health had dropped by a large fraction.　"Not bad!" When Lord Grim came out, Ye Xiu was pleased by how much Frigid Eagle had been damaged. They encouraged each other, boosted one another’s morale, and with their strategy that used their advantage in technical skill to the fullest, they had broken the teamwork of the two bosses.

After Lord Grim and Soft Mist had switched places five times, their primary target Frigid Eagle finally fell. This boss was rather easy to deal with alone, not even giving everyone much trouble when he entered an enraged state. At red blood, Frigid Eagle became faster and rode his broom around a lot, attempting to use guerrilla tactics. Unfortunately for him, the formation that had surrounded him was close to perfect after fighting for so long. Frigid Eagle didn’t even get a proper chance to fight back. Soon enough, the last 10 percent of his health was gone.

As soon as Frigid Eagle fell, his First Kill was announced on the TV. Though he might be rather weak, he was still classified as a boss by the system.

However, before everyone could be relieved at the death of one boss, a loud roar came out from the room. Tang Rou gave a warning shout and then Brown Bear jumped out of the room, through the roof with a resounding crash.

Red eyed and radiating a bloody aura, Brown Bear seemed to be fully in an Enraged State. Everyone noticed his speed as he swung his club down from the roof. It seemed like his stats had undergone a great increase.

"Has he already gone into an Enraged state?" Wei Chen asked in shock.

If that was true, then they had miscalculated in their original strategy. The current Brown Bear still had plenty of health left. If he stayed in an Enraged State like this, then the difficulty of this battle would rise again. After all, when most bosses entered such a state, they merely had a tenth of their health less and by then the battle was already coming to a close, so players could go wild with their DPS and quickly kill the boss. Yet now, a boss with over 95 percent of its health left had already entered an Enraged State. They had to be cautious when facing it; there was little room for error.

"Seems that way," Ye Xiu confirmed. There was no time for chit chat though; they had a boss to deal with first.

　For a boss with immense strength like Brown Bear, players couldn’t possibly parry the attacks. When the club swung down, Lord Grim jumped lightly to avoid it as Myriad Manifestation Umbrella struck out in its spear form.

The others continued to spectate, planning on taking a good look at the changes the boss had gone through after entering an Enraged State.

Brown Bear’s roars rang in everyone’s ears. With each weighty attack, everyone’s view would tremble every now and then. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stuck to him, prompting Brown Bear to make all sorts of attacks from different angles and directions and making sure everyone knew what sorts of skills this Brown Bear had.

"Ranged characters get to higher ground," Ye Xiu began to arrange everyone’s positions.

Dawn Rifle, Chasing Haze, Windward Formation and Concealed Light, who didn’t need to personally fight the boss, all jumped to higher ground. Cleric Little Cold Hands could also do such a thing, but, after taking a good look around, decided against it. Their current strategy relied a lot on avoiding the boss’ attacks to take pressure off the healer, so they wouldn’t stay in one place to attack, instead relying a lot on movement. The high ground in this courtyard didn’t have a position with no blind spots, so for stability, An Wenyi left Little Cold Hands on the ground.

After finishing the arrangements, they opened fire on Ye Xiu’s order.

Though Brown Bear was in an Enraged State, his weakness had long since been noted by everyone, and that was his low resistance to magic. So in the following battle, Wei Chen’s Warlock and Qiao Yifan’s Ghostblade were particularly eye catching.　　Both classes had many CC skills. As Brown Bear ran after Lord Grim, going berserk, One Inch Ash had already filled the courtyard with Ghost Boundaries, and caused all sorts of status effects to pop up on Brown Bear’s body. Wei Chen’s Windward Formation wasn’t slacking off either, a Binding Curse here, a Control Curse there, and a Hexagram Prison thrown into the mix.　Take advantage of your own strengths and strike at your opponent’s weaknesses.

Brown Bear might’ve been in an Enraged State, but under the combined effects of all these CC skills, his offensive ability was limited. Under One Inch Ash’s Plague Boundary, Brown Bear’s defense had fallen, so his life was being depleted, just like Frigid Eagle’s had.

"Keep going, maintain this pace." After taking a look at everyone’s consumption, Ye Xiu quickly calculated that they would be able to maintain this without too much pressure, so he didn’t make them change their pace. With Brown Bear being bullied like this, there was naturally much less pressure on their healer’s shoulders. An Wenyi even had time to let Little Cold Hands throw a few skills like Hypnosis and Holy Commandment to support the team. In terms of supporting skills, Clerics mostly focused on ones to do with supporting an offense.

Finally, Brown Bear’s health was approaching 10 percent. During this time, he had maintained the increases in strength that he had gained. However, would he go into another Enraged state after falling to Red Blood?

This was something they definitely had to be wary of. Ye Xiu also decided to use the usual strategy to deal with this. When Brown Bear’s health fell to 10 percent, there were indeed some changes. Compared to how he had gone wild with his attacks before, he seemed to become much calmer and his resistance seemed to have increased.

Yet this strengthening from his Red Blood state wasn’t enough to turn the tides. For a boss that had more or less been in an Enraged State for the majority of the battle, the creator wasn’t wretched enough to have his strength skyrocket two times in one battle.

With just a tenth of his health left, Ye Xiu and co didn’t even really bother with too many CC skills. This change had come too late for Brown Bear.

Brown Bear fell and the system announced their First Kill in a timely fashion.

Brown Bear’s First Kill announcement followed Frigid Eagle’s announcement rather closely. The players who didn’t know what the dungeon was like at all naturally expressed their admiration and surprise.

Sealed Mountain Hideout had a total of five bosses. By now, four were dealt with. Did Guild Happy plan to clear the dungeon on their first explorative run?

The players had mixed emotions about this, and all sorts of thoughts were discussed without holding back in the global chat.

Ye Xiu’s group didn’t bother with these discussions. With the defeat of two bosses, it was once again time to check the system’s DPS charts.

In reality, Ye Xiu never had such habits. At his skill level, why would he bother with comparing dungeon DPS and taking joy in ranking higher than others?

Repeatedly showing everyone the DPS chart like this today had caused everyone to realize that there was an ulterior motive to it. The DPS charts were there for Mo Fan to see. This guy who ate, lived, and gamed with them, but was never truly a part of the team, probably wouldn’t listen even if you grabbed his ear and yelled. Now with the data open for viewing, there was no need to speak. He could figure things out for himself!

With the data for the new section out, no one bothered to check their own, all looking for Deception’s. In the end, it was the same as before. Deception appeared on the same level as Chasing Haze and Concealed Light, who weren’t as skilled as everyone else.

"If someone would stop slacking off, our battles could definitely end a lot more quickly." With that, Lord Grim headed off to the next area.

Everyone had their characters follow while stretching their necks to look at Mo Fan’s reaction.

In reality, everyone knew that with Mo Fan’s personality, he would either not join in, but if he did, he definitely wouldn’t slack off.

He was certainly doing his best to strike hard and fast, but for some reason, his DPS just wouldn’t rise. It stayed at the same level as Chasing Haze and Concealed Light, who weren’t as skilled and everyone was surprised.

Why was this happening?

Mo Fan was gritting his teeth hard enough to shatter them, but he really didn’t understand why. He was very familiar with the Ninja class and was skilled at both PvP and PvE. When he went dungeoning with a few wild teams in the past, his DPS was always at a level that inspired awe in everyone. How come it fell so far after he had joined a team?

Though these team members were incomparable to normal players, he shouldn’t fall behind by so much.

"We have one more boss," Ye Xiu said.

To Mo Fan’s ears, it sounded just like "you have one last chance." But how could he improve his DPS? Thinking deeply, Mo Fan really couldn’t think of a reason for his low DPS. Was it because his hand speed wasn’t fast enough?

That didn’t seem right! After all, Mo Fan was always with everyone. He might not interact with them much, but he was aware of everyone’s circumstances. He had an understanding of things like their hand speeds. This probably wasn’t the reason why he fell behind.

Soon enough, their party arrived at the core of the Sealed Mountain Hideout: Sealed Mountain Hall. In here sat the big boss of the Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout, Chief Sealed Mountain Tiger!

Chapter 869: Chief Sealed Mountain Tiger

In comparison to Brown Bear, who was so buff that it looked wrong, the big boss of the Sealed Mountain Thieves and the final boss with Sealed Mountain in his name, Sealed Mountain Tiger, looked very normal.

In the eyes of players, normal meant that he looked no different from your average player. If he was thrown into the main city, he would be mistaken for a player.

However, as they approached the Sealed Mountain Hall step by step, Sealed Mountain Tiger suddenly stood from his tiger-skin covered throne in the center of the hall.

It seemed like he had been waiting for them.

Should they directly go into battle with the boss?

After the experiencing both the ambushes and the cooperation between boss numbers three and four, everyone was hoping that there would be more tasks to complete before getting to fight the last boss. This was because if there weren’t, then this boss was certain to be immensely powerful, to the point where fighting him alone would be more difficult than a road of ambushes and the combined power of Frigid Eagle and Brown Bear.

Pioneering players only wanted to safely clear the dungeon, and didn’t care about testing their limits against challenging stages. So, at this moment, no one hoped that Sealed Mountain Tiger was strong. If only he could be as weak as a normal monster, that would be great.

Unfortunately, that was also impossible. In dungeons, the strength of bosses wouldn’t necessarily increase as you ventured further into the dungeon. The second boss might be stronger than the third and the third might be stronger than the fourth. However, the final boss would always be as strong as a final boss should be. They would be the most difficult to beat, sometimes even harder than Hidden bosses.

No matter how normal Sealed Mountain Tiger looked, Ye Xiu and the others wouldn’t underestimate him.

As soon as they entered the plaza in the center of the hideout, everyone started to take in their environment and familiarize themselves with the terrain. This was battle preparation. After that, they approached slowly and the final boss finally reacted.

"Everyone, get back."

As always, Lord Grim stayed, everyone else retreated.

Sealed Mountain Tiger’s steps were calm, slowly walking out from the hall. Ye Xiu didn’t make any moves lightly either. He had to focus on figuring the boss out. There was no need to rush in to attack.

Sealed Mountain Tiger was empty handed, no weaponry in sight. His equipment wasn’t of any recognizable class either. It was impossible to figure out what class this boss might be.

But, the boss had to act eventually.

Standing on the stone steps in front of the Sealed Mountain Hall, only 18 steps away from Lord Grim, Sealed Mountain Tiger glanced at Lord Grim and raised his hand to strike.

Not caring what it was, Ye Xiu hurriedly had Lord Grim dodge to the side.

Yet what came at him wasn’t a skill, but people.

The originally empty plaza suddenly became populated with four people who had came out of nowhere. They didn’t know if it was out of convenience or not, but the names above their heads were exceptionally simple: Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta.

As soon as the four appeared, they didn’t hesitate to charge towards Lord Grim. As they charged, they each took out their own weapons.

Lightsaber, Revolver, Boxing Gloves, Dagger.

Four people, four different classes, and looking at the weapons they were all DPS-focused classes. Were these four the four elite killers working under Chief Sealed Mountain Tiger?

Ye Xiu didn’t care about the backstories of NPCs. He would defeat them no matter what sort of backstory they had. Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta quickly engaged them. Beta, revolver in hand, was naturally the first to attack.

Gunshots rang out and Lord Grim moved out of the way. Blademaster Alpha, lightsaber raised, sent over a Downwind Sword Slash. The speed of the attack didn’t see much difference from the Enraged Brother Wolf. Lord Grim sidestepped it. Unfortunately, Blademaster Alpha had already closed in on Lord Grim with this attack, sending out more skills.

Boom!

A missile exploded between them. Lord Grim was unmoved, but Blademaster Alpha was pushed back by the force of the explosion.

Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle had attacked first, and then Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze also followed with a Gatling Gun.

　

Though they weren’t your average monsters, they weren’t nearly enough to be considered bosses. So for Happy, there was no need for Ye Xiu to go up first and figure them out. As soon as they engaged in combat, Happy’s members acted as well.

Launchers Dawn Rifle and Chasing Haze’s attacks were just the opening scene. Windward Formation’s Hexagram Prison soon followed, falling on and entrapping Striker Gamma, who looked like he could beat an elephant to death with a single punch. The dagger wielding Delta was an Assassin, whose movement speed was very fast, to the point where he seemed to be having problems controlling it. He smashed directly into an oncoming brick, and then Tang Rou’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks arrived, slamming Assassin Delta into a stone lion in the plaza with the force.

The Gunner Beta, who had stayed away and kept shooting from afar, was now being kept busy by Concealed Light’s summons. With the protection of the team, Luo Ji didn’t have to worry. If all he had to do with focus on controlling his four summons, then he had very good foundations for his skill level. The Gunner Beta had to contend with four at once, no longer able to find the time to attack anyone else.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was the last to strike. Only after everyone had found their own targets did his Ghost Boundaries come to support them.

Did these four elite killers of Sealed Mountain Tiger have any special team tactics?

　

They didn’t know!

　

Since everyone had come up like this, they had isolated the four killers from one another. In a party like Happy’s, there were more than enough people who were strong enough to stand on their own, so everyone had enough skill to be a DPS MT.

　

"Very good! Keep it up!" Ye Xiu had everyone continue, seeing that they were all doing pretty well. He wasn’t bored enough hold back on purpose just to see what tricks these four killers had up their sleeves.

So, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim dueled Blademaster Alpha, while Dawn Rifle and Chasing Haze provided backup from afar.

Wei Chen’s Windward Formation tormented Striker Gamma. Strikers had some of the lowest attack ranges, so he was helpless against Wei Chen’s Warlock, whose cast range would shock everyone in the Glory circle.

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were wiping the floor with Assassin Delta, who went up against them alone.

Most of the others were taking on one in teams of two or three, but Concealed Light had managed to keep Gunner Beta occupied on his own. It was a pleasant surprise, but he didn’t dare to be overconfident, taking extreme care in his performance. As for One Inch Ash and Little Cold Hands, they sent support and healing wherever it was necessary.

With everyone taking their own jobs, the four elite killers had been completely isolated from support and backup. Yet Happy’s party wasn’t necessarily a complete team either. They also had a guy who wasn’t in sync with everyone else, and that was obviously Mo Fan’s Deception.

This guy was like a headless fly. He didn’t have a clear target, sometimes landing a few blows here, then sending a few skills there, like he was a firefighter. However, he wasn’t nearly good at firefighting as One Inch Ash and Little Cold Hands. It would’ve been no different had he not been there.

Soon enough, Blademaster Alpha couldn’t hold on any longer. He was been taking on three people at once, and among them was an expert like Ye Xiu. It didn’t need to be elaborated on how he was holding up. When his health fell to 10 percent, Ye Xiu was careful and held back a little, uncertain if this monster, who could be an elite monster or a mini boss had an Enraged State. When the Blademaster showed no change upon reaching red blood, it was evident that he didn’t have an Enraged State. Soon enough, Blademaster Alpha fell and Ye Xiu’s three person group prepared to switch targets and support another group. Yet, it was at this moment that Sealed Mountain Tiger raised his hand again, standing on the steps, and another Blademaster Alpha came out suddenly, exactly the same as the previous.

"Holy crap, this guy’s a summoner!!" Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. They had thought this was a pre-boss battle or something, and had no idea they had actually already engaged the boss. Alpha, Beta, Gamma and Delta were actually Sealed Mountain Tiger’s summons.

If this was the case, then it was a bad idea to keep tangling with these four. No matter how many summons died, it wouldn’t cause any harm to the summoner. Though continuous summoning would take a toll on Mana, but this was a boss. The mana consumption of a boss wasn’t something players cared about since their mana was usually just as high as their health.

Thinking of this, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately aimed his muzzle at the boss. At first they were thinking that they probably shouldn’t provoke the boss before the final battle, but knowing what was really happening now, it would just be a waste of time to give the boss a wide berth.

With a bang, bullets flew. Yet the newly summoned Blademaster Alpha courageously jumped in front of Sealed Mountain Tiger and took the hits for him.

"Meddlesome!" Chen Guo scolded Blademaster Alpha loudly, sending a Satellite Beam directly at him.

Sealed Mountain Tiger, who hadn’t left the stone steps all this time, finally moved. Satellite Beam wasn’t a skill that one could block with their body, so it wouldn’t matter how courageous and loyal a summon was.

With this move, Sealed Mountain Tiger disappeared. When he reappeared, he was ten body units away from his original position.

"He can teleport!" This was a headache for the onwatching Team Happy. Summoners didn’t have much offensive or defensive capabilities and relied entirely on their summons for protection, making the class complicated to control and extremely passive in battle. So Summoners needed to be very good with positioning and movement. This way, your opponent wouldn’t be able to catch you and you could have your summons continuously attack. This made the use of Summoners very complicated, to the point where not a single one had become an All-Star yet.

　

For positioning and movement, it was obvious that the faster the movement speed, the better, and was there anything faster than Teleportation? It was good that this skill wasn’t of the same class as Summoners, so they couldn’t learn it through normal means. However, self-made weapons could still give them built in skills, no? So, in the Pro League, Summoners would, without a doubt, choose to have Teleport built into their weapons. This skill would definitely fortify a Summoner’s strength.

And now, it seemed that the designers had noticed the advantages this sort of Summoner had and designed a Summoner boss who used that exact strategy. Also, boss’ class skills weren’t necessarily the same as players’. If this boss had a low CD for Teleportation, then that would be very annoying!

Chapter 870: Combine

With a single Teleport, Sealed Mountain Tiger had left Lord Grim far behind and the newly summoned Blademaster Alpha ran up to engage him. Lord Grim swung out his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella and a quick Sky Strike sent the Blademaster airborne. A step to the side and then a Falling Flower Palm sent the Blademaster into Windward Formation’s range of control.

"Will you have any problems with keeping both of them occupied?" Ye Xiu asked Wei Chen.

Wei Chen was especially straightforward, immediately replying, "Yeah, some."

They might have been summons, but they were summoned by a level 75 final Boss. The CC skills of a Warlock were weakened quite a bit, unable to perform to their full potential. Being able to keep one under control was already very impressive, but Wei Chen couldn’t fully hold onto two.　Without waiting for Ye Xiu to think of a new idea, a figure flashed by. Mo Fan’s Deception appeared, taking on Blademaster Alpha.

"Will our loner have any trouble taking it on alone?" Ye Xiu immediately asked.

Mo Fan didn’t reply, simply controlling Deception to engage Blademaster Alpha.

"One Inch Ash, pay a little more attention to the situation over here," Ye Xiu still arranged.

"Okay," Qiao Yifan agreed.

"Let’s go and take out the leader." Saying this, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim charge after Sealed Mountain Tiger. Dawn Rifle and Chasing Haze continued to provide ranged support. All three characters had ranged attacks, so gunshots sounded out before they even arrived. Missiles and bullets streaked through the air towards Sealed Mountain Tiger.

Sealed Mountain Tiger didn’t just rely on Teleportation for moving; his movement speed was also very fast, allowing him to dodge the attacks from the three.

"Be careful to complement each other’s attacks. I’ll take the left, Daw Rifle the right, Chasing Haze blast our target!" Ye Xiu commended. If they didn’t take care to cooperate with each other, then their attacks would be no different from a single person’s attacks. With Ye Xiu’s arrangement, their accuracy was assured, despite the cut in DPS.

Lord Grim and Dawn Rifle’s attacks limited Sealed Mountain Tiger’s space for dodging and Chasing Haze’s attacks flew directly at him. Unless he Teleported again, these attacks weren’t something that could be dodged through normal means.

Teleportation didn’t appear again. It seemed that the CD time for Sealed Mountain Tiger wasn’t short either, which was a huge relief for Ye Xiu. The designer wasn’t that inhumane, it seemed.

Boom!

Their attacks caused a chain of explosions, finally damaging Sealed Mountain Tiger. As a Summoner, Sealed Mountain Tiger would try to follow or get closer to his opponents even with an aggro target. Sealed Mountain Tiger used his finger to point, sending commands. Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta all had the intention to come over and protect their master, but with Happy’s members keeping them occupied, they didn’t have the chance.

"Will you be ok on your own, Soft Mist?" Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

"What do you think?" Tang Rou’s reply was full of confidence.

"Steamed Bun, get over here." Ye Xiu decisively stole him. Now knowing that Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta were just summons, there was no need to waste much time and effort on them. As long as they were kept under control, it would be enough.

They could imagine that this design for Sealed Mountain Tiger would cause a lot of parties to waste a lot of time and effort on a futile task if they didn’t know it’s true face beforehand. Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta didn’t seem like summons at all. Even a god like Ye Xiu hadn’t realized at first, so how would normal players?

With the level normal players had, they probably wouldn’t be able to deal with just these four like Ye Xiu and co could.

For normal players, they would probably need to do quite a bit of research into how to beat this "curtain raiser" battle. Then, after accumulating the experience from all those defeats, they would finally manage a single victory, only to realize that this was a battle against the Boss’ summons...

"How cunning." When Ye Xiu gave his final opinion on Sealed Mountain Tiger, he had already launched a two-pronged attack against the Boss with Steamed Bun, one coming at him from the front and the other from the back. In addition, his left and right were being taken care of by Dawn Rifle and Chasing Haze.

"You won’t be able to escape!" Steamed Bun yelled threateningly.

"Don’t let your guard down!" Ye Xiu warned sighed.

This formation had taken a little bit of time to arrange. Ye Xiu believed that Sealed Mountain Tiger’s Teleportation’s CD was up, otherwise there was no point in having the skill.

"Watch this!" Steamed Bun hollered, having Steamed Bun Invasion charge forth.

"Go!" Yet Ye Xiu’s voice rang out only after Steamed Bun Invasion had begun to charge, seeming to be unnecessary.

Seeing how he couldn’t escape by normal means, Sealed Mountain Tiger attempted to Teleport, as expected. This spell was an instant one, activated with the raise of his hand without any cast time. It was then that six pillars of light crashed into the ground like swords from the heavens and a hexagram lit up on the ground.

Warlock skill: Hexagram Prison.

The very second before Sealed Mountain Tiger’s Teleportation activated, Windward Formation’s curse struck, entrapping Sealed Mountain Tiger before he could act. Under Hexagram Prison, even Teleportation wouldn’t activate.

"Not bad!" Ye Xiu praised Wei Chen.

Wei Chen didn’t have the time to reply. He still had to deal with Striker Gamma. Having barely managed to get enough time to throw a skill their way and with such precise timing, the action naturally didn’t do any good for his situation. He was too busy trying to save his situation to reply!

There was no need for Ye Xiu to say anything more.

Steamed Bun, Dawn Rifle, Chasing Haze, and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately attacked fiercely.

With just the two Satellite Beams that crashed down one after another, the smaller beams reaching the middle, their targets survival seemed unreal.

This wave of attacks caused immense damage. However, Hexagram Prison wouldn’t entrap this level 75 final Boss for long. Yet, the moment Hexagram Prison disappeared, a sacred white flame flickered to life and Sealed Mountain Tiger was burned in an instant.

Cleric skill: Sacred Fire.

The damage was secondary to the effect of the three second silence, which once again delayed Sealed Mountain Tiger’s use of Teleport. The four took this chance to deal as much damage as possible again. When the effect of Sacred Fire ended, Steamed Bun Invasion ran up with a Strangle, getting a solid grip on Sealed Mountain Tiger.

Under this circumstance, Teleportation also couldn’t be used. Another wave of attacks flew, seeming to provoke Sealed Mountain Tiger. Strangle didn’t really count as a CC skill, so characters under its effect could still attack. Sealed Mountain Tiger pushed out with his palm and there was a loud slapping sound; Steamed Bun Invasion had somehow been slapped flying.

This was the Battle Mage skill Falling Flower Palm! So this Sealed Mountain Tiger did have some offensive skills! Yet this sort of close-combat skill seemed to be like a skill that players commonly added to their skill tree, often to make sure that their character had a few skills to protect themselves. This made it seem like Sealed Mountain Tiger really was designed based on what was mainstream for Summoners.

"Aiyo, so strong!" Steamed Bun Invasion was blown back quite the distance. A level 75 final dungeon Boss’ strength wasn’t something to laugh about. However, in the time he took to send Steamed Bun Invasion flying, he had taken a severe beating. Just as he wanted to teleport out of the way, he was caught by Lord Grim and sent smashing into the ground, head over heels, with a Grappler’s Back Throw.

Ye Xiu arranged the entire team to delay Sealed Mountain Tiger’s Teleport for as long as possible. Unfortunately, this skill was instant and they didn’t have any way to reliably predict its activation. Everyone was delaying it through their use of skill combos and their own experience. This wasn’t infallible though. Eventually, a skill wasn’t fast enough to continue the CC chain and allowed Sealed Mountain Tiger to Teleport, immediately distancing himself from them. However, Ye Xiu’s reaction was fast. As Sealed Mountain Tiger darted away, his Lord Grim was already chasing after him with a Shadow Clone.　This time, Sealed Mountain Tiger didn’t have a Teleport to use. It might have a few close-combat skills, but they weren’t specialized, so how could he deal with Ye Xiu? His greatest weapons were his summons, but they were being kept busy by the opponent. So, Sealed Mountain Tiger once again fell into his own personal hell, surrounded and getting beat on by Ye Xiu, Steamed Bun, Wu Chen, and Chen Guo.

Just from this battle, Sealed Mountain Tiger didn’t seem much stronger than Frigid Eagle. However, that was mostly because the four summons were being heavily suppressed by six people, so their master was completely cut off from receiving their support. This definitely wasn’t something a normal pioneering team could do. Team Happy’s members were all very skilled in their own right, and this gave them a huge advantage against this Boss. If it wasn’t a team like theirs, they wouldn’t be able to suppress Sealed Mountain Tiger so well.

The battle continued. As they fought, there would naturally be some bumps, like when a summons was killed and resummoned, they had to spend time getting it under control again. Or, when someone lost control of a summons, it would come over and cause some trouble, but all this was dealt with, and the situation was maintained. Soon enough, they were approaching the Boss’ red-blood state. Many players fell to this darkest period before dawn.

What sort of ace did Sealed Mountain Tiger have up his sleeve?

Since there were still four summons on the field, there was no way to clear the field for Lord Grim to go forward and test out the Boss. In their hunting down of the Boss, his health fell to 10 percent and Ye Xiu yelled a "careful", before watching the Boss warily with everyone else.

The current Sealed Mountain Tiger’s demeanor had changed. He raised his arms to the sky. Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta suddenly dispersed into smoke with four "poof"s, but the four’s weapons were left behind, spinning in the air. Then, they came together and flew into Sealed Mountain Tiger like souls, combining with Sealed Mountain Tiger.　Seeing this, everyone had a vague idea of what changes Sealed Mountain Tiger had just gone through. With his last 10 percent of health, Sealed Mountain Tiger was no longer a Summoner, but he had absorbed his summons’ power and took control of it himself, turning himself into a summons to battle.

"That isn’t very impressive, is it?" Wei Chen was already starting to lower his guard. This was just a Boss with a rather complicated fighting style. With just a tenth of its health left, it should be easy for them to deal with, right?

As his words fell, a figure seemed to dart straight through Windward Formation and Windward Formation suddenly erupted with a fountain of blood. This scene was incredibly familiar, almost exactly the same as when Brother Wolf had struck Dawn Rifle with Downwind Sword Slash.

"Holy f*ck!" Seeing his health, Wei Chen had been scared sh*tless. Windward Formation had almost been one-shotted.

"Stop him, quick!" Wei Chen didn’t dare to lower his guard anymore. This Summoner-turned-summons had terrifying attack power!

Chapter 871: First Kill Rewards (1)

Warlocks didn’t have much health and their defense was rather low as well. After taking that hit, Wei Chen wished he could Teleport, too. By then, Sealed Mountain Tiger had already turned around. Was he going to give him one final sword to heart? No, Sealed Mountain Tiger’s sword had been sheathed, and he instead held a gun in his hands. The dark opening of the muzzle was aimed at Windward Formation, and the trigger was pulled with extreme prejudice.

The moment the gun flared, Wei Chen’s view blurred and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had managed to rush over just in time, deflecting the hit with his open Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.

Tang Rou, who was always eager for a fight, and Mo Fan, who wanted to prove himself, had both charged forward with their characters.

Sealed Mountain Tiger once again switched weapons, entangling with the two melee characters with his fists and feet. Sealed Mountain Tiger’s power was much more formidable than Alpha, Beta, Gamma, and Delta. Blademaster Alpha could also use "Downwind Sword Slash," but it couldn’t compare to Sealed Mountain Tiger’s, which had the same power as number one Boss Brother Wolf when Enraged.

However, no matter how fiercely Sealed Mountain Tiger fought, he only had a tenth of his health left. Everyone had gone wild with their attacks, only demanding speed from themselves without needing to consider endurance or slowing their pace unless they needed to use potions or wait for skill CDs. For many players who wanted to DPS, they loved the last 10 percent the most.

In this team, no one wanted to raise their DPS more than Mo Fan.

Speaking of which, this last Boss Sealed Mountain Tiger really wasn’t the best to use for comparing DPS. This was because for the first 90%, there were never ending summons, and there wasn’t much point in killing them over and over again. Keeping them alive and under control was more helpful.

That’s what Ye Xiu and his party had done, so those who were responsible for keeping a hold of the summons wouldn’t have high DPS, making DPS comparisons for this Boss rather meaningless.

However, Mo Fan’s Deception had already embarrassed himself on the last four consecutive Bosses. Though he knew that this Boss wouldn’t give him much of a chance to win back his face, he still did his best. Yet the others wouldn’t hold back on this last 10 percent of health either. Explosions thundered across the field and blades cut through the air, all sorts of skills erupted on and around Sealed Mountain Tiger.

This wasn’t just the last 10 percent of health for the Boss, but also the last 10 percent of health for the entire dungeon. They could go wild and exert less caution now. At the end of the dungeon, getting the final victory was the only requirement to success. Even if someone was wiped out in the process, it wouldn’t change that fact.

Of course, no one would completely ignore the state of their health, but they would be able to do a few more risky techniques when attacking.

Sealed Mountain Tiger’s health plummeted.

The health of Happy’s members were also jumping around messily.　An Wenyi was the busiest one. In a chaotic situation like this, he struggled a little. Reaction time and hand speed were his biggest weaknesses.

It was a good thing they also had Ye Xiu

During their offense on Sealed Mountain Tiger, his Unspecialized would send a few heals when An Wenyi lagged behind.

Though the effects might be limited, An Wenyi’s heals were often just a second too late, allowing Lord Grim’s weaker heals to keep near-death characters alive in that one second before Little Cold Hands landed a heal.

In the end, there were no casualties.

This was in part because the players behind the characters were skilled, but more because the healer had a good grasp of the situation on the battlefield.

An Wenyi’s reaction time and hand speed might not be able to keep up, but his awareness and judgement were very clear. He knew how to keep everyone at a safe level of health. It was just that his skill sometimes wasn’t enough to turn thoughts into reality, but with Ye Xiu’s Unspecialized, they were fine.　System Announcement!

Accompanying Sealed Mountain Tiger’s defeat was the eye-catching and timely announcement from the game.

The First Kill announcement for Boss Sealed Mountain Tiger and the entire Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout jumped out in turn.

It was already 3:13 AM by now and the servers were still as crowded as ever. The players might’ve been expecting these two shocking announcements, but they still went berserk upon actually seeing them.　These guys really did it!!!

At level 70, in a ten-person party dungeon, they had managed to clear it on the first try.

This was something impossible for normal players, but Guild Happy had done it. Were these guys really at the pro level already?

With the dungeon cleared, it was time for them to retrieve their First Kill rewards. Compared to these, the drops from the dungeon were pathetic. Sealed Mountain Tiger only dropped two pieces of purple equipment in the end. For normal players, this was enough for them to cry tears of joy. However, for Happy, for a team that wanted to achieve victory in the Challenger’s League, what they wanted was orange equipment.

Relying on dungeons to earn orange equipment was too hard. Yet now, five bosses plus the dungeon itself made six First Kill records. From what they had seen, the rewards from these kinds of records would be at least on par with orange equipment. They just weren’t sure if the total rewards would be decreased after they cleared every single boss.

The current rewards were what Happy truly cared about.

"I’m going to collect them!" Ye Xiu said.

"Go!" Everyone took a deep breath.

"First Boss Vanguard Brother Wolf’s First Kill," Ye Xiu said as he clicked on the rewards for this First Kill.

In the party chat, the system sent a notice.

"Orange words!!" Chen Guo hadn’t even seen what it was, but was already screaming out seeing the color of the words.

"Stay calm!" Ye Xiu said.

"A Weapon!" Chen Guo took another glance and screamed in joy again. Weapons were the most important out of all the pieces of equipment. In the pro circle, the use of silver equipment was far from a hundred percent, but it infinitely neared that rate. The reason it never reached it, was because there would always be new teams that dragged the overall percentage down every season.

Vanguard Brother Wolf’s First Kill, rewarded equipment: Killing Wolf.

Level 75 Tachi.

Weight 2.4 kg, Endurance 24, Attack Speed 8;

Melee Attack 750, Magic Attack 800;

Strength +42, Intelligence +35;　Melee Crit Rate +10%;

Attack Speed +3;

Downwind Sword Slash Skill Level +3;

Upon attack, there is a 5% chance of weakening the target’s Melee defense by 10% for 5 seconds.

Everyone’s cursor and attention were all on Killing Wolf, admiring the stats of the equipment, until Ye Xiu spoke up, "Does anyone of us use swords here?"

"Ah?" Qiao Yifan responded.

"Er, here, you take it?" Ye Xiu asked. His question wasn’t because he didn’t want anyone else to use it, but because Killing Wolf didn’t really suit One Inch Ash’s Phantom Demon.

Tachis were a rather well-rounded kind of sword, used for both melee and magic and an apt choice for any of the four swordsman classes. Which exact sword one should use still depended on the bonuses that the sword gave though. From the bonuses on Killing Wolf, it could be seen that Killing Wolf was more suited for Blademasters. If not, then Berserkers and Sword Demons were a good choice as well. However, Phantom Demons and Spellblades wouldn’t earn much of an advantage from using this tachi.

One Inch Ash was currently using an Orange short sword. Short swords had the strongest magic attack and Intelligence bonuses among the sword types. If you were really to compare Killing Wolf to One Inch Ash’s short sword, then Killing Wolf wouldn’t even provide advantages in the basic stats. One Inch Ash didn’t need to switch weapons at all.

"I don’t think I have any use for this…?" Qiao Yifan was, of course, clear on this as well.

"Just hang onto it for now!" Ye Xiu said.

Though they had gotten a weapon their team didn’t really need, Glory didn’t bind equipment to player accounts, so the weapon still had value to it. If it was another game, they might not be as happy about it.

With the first Boss giving them a piece of orange equipment, everyone was very confident. It seemed that even the individual Boss rewards were very bountiful.

"Second Boss!" Ye Xiu announced as he collected the rewards for the First kill of the second Boss, Head Guard Sand Leopard.

"Ah! So much!!" As soon as the notice popped up in the party chat, Chen Guo expressed her surprise again. This time, there were three rewards. Yet with another look, all the rewards were something something stone, something something wood; they didn’t sound like equipment. Hovering their cursor over the names, they were three materials, as expected.

The materials that came from a dungeon record rewards would be on par with wild Boss drops. However, with what little they knew about level 75 materials, the three materials: Sealed Mountain Stone, Sealed Mountain Wood, Blue Fang Moon… The worth of these materials that sounded like local specialities would have to be researched.

Then it was the third Boss, Tactician Frigid Eagle.

Though, out of the five Bosses, Frigid Eagle was the weakest individual, he still had a First Kill record, so the rewards wouldn’t be bad. Plus, with all the ambushes that Frigid Eagle had planned, and teaming up with the fourth Boss after that, it was a major test of player endurance. If they were less skilled at controlling their own pace, then this round would probably have been even harder than the Final Boss.

Frigid Eagle’s First Kill reward was a pair of leather boots with a very character-specific name called Frigid Eagle’s Boots.

The stats were, of course, orange equipment level. Apart from the basic melee defense, it added a bonus of 30 Intelligence, 12 movement speed, and 10 jump power.

For a pair of shoes like this, the bonus to Intelligence was great for a Witch. However, for Battle Mages, Intelligence was also important. Without a doubt, this pair of shoes went to Soft Mist.

"Next one!" Ye Xiu said as he clicked on the First Kill reward for the fourth Boss, Vice Chief Brown Bear.

Chapter 872: First Kill Rewards (2)

The boss Brown Bear could be considered a Berserker, but his unique spiked club definitely wouldn’t drop. In Glory, boss drops wouldn’t be universal. Nearly all boss drops matched the boss’s class. For example, a physical type boss like Brown Bear wouldn’t drop mage-related equipment.

Although Happy wasn’t obtaining these items from the boss’s corpse, from the First Kill rewards of the previous three bosses, the rewards all complied with the boss drop rules.

After clicking on the button to receive the rewards, a message immediately popped up in their team chat.

Sealed Mountain Heavy Armor

This was the Brown Bear’s First Kill reward, a Level 75 Orange heavy armor. +37 Strength, +28 Vitality, -20 Spirit, Physical Defense +10%, Strength +4%, Vitality +4%, Spirit -10%....

This heavy armor focused on strengthening the basic stats. This type of equipment weren’t specific to a class. If the stats and armor proficiency matched your needs, it was suitable to use, but this Sealed Mountain Heavy Armor had a flaw just like its original owner. While it strengthened strength and vitality, it also weakened spirit.

In the pro scene, where a small detail could decided victory or defeat, this small flaw was extremely detrimental. The spirit stat closely related to the effects of buffs and debuffs. In a high-level confrontation, such things were crucial. No one in the pro scene would be brave enough to use a piece of equipment that lowered spirit.

The value of Silver equipment could be seen here. Even if the stats weren’t too outstanding, it wouldn’t have a troublesome flaw that made it hard to use. For successful Silver equipment, every stat would beneficial.

Sealed Mountain Heavy Armor clearly wouldn’t have any market value in the pro scene. However, utilizing it as research material wouldn’t be bad. Ye Xiu took the piece of equipment and clicked on the First Kill rewards for the final boss Sealed Mountain Tiger.

"Orange equipment!"

"Weapon!!"

Even though it was their fifth time receive First Kill rewards, Chen Guo was still as excited as ever. As soon as she saw the most valuable type of equipment appear again, she cried out in joy.

At this point, some of them hadn’t even checked what it was yet, when Chen Guo leaked it out.

Tiger Seal.

Just from listening to its name, it didn’t seem like anything impressive. It was only after hearing Chen Guo’s cry did everyone hover over it to see the true appearance of this weapon.

It was a magic staff.

Weight: 3.0kg. Durability: 30. Attack Speed: 10.

Physical Attack: 270

Magic Attack: 825

Intelligence +40

Spirit +20

Cast Speed +12%

Restores 3% mana every minute

Whip: Effects +10%

Tiger Seal - Physical summons have their battle strength increase by 20% inside a nine coordinate area with the staff at the center.

No one in Team Happy was a noob now. At worst, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Luo Ji hadn’t been playing for very long and didn’t have an extremely deep understanding of certain concepts.

But after seeing the stats for Tiger Seal, everyone was silent for a good half a minute.

"Top tier!" Ye Xiu was the first to speak up.

"What? It’s the top of the top!" Wei Chen gaven an even higher evaluation of it.

"What’s the best Summoner Silver weapon right now?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That’s not important." Wei Chen replied.

"Could Tiger Seal be even better than the current best Summoner Silver weapon?" Chen Guo was astonished. The exact stats of Silver weapons were treated as secrets by the various clubs. The stats wouldn’t be publicly announced. They didn’t want their opponents to know. Only the owner would know the precises stats of their Silver weapons. Anyone else could only guesstimate through real combat.

However, as the scene developed, pro players began moving around more frequently. Hoping for the transferred player to protect the secrets of their old club had no way of being monitored, so the stats of Silver equipment was becoming more and more transparent. That was still only limited to the pro scene though. After all, no player would transfer several times in a row just to report information on all the team’s Silver equipment. As a result, although it could be said that the stats weren’t a secret, it was still confined to a limited area. Perhaps after one transfer, the two teams wouldn’t have many secrets left, that’s all.

If the information was still a mystery among pro teams, it would be even more of a mystery to normal players. Apart from those that had been released to the public, the rest were all guesses. Wei Chen had left the pro scene long ago, so he didn’t have any reputable information sources. Of course, with his skill, if he took the time and effort to conduct research, his conclusions would be a lot more accurate than those random guesses by the average player. He didn’t have that sort of leisure time though. If he had to do research, he would research the classes that he was interested in, like Warlocks. Wei Chen didn’t have much of an understanding of Summoner Silver equipment, yet this guy acted like he did, saying "It’s not important." It was as if Tiger Seal crushed its competitors, exciting Chen Guo.

"Saying which one’s better or worse can’t be clearly determined with just a few words. It depends on the player’s style and needs, but at the very least, this Tiger Seal can contend with any Level 70 Silver Summoner weapon. It’s a weapon that’s enough to dictate a character’s skill tree." Ye Xiu said.

"Is it because of Tiger Seal’s effects?" Chen Guo could still realize this point.

"Of course." Ye Xiu said.

According to the description for Tiger Seal’s effects, a nine coordinate area was the equivalent of a 30 by 30 unit square. That was quite a considerable region. And a 20% increase in battle strength... in Glory, battle strength wasn’t a single stat. It was a comprehensive term equivalent to saying a increase in 20% for every stat.

With these effects, if the Summoner wielding Tiger Seal didn’t use physical summons as his main pets, that would be too wasteful.

"Concealed Light, this staff is for you." Ye Xiu said.

It was obvious who should be the one to take this valuable weapon. Unfortunately, Luo Ji was clearly the weakest one among the team, yet the first piece of equipment that was a huge improvement than before had to be his class…...

Of course, he couldn’t say these words out loud. Wouldn’t that hurt Luo Ji’s confidence?

Luo Ji understood this very well. Tiger Seal was a mighty weapon, but it ended up with him. He expressed his apologies.

"Don’t be like that." Ye Xiu said, "Keep working hard, so you can use this weapon to strengthen our team!"　　

"I will." Luo Ji held his head high and made a solemn vow.

"Tiger Seal.... A skill effect that has never appeared before should be studied." Wei Chen said.

"Let’s do that later. It’s time for the final reward!" Ye Xiu sucked in a deep breath. Next would be the reward for clearing the dungeon for the first time. Compared to the individual bosses, the first clear rewards should be more generous, no?　　

"Hurry up and accept it!" Wei Chen was getting impatient.

Afterwards, a string of messages flashed onto his chat window. Sure enough, the rewards for a First Clear were more generous than for a First Kill. It gave their team a total of two pieces of Orange equipment and four material drops.

The uses for the materials were still unknown, so the materials were naturally not mentioned. Of the two pieces of Orange equipment, one was plate armor, Sealed Dusk Belt. Strength +16, Vitality +16, Physical Defense +5%, +3 to Stun, Knockback, and Blow Away resistance. It clearly emphasized physical defense.

The stats of this belt were quite good, but there were only three classes proficient with belts: Knights, Paladins, and Spellblades. Team Happy had none of these classes, so this belt naturally fell into Lord Grim’s hands.

Apart from Sealed Dusk Belt, the other Orange accessory was Smoke Stream Necklace.

Accessories had no weight. The basic stat was Magic Defense. Apart from that, Smoke Heart Necklace added 45 to Intelligence, +5 to Jump, +10 to Broom Flying Speed, 5% chance for Star Ray to have Smoke Stream’s effects.

From its support stats, it was undoubtedly made for Witches. As for Smoke Stream’s effects, it was something new. No one had heard of it before.

"This... let’s keep it to test for now!" Ye Xiu decided. For non-Witches, it only added +5 to Jump and +45 to Intelligence. The supplementary effects couldn’t be used. Next, they needed to see what exactly this Smoke Stream was. If it was valuable, then from this equipment, they could research how to reproduce these Smoke Stream effects. This type of work was what people, who wanted to create self-equipment, studied all day. 　

It was too early for that now. As of now, everyone was still Level 70. No one could use Level 75 equipment yet, so for now, they wouldn’t even be able to see the effects of Smoke Stream.

"Okay, that’s it." Apart from these rewards was experience points. Compared to quest rewards, the amount of experience was quite substantial. However, hoping to be leading the leveling charts with just this was too optimistic.　

Ye Xiu’s group had cleared Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout in roughly three hours. They took all of the first kills, but setting a dungeon record was still far away.

　

The dungeon record didn’t start from when the first team cleared the dungeon, but rather a set time determined by the system. The dungeon record would be broken starting from this preset time.

Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout’s initial time was one hour. It had taken Happy three hours. They were still far far away from reaching that mark. It could also be seen from this that clearing Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout in three hours wasn’t efficient. However, obtaining those first kill rewards was a huge convenience. They had a lead over the club guilds by who knew how much.

"Which dungeon should we run next?" Chen Guo was very excited being able to take advantage of this moment. The normal players weren’t even close to beating these Level 75 dungeons. They could freely choose which first kills they wanted to take.

"Hmm... let’s see. In order to maximize efficiency, we should split into two teams and run two different five man dungeons." Ye Xiu said.　

"Good idea!" Chen Guo praised.

"Okay then. Let’s split into two groups." Ye Xiu said.

"If we do that, will the healing be enough?" Wu Chen asked.　

Even though Lord Grim had some healing capabilities, it could only be used in dire situations. Relying on those heals to survive was not possible in these difficult dungeons.　　

"No problem." Ye Xiu laughed, "I’ll just play as a Cleric."　　

"If we do that, then we won’t have enough MTs?" Wu Chen asked.

"Okay then, I’ll just use a Paladin account. That should work too, right?" Ye Xiu said.

Everyone was silent. Being proficient at every class was just too shameless.

Chapter 873: Sullen Kitten

Paladins, like Knights and Clerics, were also categorized as Priest type classes.

This class was able to equip plate armor with powerful defensive capabilities. On top of that, they had healing skills that didn’t lose to that of Clerics and even had some defensive buff skills, so it wasn’t uncommon for them to be the MT. However, those who were both the MT and healer of a team, like Ye Xiu was doing, were all experts. It wasn’t something that just anyone could achieve. For Glory’s Encyclopedia, there was no doubt that he could do it.

After arranging the teams, Ye Xiu went rifling through the drawers to find an account card to use. Chen Guo, on the other hand, ran to the main city to find equipment for their new Paladin. The others stocked up on items and repaired their equipment as needed, eager to get another First Kill.

Only one person was uncommonly depressed: Mo Fan.

The experience bonus from First Kills was something that everyone gained. As for equipment, there wasn’t a single piece that Deception could use.

Yet that wasn’t what Mo Fan cared about; what he cared about was still his DPS.

When the Boss Sealed Mountain Tiger finally fell, he had taken a look at the chart. As expected, the DPS chart wasn’t a good judge this time. Lord Grim, Dawn Rifle, Chasing Haze, and Steamed Bun Invasion were responsible for killing the Boss and were thus far ahead of everyone else. As for those who were dealing with the summons, their aim was to keep the summons from interfering, not to kill the summons. If someone who didn’t know the details took a look, they would probably think that the ones responsible for summons had played dead for the entire battle.　

Mo Fan impatiently wished to prove himself, yet they had met a Boss like this. It was frustrating as hell. With this Boss killed, he had run off to look at the DPS charts alone. As for Ye Xiu? He had drawn up the DPS charts for everyone to see for each Boss, yet this time he hadn’t even mentioned it, running off to collect the rewards with the others.　　

Mo Fan gloomily checked the rewards with the others, only perking up upon hearing that they were going to continue running dungeons. However, when he realized that they were splitting into two teams, he was a little disappointed. He had wanted to continue competing in the environment of a ten person dungeon.

But anything was better than nothing.

Soon enough, the teams were decided.

One team was made up of Wei Chen, Tang Rou, Qiao Yifan, Luo Ji, and An Wenyi.

Mo Fan was put with the remaining four, Ye Xiu, Steamed Bun, Wu Chen, and Chen Guo.

Wei Chen’s team stocked up on items before setting off. As for their side, Ye Xiu was still rummaging around for that account card, and since it was an empty account, they had to get equipment for it, too. Mo Fan was impatiently waiting to begin.

Chen Guo took a look around the market and quickly managed to obtain the necessary pieces of equipment.

With the new level limit, all level 70 weapons, apart from orange ones, were facing obsolescence. This preliminary stage of exploring the new update was their last chance to get rid of such items for profit. So, there were plenty of level 70 weapons on the market; no one hid them anymore.　

Chen Guo’s wander around the market allowed her to obtain a set of equipment that was originally scarcely possible to obtain. It was all top quality purple equipment, and the price was much lower than it once would’ve been. For level 70 orange equipment, its stats were on par with level 75 purple equipment, so they wouldn’t become obsolete just yet. However, once level 75 purple equipment began to flood the market, level 70 orange equipment wouldn’t be highly-valued items any longer. Currently, orange equipment was still hard to come by, but Ye Xiu’s Paladin was just a temporary character, so there was no need to spend too much on it. Purple equipment was enough, that was what Ye Xiu himself had said. So, Chen Guo didn’t worry about if what purple equipment she had was good enough.　

The card was found, the character logged in and equipped the equipment that Chen Guo had obtained. The second team was finally good to go. Mo Fan rubbed his hands, vowing to get a beautiful DPS in this five person party.　　

Small, five-person dungeons were aplenty. Barrier Mountains alone had two. Plus, five-person dungeons were there to help players accumulate equipment, so it’s difficulty and rewards were incomparable to larger team dungeons. Of course, Ye Xiu and co weren’t aiming for the drops, but the First Kill and First Clear rewards. These rewards were part of a competition between players, so they had little to do with the difficulty of the dungeon itself. There was little difference in the rewards, still having a great chance to give them pieces of orange equipment.　

Wei Chen’s team had entered a dungeon first, so Ye Xiu’s team headed for the remaining five-person dungeon, Barrier Mountain’s Snowstorm Mine.　　

Again, the backstory of the place was completely ignored as they darted inside.　　

Ye Xiu’s Paladin had to charge at the front as the MT. Everyone met up at the entrance of the dungeon and then directly entered. This was when the other three members of their team saw the name of Ye Xiu’s account and immediate felt their stomachs contract.　

Ye Xiu’s Paladin was a female character, but what was even more strange when considering the player behind it was the name.

Sullen Kitten...　

Even a stoic guy like Mo Fan felt the corner of his lips spasming with response. Wu Chen was a calm guy, but this was a little too difficult to bear. His head hung so low that it was almost on his keyboard.　

Only Steamed Bun’s personality was blunt and frank. Steamed Bun Invasion stepped forward, circling Sullen Kitten a few times and asking, "Who are you? I think you joined the wrong party."　

"Ahem..." Chen Guo coughed. She had seen the name upon giving the character equipment, and had time to get used to the unfamiliarity. She spoke up for Ye Xiu. "It’s just an open account, don’t think too much about it."

"Whose?" Steamed Bun asked in surprise.

"Your boss." Chen Guo replied.

"Just as unique as expected!" Steamed Bun continued to say in surprise, circling the character again.　

"Ok, ok, let’s start the dungeon." Sullen Kitten spoke with Ye Xiu’s voice, "There’s no need to say too much for a small dungeon. We can research it as we fight."　

Ye Xiu’s words were very agreeable, most likely because it would be him who was also responsible for the healing. He was very confident that he would be able to keep the situation under control. As soon as the words fell, his Sullen Kitten rushed forth. Even the heavy plate armor couldn’t hide this female character’s petite and delicate figure. Watching the figure disappear into a sea of monsters, everyone coughed to cover up their inner turmoil.　

Paladin was a class that could be used as an MT, but it wasn’t as mainstream as Knights. A large reason was because Paladins were slow at pulling aggro and were rather passive. They weren’t like Knights that, after a Charge, other classes could immediately start attacking. For Paladins, they needed more time to accumulate aggro.　

The delicate Sullen Kitten swung around a massive Hell Stone Battle Axe. However, compared to the contrast between player and character, the contrast between weapon and character was almost negligible.　

Sullen Kitten, ankle deep in monsters, tossed up her Hell Stone Battle Axe, which quickly turned into a falling star that smashed into the ground, causing a small scale earthquake.　　

This was a under level 20 skill for Exorcists: Star Fall. The current method Ye Xiu was using to pull mobs was a rather common method for tanking Paladins.　　

Ye Xiu, of course, had no problems with his technical skill. Once his teammates had woken from their daze at the contrast between player and character, they quickly joined in, DPSing.　　

There might’ve been a five level difference between them and the monsters, but with their skill, these five-person small dungeon mobs were a joke. Ye Xiu didn’t need to take command since everyone was doing fine, with their skill. Chen Guo wasn’t as good as the others, but she focused on doing her part, launching attacks from afar; this role of hers was very safe.　　

The road was smooth going; the few bumps that popped up were easily overcome. Since it was Ye Xiu who was responsible for keeping everyone’s health at a safe level, they’re characters weren’t in danger of falling so long as they were in his cast range.　　

Using heals to pull aggro was also an important aspect of MT’ing for Paladins. In fact, for a skilled party like them, a Paladin wasn’t a very appropriate MT. Since their individual skill level was quite high, they were often able to avoid damage. The less health they lost, the less pressure there was on the healer.　　

On your average team, it was a good thing if the healer didn’t have much pressure on them. However, when your MT was a Paladin, the healer needed a more pressure since this would make up for the Paladin’s lack of aggroing skills. So Ye Xiu sometimes had to purposefully let the mobs hit him and force aggro by healing himself. How much health he should give up and how much he should heal all relied on his own judgement.　　

Soon enough, their party had arrived at Snowstorm Mine’s first Boss: Head Miner Zalu.　　

Zalu held an oil lamp in one hand and it seemed like that was his weapon. Out of the 24 classes, the only class that dangled their weapon from their hand like that seemed to only be the Cleric.　　

But a Cleric as a Boss… Where would it’s offensive capabilities come from?　　

"I’ll go first." Ye Xiu went up to test the Boss, just like always. As soon as Sullen Kitten stepped into Zalu’s aggro range, they saw Zalu swing his lanturn and the oil light within shone out at Sullen Kitten. Following that, the light flashed and, with a loud roar, a streak of fire blazed out Sullen Kitten.　　

"That’s Flamethrower!" With that, Ye Xiu realized that his Boss was actually a Gunner. This guy was using an oil lamp as a gun! That was pretty creative, to be honest.　

As he spoke, his hands also moved. Sullen Kitten threw out a horizontal slash with her Hell Stone Battle Axe, and the axe front smacked against the streak of fire. The moment the two came into contact, the axe’s surface shone with white light and the streak of fire swerved in the direction the swing.　　

Paladin skill: Halo Smash. It was a defensive skill that could send any oncoming attack in a different direction, both physical and magical attacks.　　

The streak of fire that was sent off was, as Ye Xiu had planned, smacked back into Zalu himself.

The Boss didn’t seem very dexterous, unable to dodge the returned attack. The streak of fire smacked right into him. He cried out and spun his oil lamp like a windmill, sending lamp oil scattering through the air like rain. Soon enough, the drops of oil ignited in midair and turned into a hail of fire that fell towards Sullen Kitten.

"Huh, interesting." Ye Xiu decided to have Sullen Kitten stay without dodging this time, testing out the power of this move. Instantly, he was hit by several small fireballs. He healed himself as he took careful note of the damage and he quickly gained a good understanding of the Boss’ power.

"Let’s go, everyone!" Ye Xiu thought that this sort of Boss didn’t need too much figuring out. With his words, the other four immediately began to attack.

Chapter 874: Only Two First Clears

As Ye Xiu expected, the small boss with the oil lamp wasn’t hard to deal with. Since he shouldered the responsibility of both MT and healer, the most complicated tasks were done by him. The others could more or less just mindlessly DPS.

The battle was swift, but Wei Chen’s team was faster with their head start, Ye Xiu and co hadn’t even finished their boss off when they vaguely heard those guys sighing over something.

These sounds came from out of the game, and since the sounds of battle were rather intense, Ye Xiu didn’t hear them clearly. Yet, soon enough, Wei Chen yelled at him from where he was sitting next to Ye Xiu, "The bosses of these small dungeons don’t seem to have a First Kill reward!"

Ye Xiu paused for a moment before he realized what had happened.

Wei Chen’s team had already killed off the first boss in their dungeon, but there had been no system announcement. No wonder they seemed so disappointed. The rewards for these records were their true goal. If the individual bosses didn’t have First Kill rewards, then that meant this whole dungeon would only give one First Clear reward each.

However, they were already here, so they wouldn’t just give up halfway. After wallowing in a moment of disappointment, they continued running the dungeon.　

Ye Xiu and co soon finished with Head Miner Zalu as well. The system didn’t respond, just like Wei Chen had said. The items dropped from Zalu were only a few pieces of blue equipment, something they didn’t even need to look at.

"If we had known this earlier, then we would be in a ten-player dungeon by now!" Wei Chen was still ranting, his headphones around his neck, "We don’t really even need to use headphones and mics, really."

That was rather true actually. Everyone was sitting in the same room after all, so they could just talk directly. They didn’t need the voice chat in game. Since they had split, it would be better for their communication if they didn’t wear headphones. As for the sounds from the game, they didn’t really need it since the small dungeon wasn’t difficult enough for them to require it to make judgements.

Everyone then took off their headphones. Wei Chen’s group was already enroute to the next boss. As for Ye Xiu’s side? As soon as Zalu fell, Mo Fan impatiently clicked open the DPS chart.

This time’s DPS was finally at an acceptable level, compared to how it was in Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout. However, Mo Fan was still a little dissatisfied with his performance, because he was only second on the chart, not first. The first was still Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle. During their run of Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout, Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle was always first as well.

Deception’s DPS was a little worse than Dawn Rifle’s, but not by much. However, Steamed Bun’s DPS that followed his wasn’t far behind either. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze, on the other hand, was a larger distance behind them. Mo Fan didn’t bother looking at hers though. In his eyes, Chen Guo didn’t even count as a competitor.

It wasn’t completely satisfactory, but it wasn’t too bad either!

Mo Fan perked up a little at seeing his DPS this, but then he saw that Ye Xiu’s Sullen Kitten was already charging ahead with her massive axe. Did he not have any intentions to discuss this round’s DPS?

Mo Fan’s spirits fell.

This was a premeditated attack on him, wasn’t it?

When he saw that Mo Fan had done well, he didn’t say anything; when he saw that Mo Fan had done badly, he had to bring it up to humiliate Mo Fan? This guy was as vicious as ever!

Mo Fan’s thought spun wildly, but he still urged Deception forth to catch up with the rest of the team.

After that there were mobs, then the second boss, and then the third. The difficulty of a five player dungeon was negligible for these experts. Not long after Wei Chen’s team had finished, they had cleared Snowstorm Mine as well.

Unlike team dungeons, which often only allowed a character’s entry once a day or even once a week, the new level 75 five-player dungeons all let a single character enter up to three times each day. This was why many guilds and players were researching them. If they could get more time to figure out the dungeons, some expert players might actually be able to clear them. Three tries were too few though. Ye Xiu and co might’ve been a bit late to the party, but they managed to clear it on their first try; the First Clears were easily taken by them.

The players on the global chat were all admiring this, and there was no need to discuss how the leaders of the big guilds felt. Wasn’t this just dandy? Three First Clears had been bound to Happy’s name already. These records would be immortalized in the game.

And on Ye Xiu’s side? The two teams were preparing to collect their respective First Clear rewards, Wei Chen bet Ye Xiu a pack of smokes that their rewards would be better than Ye Xiu’s.

"Hahahahaha!" Their reward was revealed amidst Wei Chen’s laughter.

"A weapon!" Wei Chen announced with triumph. This weapon was half a win for their bet, as weapons were far more valuable than other pieces of equipment.

However, Weki Chen’s expression fell a little upon checking the type of weapon.

Blood Chipper Greatsword.

It was Orange, and the stats weren’t bad, but it was, unfortunately, not something Team Happy’s members needed. The only swordsman, Ghostblade One Inch Ash, would never use a Greatsword. Even Sword Demons would never use the completely melee focused Greatsword in the Pro League.

"This effect seems interesting!" Ye Xiu said, looking at the Blood Chip effect that was at the bottom.

Blood Chip: 3% chance to inflict Blood Chip, reducing the target’s max HP by 1%

"Just 1 percent? That’s not much," Wei Chen said.

"But what about against a boss?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Boss…?" Wei Chen paused for a second, "It would be useless against a boss too, unless it activated immediately. If they took a whole percent of health as damage, that’s pretty terrifying. It’s just that this effect is has too low of a chance to activate. If it doesn’t activate immediately, then after a while, the boss would’ve long since lost more than a percent of its health and the effect would only work to reduce its maximum health, and what use would that have?"

"It might be useful in some special situations," Ye Xiu suggested.

"It won’t be very useful in PvP, at least," Wei Chen said.

"There’s a one percent, so who’s to say there’s no five percent, or even ten?" Ye Xiu said.

"Hm, if that’s the case…" Wei Chen wavered a little.

"Let’s just hang onto it for now!" Ye Xiu said.　Without these words, the weapon would be deemed useless, just like the blue and purple equipment they had gotten from the other boss drops. Those would be thrown into the guild storage later. As for Orange weapons like this, they would research the stats for their silver equipment development.

"What’s your reward?" Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu hadn’t collected it yet. Seeing Wei Chen paying attention to his screen, he clicked it.

It was also a piece of orange equipment. The rewards for the First Clear of a five player dungeon were incomparable to the rewards of a team dungeon, too. Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout had given them two pieces of orange equipment and four materials for First Clear. On the other hand, their five player dungeons only gave out a single piece of orange equipment each, on par with a First Kill of an individual boss in a team dungeon.

"Hurry up and take a look!" Wei Chen urged.

The orange words: Cloud Bust Moonfall. They didn’t hint at what sort of equipment it was at all.

Ye Xiu’s cursor hovered over it and it’s information popped up. Wei Chen fell silent, because he had lost.

Cloudless Moonfall was a Spear and, in Happy, Tang rou’s Soft Mist was an obvious choice of user. This reward had found itself an owner.　Cloud Bust Moonfall.

Weight 3.5 kg, Durability 35, Attack Speed 3;

Physical Attack 911, Magic Attack 632;　Strength +55;

Attack Speed +1;

Crit Rate +12;

Light Element attacks;　When attacking with Chasers, there was a 5 percent chance that an extra same-element Chaser would be generated and hit the target directly, doing piercing damage.　With Ye Xiu, who was so well versed in the Battle Mage class, the others didn’t feel like they had a right to even comment on the weapon. As for Ye Xiu? He very much satisfied with this spear.

With just the basic stat of Attack Speed, this spear had 3 in comparison to the slowest 1 that was common among spears. Then, it even had a bonus to Attack Speed of +1, so that made the overall Attack Speed 4, an incredible improvement. This was something both valuable and hard to come by for spears.

Apart from that, the additional bonuses for Strength and Crit Rate were common on spears. Cloud Bust Moonfall had stats that were deserving of its status as a level 75 orange weapon. As for Light Element attacks, that had to be judged according to the situation. A weapon with an element would mean that resistances also had to be taken into account during damage calculation. If the target had high resistance to Darkness, then Light element attacks would do far more damage; if they had high resistance to Light, then the damage would be greatly reduced. Ice and Fire didn’t affect Light Element attacks directly, but the damage from an elemental attack would be slightly higher than a damage from a non-elemental attack. Overall, a weapon with an element might give you an advantage over your target, but might also give you a disadvantage. It was hard to judge the overall benefits compared to the situational ones.

As for the last effect, it was something new to level 75. Ye Xiu had never seen anything like it either. From the description, this was definitely a great addition to one’s DPS. Five percent was a bit low, but if there was a high chance of an effect like this activating, then that would be too overpowered.

Overall, Cloud Bust Moonfall wasn’t as eye catching as the Tiger Seal that they had obtained earlier, but the stats were a good bonus and even the Light Element wasn’t something that would drag you down. Without a doubt, this was a weapon that should be immediately equipped upon reaching level 75, so it would definitely be given to Soft Mist.　

"Five-player dungeons are boring. How about we find another ten player dungeon instead?" Wei Chen suggested after they exited from their respective dungeons. With just a single reward item waiting for them at the end, five player dungeons weren’t really worth it.

"Sure. There’s two more ten player dungeons, right?" Ye Xiu said.

In the three new level 75 areas announced, only Barrier Mountains had a ten-player dungeon. However, everyone now knew that the other three areas that were revealed with the update would also have two other ten player dungeons.

Everyone prepared to head of to the ten player dungeons. Mo Fan was rather depressed though. The five player dungeon had been cleared and though he hadn’t overtaken Wu Chen, his DPS wasn’t bad. Yet what was the worst was that Ye Xiu didn’t talk about DPS at all for this run. Mo Fan couldn’t take it anymore and, for the first time ever, initiated a conversation, "Aren’t we going to take a look at the DPS?"

"Oh? I forgot to look during that run. We’ll check when we do the ten player dungeon later," Ye Xiu replied calmly.

Chapter 875: Studying DPS

Mo Fan was never one to speak nimbly. As soon as he thought of what to say, Ye Xiu had logged off. For a ten player dungeon, Ye Xiu would obviously choose to use Lord Grim over Sullen Kitten.

Gray Corner.

One of the six new areas.

It was located in the southeast region of the Heavenly Domain mainland. It was the largest of the six new areas and the one with the most dungeons.　　

Gray Corner had three five-player dungeons, one ten-player dungeon, one twenty-player dungeon, one fifty-player dungeon, and one hundred-player dungeon. Every dungeon option was available at Gray Corner.

All six new areas opened simultaneously, but if you followed the quest chains, the areas were linked together in certain places. Gray Corner was considered the final map for those who were rushing to Level 75.

Gray Corner was set up as a gray area, where fish and dragons mixed together. This sort of place was an especially vicious and atrocious place. Gray Corner’s ten player dungeon was located inside the city, but it wasn’t difficult to find. If you went through the teleportation formation to the city, you would find it rather quickly.

Ten player dungeon: Underground Market.

Yes, the Underground Market became a place of slaughter. The environment of Gray Corner could clearly be seen here.

Happy’s team of ten didn’t talk too much about this place and quickly reached the dungeon entrance. It was already four in the morning. The number of players in the game had decreased significantly compared to before, especially near ten-player dungeons. There weren’t many sightseeing teams left. Even if you were just there to take a look around, it still used your dungeon entry.

Without saying a word, the team entered the dungeon.

The monsters in the Underground Market looked like dutiful buyers and sellers, but the fight they put wasn’t any worse than those Sealed Mountain Thieves. The team followed their usual strategy. Lord Grim assumed the role of the main tank. Everyone fought cautiously against them as if these monsters were all bosses. After familiarizing themselves with the features of these monsters and a certain level of coordination had been established, they slowly increased their speed through the dungeon.

The Underground Market had five bosses, just like Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout. It took them longer to familiarize themselves with the monsters this time. They had already spent around forty minutes before meeting the boss.

Blackhearted Peddler Niles. He had a ferocious appearance. It looked like he’d have more of a future as thief than a peddler. When this guy appeared, he wasn’t alone. He dragged his entire gang of hoodlums into the fray. As soon as he saw Lord Grim and the others emerge, he shouted for them to attack. There was no time for any sort of negotiation. The aggression towards them was completely unreasonable.

Team Happy was helpless. Wei Chen cursed at the system’s stupidity, but they could only square up and face them.

Including Niles, there were ten enemies, the same as the player count.

Fortunately, the team’s strength was up to par. Moreover, at Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout against Advisor Frigid Eagle, they had some practice on how to deal with a mob of monsters with the same numbers as them. The only difference was that the boss had come out to battle as well. The boss led the assault too. Before the two sides clashed, he raised his hands and roared. A shadow flew out. On their side, Steamed Bun cried out, "Ah!"

Steamed Bun Invasion had been hit. His "Ah!" appeared to be of a cry of joy though.

Soon afterwards, Steamed Bun’s overjoyed voice followed: "He’s a Brawler!"

Everyone was speechless.

Blackhearted Peddler Niles had thrown a brick. It was the Brawler’s Brick Buster. Steamed Bun seemed to have found a sense of belonging with the boss.

"Let me deal with him!" Steamed Bun wanted to rush over.

"First, deal with that one next to you. I’ll handle him for now." Ye Xiu hastily said. Even with a five level disadvantage, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun wouldn’t have any problems dueling small mobs. However, against an unfamiliar ten-player dungeon boss, Ye Xiu felt like it was more reliable for him to be the one to sense out the boss. After all, he was more experienced. Even though the boss was unfamiliar, just from his actions so far, he could already make numerous predictions. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun didn’t have the ability to do that just yet.

Steamed Bun didn’t object to Ye Xiu’s words. He turned his hands and threw the brick at the monster next to him, while saying: "Okay boss! Take good care of him for me!"

"Sure….." Ye Xiu replied and then went to block Niles.

In this chaotic battle, An Wenyi once again had the most pressure on him. If any of them messed up, the healing pressure on him was enormous.

The experience felt scarier than the outcome. Apart from the boss, his nine followers were cleared away rather easily. During this time, Ye Xiu had grasped the boss’s attack patterns. Afterwards, he adjusted their formation and everyone attacked. Everything went smoothly. Soon, the boss reached red blood. Ye Xiu waited the instant before the boss turned Enraged before escaping, while everyone else retreated first. Nile’s Enrage wasn’t a terrifying killer move though, and he quickly fell under their attacks.

First Kill!　

As expected, a First Kill appeared for a mini-boss in this dungeon. The team was pleased with the outcome. The outside players quietly cursed. The club guilds continued to cry.

Not waiting for Ye Xiu to speak up, Mo Fan checked the DPS charts.

As soon as he checked, his mind went blank. He hoped Ye Xiu would forget to check just like he did in the five-player dungeon.

But Ye Xiu just had to mention it. He even added more fuel to the fire: "Didn’t that someone want to check the DPS charts just a moment ago?"

That someone had been Mo Fan of course. He had already checked the charts. When he heard Ye Xiu point at him, he couldn’t help but tighten his grip around the mouse.

Everything seemed to be the same as Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout.

Number one was Dawn Rifle. Wu Chen had come from the pro scene. His skill was practiced. Launchers were high DPS characters to begin with, so Wu Chen’s performance had stayed on top.

Number two was Lord Grim. This time, he wasn’t higher than Dawn Rifle, but his pull over the aggro was very steady, so his DPS wasn’t far behind Dawn Rifle’s. He also belonged in the top ranks of the DPS chart.

Third and fourth place was Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. Fifth place was Windward Formation. Sixth place was One Inch Ash.

Seventh, eighth, ninth belonged to the sandbaggers: Deception, Concealed Light, Chasing Haze.

However, Concealed Light and Chasing Haze had good reason for their poor DPS. Everyone recognized their contributions.

Mo Fan wanted to go mad. What’s going on? Why is my DPS a total mess when I play with the team? It wasn’t like that in the five-player dungeon!

Not even mentioning how far away the six above him were, just among the three in the bottom group, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze was only slightly lower than Deception and Concealed Light. Although Concealed Light lost to Deception by only a bit, Mo Fan knew very well that Ye Xiu had restricted his usage of summons to just four. It was only under these restrictions that Concealed Light had lost to him. If it was under normal circumstances and Concealed Light went all out? Deception would probably lose by quite a lot more.

In reality, Deception had even lost to the four summons Concealed Light occasionally.

"Mm, the DPS chart is still like this. There’s nothing much to say. Those who did well, keep up the good work. Those who did bad, continue being a deadweight." Ye Xiu said.

Everyone knew who he was pointing to. They laughed and then continued onwards. Mo Fan was in turmoil. Deception seemed to be swaying when he moved.

The team continued to clear monsters and clear bosses.

They advanced through the second boss and third boss. Every time they checked the DPS carts, Deception continued to falter.

Mo Fan was about to fall apart. He resisted asking about it because he knew that Ye Xiu was trying to make him realize something through these unsatisfactory results. If he asked, wouldn’t that mean he was doing what that guy wanted? Mo Fan endured and endured. He swore that he would find what the problem was on his own.

But as a result, he wasn’t able to focus. Ye Xiu’s instructions never included him. When the fourth boss fell, Mo Fan wasn’t careful and actually died.

In dungeons, deaths happened. The probability of equipment dropping was rather low. After all, dying was normal in a dungeon, so the penalty was much smaller to not excessively destroy a player’s morale.

Today just wasn’t Mo Fan’s day though. When he died, he actually dropped a piece of equipment.

But at this moment, how could Mo Fan be hurt over a piece of equipment? His character was kicked from the dungeon. Mo Fan continued to be in a daze.

Everyone continued to quietly take care of the fourth boss. No one said anything. Console him? It wasn’t worth wasting their breath!

The loss of Deception didn’t affect the battle much. The fourth boss soon fell and another First Kill record was announced.

"Continue." Mo Fan’s Deception wasn’t there. As expected, Ye XIu didn’t bring up the DPS chart and the team advanced.

Deception was still standing outside of the dungeon in a daze. Mo Fan was also staring blankly from his seat.

Why?

Mo Fan wasn’t thinking about why he died. Because he knew that it was his mistake. If he hadn’t been careless, he wouldn’t have died there.

He was still thinking about his DPS.

Although he couldn’t see the fourth boss statistics, he didn’t think there’d be much of a difference compared to before.

Because he couldn’t find a breakthrough direction, he felt like he had hit a wall. However, was the reason why the others were outdamaging him because they were that much better than him?

Mo Fan looked around.　　

With a cigarette in his mouth and smoke obscuring his face, Ye Xiu.

With a look of hatred on his face and the occasional cursing, Wei Chen.

With his brows raised and his eyes laughing, and who knew what he was so happy about, Steamed Bun.

Mo Fan couldn’t keep looking around. Why was his DPS lower than theirs! Why?

Mo Fan needed a logical explanation. He knew that Ye Xiu definitely knew the reason, but compared to asking him, Mo Fan would rather spend ten times the effort to look for the issue.

Everyone continued to dungeon. Mo Fan started looking through today’s DPS charts. He was going to thoroughly study them.

Starting from Sealed Mountain Thief Hideout to Gray Corner’s Underground Market, the DPS charts hadn’t change much. The high-performing ones were just those and the bottom feeders had always been the three of them.

Mo Fan checked each and every boss, but couldn’t find any clues.

There was also the five player dungeon. Mo Fan checked those. Even though he also lost to Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle, the difference wasn’t that big. That Wu Chen really was quite good too. Just by looking at his good sitting posture and calm face, he seemed a lot more like an expert compared to those other guys.

As he looked through the statistics for the five-player dungeon and the ten-player dungeons, Mo Fan suddenly noticed a difference.

He didn’t look at their rankings, but rather the damage.

From the five-player dungeon to the ten-player dungeon, his DPS had dropped. That was normal. Ten-player dungeons were much harder than five-player dungeons.

But the others? In the ten-player dungeons, not only did their DPS not fall, their DPS had actually gone up.

Was that the reason? Just how were they playing?

Chapter 876: Problem Found

Having noticed the contrast, Mo Fan began to consider what had been different between small dungeons and team dungeons.

His own technique, his own skill was still the same. As for the others? How would he know?! Mo Fan was frustrated. The arrangement of Happy’s training room was the same after moving into the apartment from the internet cafe. Three computers in a row, four sides, forming a square.

The others craned their necks around, all having a friend beside them whose screen they could look at. Only Mo Fan sat in a row of his own. If he wanted to check on another’s performance, he would have to get up and walk around. Mo Fan couldn’t help but long for Su Mucheng’s presence. When Su Mucheng was around, she had always sat in the same row as him...

The upset Mo Fan considered getting up to take a look at someone else’s progress, as Ye Xiu’s voice flooded his ears. He was now hearing it from outside, instead of within the game. However, he generally filtered out these noises. Ye Xiu’s arrangements rarely mentioned him, too.

Hearing his guy’s annoying voice made his frustration build. As he was bothered by the voice, Mo Fan suddenly realized something. He remembered that this guy’s annoying voice had rarely made an appearance during their five-player dungeon run!

Carefully recalling that process, Mo Fan became certain. When they ran five-player dungeons, apart from the cautious orders of "go", "stop", or "heal", there was none of the endless chatter about what tactics they should use.

Was it because he had been so distracted by that hateful voice that he didn’t do as well in team dungeons as he did in small dungeons?

This was an involuntary thought that popped into mind, but he quickly knew that it wasn’t possible. The DPS of small and team dungeons were something he could easily check. What caused him to lag behind wasn’t because he wasn’t performing as well in team dungeons, but because when the others went into team dungeons, they seemed completely unaffected by the change in difficulty, able to perform to their fullest despite it.

Could it be… that it was because of that guy’s leadership?

Mo Fan spaced out a little. If that was true, then he had to admit that it was a logical reason. After all, in the team dungeons, everyone moved in accordance with Ye Xiu’s arrangements, even performing specific skills that he would name. Only his Deception was completely independent, fighting however he wanted.

He had been very proud about that, feeling like such a rebel, unmoved by Ye Xiu.

Now, it seemed that the very thing he was proud of was actually the perpetrator of his awkward DPS.

Mo Fan refused to believe this. He couldn’t care about it anymore and stood, running over to watch someone else. As he watched, he imagined his own character in their character’s place: if it was Deception, what would he do in this situation?

The contrast was stunning.　Mo Fan was watching Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, a melee character, just like Deception. His usual silence was almost broken as he watched, almost unable to stifle the words "How did you do that; this is what you should do" and other such phrases. However, after a few exchanges, Mo Fan realized that these seemingly silly decisions were giving a huge boost to Tang Rou’s DPS. By now, Mo Fan had also found the reason, teamwork!

For example, in the wave of attacks just now, Tang Rou had chained it with Steamed Bun Invasion’s Strangle. As soon as Steamed Bun Invasion landed a Strangle, Soft Mist immediately sent forth a wave of high-damage attacks at the boss, which only ended when the effect of Strangle ended. It wasn’t just Soft Mist, but all the other characters with physical skills seemed to have been waiting for this moment and unleashed their skills without restraint in these few short seconds.

Under the effects of Strangle, the target’s physical defense would be reduced by 50 percent. That meant all damage received from physical attacks would experience an immense increase. In these few seconds, Mo Fan watched Soft Mist’s DPS skyrocket with awe.

He finally understood!

Mo Fan returned to his own seat. He felt like he understood the source of the problem now. So, it had been because of their careful teamwork that the others retained high DPS even in team dungeons. Mo Fan naturally recognized skills like Strangle and he knew how much more damage he could deal if he used this chance to land a blow. As for the others? They seemed to be waiting for a skill like Strangle, holding onto their skills. As soon as Strangle hit, they didn’t just land a single blow and retreat.

He should have paid more attention to coordination.

Mo Fan’s spirits rose, feeling that he found the main source of his problems. He eagerly wanted to charge in and show everyone how well he could coordinate with them.

Wasn’t it just paying attention to these opportunities? Grabbing opportunities was his forte! As a scrap-picker, Mo Fan had confidence in this area. However, he obviously couldn’t squeeze into the current dungeon. Mo Fan found a place to fight monsters by himself, but his mind was full of that refined and opportunistic battle style.

On Ye Xiu’s side, things were smooth sailing even though they were short one man. However, one less person was still one less person, and even a leecher would still contribute to the DPS. They were, admittedly, slower.

The Fourth boss was successfully dealt with, and then after a series of mobs, they finally arrived at the last boss of the Underground Market.

Utilizing the same strategy, they finally cleared the Underground Market in three hours.

By then, it was already eight or so in the morning, and the sun had long since risen. Yet everyone was still full of energy, even those who weren’t used to staying up late like Chen Guo.

It had once again come to the time for them to collect their rewards, and everyone was eager. On the other hand, Mo Fan had already let Deception head off to the next ten player dungeon. He had to win back his face her. Mo Fan was completely uninterested in the chattering over their rewards.

"Ah!"

"Ah!"

"Yah!"　

Chen Guo’s unnecessary enthusiasm caused Mo Fan to roll his eyes more than once.

The First Kill rewards for the individual bosses gave out equipment worthy of bosses, and the first boss gave out a level 75 Orange accessory.

The second and third bosses all gave out materials, totalling at six; the boss to material ratio was the same as Sealed Mountain Thieves Hideout.　The rewards for the fourth and fifth boss were both Oranges equipment. The fourth was obviously for the Thief class and wasn’t much use to Team Happy. The fifth boss gave out something that was most suited to Elementalists, but it would also give a boost to other magic based fighters. Equipment that could be helpful across multiple classes weren’t rare in Glory either.　

Finally, the time came to collect the First Clear reward for the entire dungeon.

"Weapon! Weapon! Weapon!!" Chen Guo wished aloud. There hadn’t even been a single weapon among their First Kill rewards for the five bosses.

Ye Xiu was far calmer than Chen Guo. Underground Market’s First Clear reward, collected!

Fire Red BaronThe name of the Orange equipment came into view, but they couldn’t tell what it was. Then came Chen Guo’s excited screaming and everyone immediately knew it was a weapon.

Fire Red Baron, Level 75 Orange Handcannon.

Weight 3.9kg, Durability 39, Attack Speed 1;

Physical Attack 895;

Magic Attack 651;　

Strength +58;

Physical Crit Rate +10;

Fire Element Damage +10%;

Fire Element Damage Crit Rate +15;

Fire Element Crit Damage +20%;

When attacks land, there’s a 4% chance of triggering a Firestorm.

The basic stats were, doubtlessly, at the level of a level 75 Orange weapon, and following that was a heap of boosters for Fire Element attacks, fulling portraying its status as the First Clear reward of a team dungeon. This Fire Red Baron was similar to the Tiger Seal Luo Ji’s Concealed Light had in one aspect, and that was its ability to change one’s skill tree build. With such obvious favoritism for the element of Fire, the gunner holding this would have made a mistake in choosing it if they hadn’t favored skills with an addition of Fire Elemental damage.

Chen Guo herself was a Launcher, so she understood the value of this reward . However, she didn’t have any intention to take the weapon for herself. She was happy because they had an expert Launcher on their team right now, Wu Chen, whose DPS was even better than Tang Rou.

Limited by his natural potential and age, Wu Chen’s skill probably wouldn’t see any more miraculous improvements. However, in the current Team Happy, he was an invaluable veteran. In addition, his character's strength gave a boost to Happy’s chances in taking the Challenger’s League.　There was no debate about it; Fire Red Baron went to Wu Chen’s Dawn Rifle. Then, the other piece of Orange equipment, False General, was a cloth armor particularly suited to Ghostblades. There was no arguments as to who that went to.　Apart from these two pieces of Orange equipment, there were some materials that they stored away from now.

"There’s one last ten player dungeon; let’s get this all done in one night!" Chen Guo who was usually against these sorts of unhealthy habits didn’t even mention breakfast, encouraging everyone to continue and clear the last of the ten player dungeons as well.

"Sure!" No one had any problems with that. They were all satisfied from the continuous First Kill rewards.

"Then let’s go!" Ye Xiu said, and everyone’s characters left through the teleportation portal in Guizhi City, heading for the last ten player dungeon, The Land of Despairing Spirits in the Forest of Shattered Skies.

Mo Fan’s Deception had long since been waiting for them, fearful that he would be forgotten. It was a good thing that Ye Xiu invited him as soon as they arrived. Mo Fan had never been so eager to enter a party before and Deception ran all the way to where Ye Xiu had told him to go, returning to their party.　　

"Do your best to DPS," Ye Xiu called out their slogan for dungeons.

"Humph!" Mo Fan uncharacteristically responded, surprising everyone. The all looked around to see what expression was on that guy’s face.

The ten entered the dungeon, familiarized themselves with the mobs, and began to progress. Yet at ten minutes past eight, the TV suddenly announced: Congratulations to Guild Tyrannical Ambition for the First Kill on The Land of Despairing Spirit’s Original Wraith.

"Ah! How could it be!" Chen Guo exclaimed. Someone actually managed to take the First Kill for a ten player dungeon before them. Chen Guo was shocked.

Ye Xiu clicked into the First Kill record and understood what had happened upon reading it. He sighed with helplessness, "Seems like the pro players are awake."

Chapter 877: 20 Player Dungeon, If You’re In, Press 1

Hearing this, everyone paused, shocked, and all clicked on the record. In the system announcements, if all the members of a party were from the same guild, then the system would announce their guild’s name. You could still view the individual participants if you clicked on it, though. The First Kill namelist of the first boss of the Land of Despairing Spirits, The Original Wraith was a sight to behold.

Desert Dust, Immovable Rock, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Dark Thunder...

This line-up you usually only ever saw in pro matches was now placed on this record ever so magnificently. Being able to set a record at such a time meant that the players behind the characters weren’t power levellers who were there just to get the characters to the new level limit, but the true owners: the four Gods that had teamed up in Tyranny this season.

The other six were all characters on Tyranny’s roster as well. Without a doubt, Tyranny’s pro players had just begun a new day of activities. The new update was something the pro players had come to take a look at too, so they would go and run a few dungeons on the way. To say they were aiming for First Clear or Kill rewards was to underestimate these powerhouse teams. Only a poor team like Happy would be aiming for these sorts of rewards. With the foundation that Tyranny had, there was more importance in the taking of the record itself. As for those rewards, they wouldn’t do anything to give them an advantage.　So the pro players of the big teams weren’t particularly anxious or impatient because of the new update. Everyone’s daily lives were still the same. Some of the clubs had even emphasized that they should make sure to keep good habits in order to maintain their state for future matches and not to get too involved in the online game...

This emphasis was very much necessary. Pro players were all obsessed with Glory. Asking them to resist the temptations of a new update was an impossible request. Though the clubs may have made such a request, there might still be pro players who stayed up at night, playing on an alt.

However, it was now past eight in the morning, those who had a healthy sleep schedule were due to get up, so these guys could charge into the online game for some action. They might’ve said it was to familiarize themselves with the new mechanics, but in reality, which one of them wasn’t interested in the new update?

When the First Kill for the Land of Despairing Spirit’s first Boss was announced, the normal players were a little numb to it. These guys had stayed up for the release, just like Ye Xiu and co, so they were used to the First Kill announcements popping up again and again throughout the night. They all needed a moment to compose themselves, but that was when they suddenly realized that this time, it wasn’t Happy that had gotten the First Kill this time!

Tyrannical Ambition!

Then, they clicked into the record and were immediately blinded by the eye-catching names.

The chat for higher ups in each club’s guild department also exploded with activity. To them, the new update was the arrival of a very important job. All-nighters were common on days like this. In the past, competing for First Kills and First Clears were a vital part of their job. Now it was a little different. A nightmare like Ye Qiu had darted into the game, bringing with him a team of his own. While the big guilds ran around the dungeons to get a feel for it, they were accumulating First Kills and First Clears like they were going out of style. In one night, the First Clears of four dungeons had been taken.

The guild leaders were going crazy, helpless and wishing for dawn to come soon! They knew, of course, that after the sun had come up, the pro players of each team would come into the game to familiarize themselves with the new updates. Although First Clears and First Kills weren’t a part of a pro player’s job, they could grab a few along the way!

The number of members on each of the big teams was around ten or so, so ten-player team dungeons were the natural choice. There were only three ten-player dungeons released in the new update and two had already been cleared by Guild Happy already. The guilds of the big teams would, of course, make sure to remind the pro players to go for the dungeon without First Kills or Clears as they prepared to log into the game and try out the new updates.

It was Team Tyranny who had gotten the opportunity.　

The current pro player characters that were in the game weren’t equipped with their usual set of Silver equipment. In terms of the strength of characters, they were about the same as Happy’s all orange characters. However, their skill, tactics, and coordination were far beyond what Happy currently possessed.

For Ye Xiu and co, running a ten-player dungeon took about three hours. However, Tyranny’s members had gotten to and dealt with a boss within twenty minutes. When they explored new dungeons, they didn’t need to be as cautious as Ye Xiu’s party, where unfamiliar mobs and bosses needed Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim to go up and figure them out first. They all just went all in for it because they were confident that no matter what happened, they would be able to deal with it. There was little need to emphasize how Tyranny also had the best Cleric in all of Glory...

So, seeing that Tyrannical Ambition had gotten the First Kill for the first Boss, Ye Xiu knew that they had no chance of getting the First Kills and First Clear for this ten-player dungeon.

"Should we continue?" It evidently wasn’t just Ye Xiu who knew. Seeing that Ye Xiu hadn’t said anything for a long while, Chen Guo spoke up.　"No need," Ye Xiu sighed. They weren’t as casual as the powerhouse teams. They weren’t here for anything but the First Kill reward, so there was no need to stay in this dungeon that they couldn’t obtain a First Kill from.

"Should we leave?" Chen Guo asked.

"Let’s leave!" Ye xiu said.

If they weren’t aiming for the First Kill rewards, then a ten-player dungeon that took three hours wasn’t worth their time.

Getting out of The Land of Despairing Spirits, the energetic group had all become a little downtrodden, Mo Fan included. He didn’t really care about First Kill rewards. He was going to use this dungeon to win back some face. Now that they weren’t going to run the dungeon any longer, Mo Fan felt like he had energy that he didn’t know how to spend, becoming extremely gloomy.

"Maybe we can run a few smaller dungeons?" Chen Guo suggested. Five-player small dungeons didn’t have many rewards, but it was better than nothing.

"There will probably we pro players running the small dungeons, too," Ye Xiu said as he opened up QQ and yelled into the chat, "Who’s here?"

Whoooooosh….

A bunch of people popped up, all greeting him as "god" or "senior". Ye Xiu made a rough guess that there were about thirty or fourty people who appeared immediately. When had this chat ever been so active? It was obvious that they had all begun their online activities already. As for what they were doing, did it even need to be mentioned? If it was usual training, they wouldn’t be allowed to be messing around on QQ. They were all enjoying the new update!

"Sup?" Troubling Rain asked. It was evident that they were in a dungeons; even Huang Shaotian only had the time to type three letters and a question mark.

"Have you all eaten yet?" Ye Xiu asked.

"F*ck off f*ck off f*ck off!" Though he might’ve been rather busy, Huang Shaotian still typed a whole six words.

"What dungeon are you running?" Ye Xiu asked directly.

"The Land of Despairing Spirits," Huang Shaotian replied.

"Pathetic! The First Kill has already been taken by Tyranny," Ye Xiu said.

"Are you trying to provoke me?" Huang Shaotian accused him in a rage.

"Funny isn’t it, like you guys aren’t rivals. What’s there to provoke?" Ye Xiu asked.

"........" When Huang Shaotian was speechless, he had to use more ellipses as well.

"What dungeon is everyone else running?" Ye Xiu chose to speak to the group at large this time.

All sorts of word filled the screen, the names of all sorts of dungeons. With a glance, Ye Xiu saw what he had expected; plenty of small dungeons had been taken already. A single team could run two five-player dungeons at once! But the majority of them were at The Land of Despairing Spirits. It seemed that many had gotten requests from their guilds to grab some First Kills from their guilds.

"You want to avoid taken dungeons so you can continue to grab First Kills?" Vaccaria popped up; Wang Jiexi had guessed Ye Xiu’s intentions.

"I have far more First Kills than all of you, ok?" Ye Xiu replied.

Everyone was silent; wasn’t this because you shamelessly spent the entire night online?

"Anyone who wants to do a 20 player dungeon, press 1!!!" Ye Xiu began to yell.　Blood coughing and sweat dropping emojis came like a flood. This suggestion was just too much.

There were also some who couldn’t help but jump out. They were obviously people who viewed Ye Xiu as an opponent.

One Autumn Leaf: "F*ck, what the hell do you mean by that!"

"..." Ye Xiu replied.

Everyone was dumbstruck. Had such a simple sentence made Ye Qiu incapable of retort? That was so strange, but soon enough they knew it wasn’t the case.

Ye Xiu said, "Sh*t, I really can’t get used to this name speaking to me."

Everyone burst out with laughter.

Everyone knew who was using One Autumn Leaf’s name; it was Excellent Era’s Sun Xiang! This guy was, indeed, a prodigy. That was something everyone had to admit to, but this guy was too arrogant and looked down on everyone. He might have the skill, but his reputation wasn’t very good. Not many pro players liked him.

Sun Xiang was frustrated as well, but his usually dexterous hands seemed to have frozen, unable to type anything in reply. He could only watch as Ye Xiu’s newly named "Lord Grim" continued: "How come Excellent Era’s people are still in here? Shouldn’t relegated people get kicked out? Wasn’t that a rule here?"

"There’s no rule like that!" Sun Xiang raged, looking through the chat rules. Who would believe that such a harsh rule actually existed?!

It wasn’t only Sun Xiang that went to flip through the rules, the spectators did as well. In the end, wow, there really was a rule like that.

Sun Xiang didn’t know how to respond at first, but he wasn’t that slow. After a moment, everyone realized what had just occurred.

"F*ck, you just added that, didn’t you?!" Sun Xiang yelled. Ye Xiu was a veteran among veterans, and that meant that he had been one of the first members of this chat, holding the position of an admin. The pro players were laughing like crazy by the time Sun Xiang had yelled.

"Yup!" Ye Xiu admitted bluntly.

Sun Xiang’s hands froze again, unsure of what he should type next.

"So, if you keep spewing bullsh*t, I’ll kick you!" Ye Xiu threatened and then turned to yell once more, "Anyone up for a 20-player dungeon? Press 1!!!!!!"

Chapter 878: 20 Player Dungeon, Start

1.

After Ye Xiu asked the chat, there was someone who actually pressed 1. Most of the players in the chat were just here to watch. When they saw someone actually raise his hand, of course they would be delighted, but the person who pressed 1 was too much of a heavyweight! Many of the players were dumbstruck. If these Gods allied together to run a dungeon... what type of scene would that be?　

"Just you or your entire team?" Ye Xiu replied calmly.

"Entire team." The other side replied.

"Perfect. Each side has ten players." Ye Xiu said.

"Which dungeon do you want to run?" The other side asked.

"Barrier Mountains!" Ye Xiu said.

"Rebel Army Vanguard Camp?" The other side asked.

"I think that’s the one." Ye Xiu replied.

"Contact me in game."

"Okay."

After finishing the conversation, the two left at once. The remaining players were left stunned, admiring the chat log between the two Gods.

Ye Qiu. Wang Jiexi.

Lord Grim. Vaccaria.

Clearing dungeons wasn’t anything amazing. Right now, all of the pro players were running dungeons. It was just that these two Gods combining forces to run a dungeon was too crazy.

"Twenty-player dungeon! Set out!" After Ye Xiu finished his business in the group chat, he immediately called out to his teammates.　　

"Twenty players? We don’t have enough people." Wei Chen asked dubiously.

"We’re going to run it together with Team Tiny Herb to get a twenty player team." Ye Xiu said.

Bang!

Who knew what made that sound. In any case, someone lost had his cool. Everyone traced the sound back to its source, which turned out to be Qiao Yifan, who was always cautious and never overstepped the boundaries.

It had been half a year since Qiao Yifan had left Tiny Herb. Qiao Yifan had only spent a year together with Tiny Herb. However, his days there couldn’t be forgotten so easily. His excitement when he was chosen by the team to admiring his seniors when he first joined to his friendship with Gao Yingjie to having no opportunities to perform to his doubt towards himself... Qiao Yifan’s invisibility in Tiny Herb wasn’t false. Perhaps others might not remember what he had done in Tiny Herb during that year, but for him, many things had happened.

He had left Tiny Herb, or to be more accurate, Tiny Herb had given up on him. Qiao Yifan didn’t blame Team Tiny Herb though. Everyone in Team Tiny Herb had been more outstanding than he had been. That was just the reality of things. However, he still hoped to one day improve enough and stand on stage against Tiny Herb, letting them see how far he had come. He couldn’t help but occasionally dream of this scene.

He had never imagined that his first encounter with Tiny Herb would be in a dungeon team inside the game. In front of Ye Xiu, it seemed like he always had to be prepared to face the unexpected!

Qiao Yifan felt a myriad of emotions because of a few personal matters, but for Wu Chen, suddenly pulling along Team Tiny Herb to play together for a twenty-player dungeon was simply too shocking. Wu Chen felt the same as many of the players in the pro player group chat. He felt like he was going crazy.

As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, their greenhorn minds stayed steady.

Mo Fan cared even less. He just felt pleased at having another chance to run a dungeon.

Normally, Chen Guo would be the most excited, but because Chen Guo was sitting next to Ye Xiu, she had seen Ye Xiu pulling up the QQ chat and advertising. Having seen everything from start to finish with her own eyes, her emotions were quite stable.

"We’ll restock and head out!" Ye Xiu instructed, "We’ll be running Barrier Mountain’s twenty-player dungeon."

Soon afterawrds, the two teams gathered together in front of the entrance to Barrier Mountain’s twenty-player dungeon, Rebel Army Vanguard Camp.　　

"Everyone’s here?" Ye Xiu saw Tiny Herb’s characters. None of them were unfamiliar. All of them were Team Tiny Herb’s brave heroes.

"We’re all here." On Team Tiny Herb’s side, Vaccaria stepped forward. Wang Jiexi talked to Ye Xiu, while measuring up Team Happy. He had seen some of their faces before, but there were a few unfamiliar faces too.　　

"Before we begin, how will we be splitting the rewards?" Ye Xiu said.

"According to each other’s needs!" Wang Jiexi said.

"By class?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Yes."

"What if there are conflicting classes?" Ye Xiu asked.　　

"Roll." Wang Jiexi said.

"Materials?"

"Fifty fifty."

"Alright, let’s do that then." Ye Xiu had no objections to the standard method of distribution, but the others behind them were still in admiration.

Look, that’s the aura of Gods. We haven’t even started yet and they’ve already finished discussing how to split the spoils.　

"How are we assigning roles?" Next, everyone in the team needed to have a specific role.

"We can take care of tanking!" Wang Jiexi said.　　

"Of course." Ye Xiu agreed.

Chen Guo had been calm the entire time, but if she could still hold her excitement, she wouldn’t be Chen Guo. A dungeon! And who would be their tank? Xu Bin! Who would be the tank character? Angelica!

Glory’s number one Knight! To think she would have the opportunity to run a dungeon with him as a tank, this this this... Chen Guo finally couldn’t keep her calm. Not crying out excitedly so the team wouldn’t lose face took great effort on her part.

"Healer?" This time, Wang Jiexi asked first. His character’s line of view couldn’t help but look towards Ye Xiu’s Little Cold Hands. Wang Jiexi was treating them like a pro team.

For a pro team, the tank wasn’t too important, but the healer role couldn’t be neglected. What type of person was the person who held such an important role in Ye Qiu’s team? Wang Jiexi wanted to know.

"Mm... I’ll have to trouble you guys with healing!" Ye Xiu said.

"What? Is there a problem with your side?" Wang Jiexi asked.

"There isn’t a problem, but in front of Team Tiny Herb’s great healer, being modest is a must!" Ye Xiu said.

"Cough..." An Wenyi couldn’t help but cough. Talking big didn’t need all the chatter! Just being compared to a champion team’s healer made An Wenyi feel ashamed.

Wang Jiexi chuckled. He could see the implications of those words. It probably wasn’t Happy being modest, but rather an issue with his skill level!

"Group up. Group up." Ye Xiu shouted and the twenty players joined together.

　

"You can be the leader." Wang Jiexi arranged directly.

"Sure!" Ye Xiu didn’t object, "Then let’s go?"

"Go!" Wang Jiexi ordered. Team Tiny Herb’s ten players immediately entered the dungeon. Happy’s side followed.

"Tank, pull monsters. Healers, watch our health. Everyone else, deal damage." Ye Xiu began instructing.

They were pioneering, after all. Apart from these words, there wasn’t much else a shot caller could say.

Glory’s number one Knight took up his shield and charged forward. The others readied their skills according to their class. Gao Yingjie’s Kind Tree rode his broom and nimbly flew over to Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash.

"Yifan?" Gao Yingjie’s greeting wasn’t very certain, even though he had heard the news long ago.

"Yeah….." Qiao Yifan felt a bit apologetic towards Gao Yingjie because he had left without a word. He had never told his best friend what his plans had been either.

"Hey, this kid’s got some manners. He took the initiative to say hi?" Steamed Bun Invasion passed by and immediately stopped to comment.

"Ah?" Gao Yingjie was at a loss.

"Not bad, not bad. I think well of you. You don’t need to be afraid of the ground! There’s me to protect you." Steamed Bun said.

"Oh..." Gao Yingjie replied in confusion. He immediately controlled Kind Heart to attack the monsters, not daring to delay. When this talent erupted, even Steamed Bun was a bit stunned.

"It seems like he’s better than even me?" Steamed Bun said to Qiao Yifan.

"Haha...." Qiao Yifan didn’t know what to say, but he was quite proud of his friend.

"Yes yes, it seems like it’ll be easy! Everyone go, everyone go! Wang Jiexi, don’t be a leecher. If you’re not the number one damage dealer here, you can’t come on the next raid." Ye Xiu observed the battlefield.

Team Tiny Herb was in uproar. Leecher? Can’t come? They never thought that there would be a day these words would be placed onto their team captain.

"Number one Knight, stabilize it! You’re not thinking of letting an OT happen, right!!" Ye Xiu instructed Xu Bin.

"Great healer! Don’t only heal your Tiny Herb friends. Our side has ten fresh health bars too!" After instructing the tank, Ye Xiu started chattering to the healer.

"That’s all you’ve got to say!" Team Tiny Herb’s healer, Yang Baiqing, was no stranger with Ye Xiu. After hearing his name mentioned, he couldn’t help but reply back.

"There’s just….. Nothing worth saying. If I don’t say something, won’t it seem like I’m doing nothing?" Ye Xiu said.

It was true. Against these small monsters, their skill level was more than enough, but Ye Xiu’s nitpicky shotcalling style was difficult to look at with straight eyes.

But in general, their dungeon progress went smoothly and harmoniously. Not just friends like Gao Yingjie and Qiao Yifan, but the others on the two sides started to talk with each other.

"Sister, how fierce!!" Team Tiny Herb’s Liu Xiaobie was a hand speed expert. Right now, he was surprised at Tang Rou’s ferociousness. It wasn’t Tiny Herb’s first encounter with Soft Mist. When the tenth server had just opened, Wang Jiexi had led Tiny Herb’s members to spar with Ye Xiu on multiple occasions. Their interactions with each other weren’t few. At that time, Soft Mist had just been some noob to be crushed by them, but after a year had passed, she had improved by leaps and bounds, making them feel a bit frightened.

"You’re very good too." Tang Rou politely replied back.

"How about we see who can kill more?" Liu Xiaobie said.

"Okay!" This suggestion was exactly what Tang Rou wanted, so she happily accepted.

Team Tiny Herb’s Xiao Yun was a Battle Mage player too. He was having fun in the dungeon. His thoughts were similar to normal players. He wanted to find a girl to get closer to. Soft Mist was a Battle Mage too, so she was his first choice. However, Liu Xiaobie took her away. He had no choice but to switch targets.

"Girl, your rhthym’s pretty good!" After moving closer to Little Cold Hands, Xiao Yun found an opportunity to chat.　

"I’m a guy." An Wenyi replied back adeptly.

F*ck….. Xiao Yun’s Battle Mage turned away and left.

Chapter 879: Teamwork

Team Tiny Herb did, in fact, have one female player called Liu Fei. However, since they were very much familiar with each other, Xiao Yun didn’t have any interest in chatting with her. Looking at Happy’s line-up, there was only one other female character: Chasing Haze.

Unfortunately, Xiao Yun’s character was a Battle Mage and Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze was a Launcher. As soon as the battle started, the two characters had been as far as can be from each other. Running over to Little Cold Hands had already been the limit to the amount of the monsters his character could reach. If he ran to where ranged attackers like Launchers were positioned, then he would really become a sightseer. Although familiarizing yourself with the new update didn’t require the serious and strict attitude that training did, even their Captain Wang Jiexi was doing his all to DPS, so Xiao Yun didn’t dare to let down his guard. In the end, he could only admire from afar and sigh. Running back into the mobs, he decided to still aim for Soft Mist and see if there was any chance.

When Tang Rou fought, she didn’t hold anything back at all, and Xiao Yun silently hid his shock. If he hadn’t already known that she was a girl, Xiao Yun would’ve thought she was a G.I.R.L.*.

Like the other members of Tiny Herb, he too was amazed by how much Soft Mist had improved after watching her fight. Now, if they were to PKed, they wouldn’t dare to be certain of their own victory.

"She’s improved so fast. Talented, as expected!" Wang Jiexi had hoped to recruit Tang Rou a long time ago, but had been rejected. Seeing her current skill, he couldn’t help but lament aloud.

"Isn’t she?" Ye Xiu replied with a smile after hearing his laments.

"Prodigious." Wang Jiexi agreed to that. Even among the pro players of Team Tiny Herb, Tang Rou’s valiance was very eye catching.

"What about the others? What do you think?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That Warlock and Launcher seem very familiar with their roles; they’re both veterans! I heard that the Warlock is the ex-Captain of Blue Rain?" Wang Jiexi asked.

"Yup."

"That Launcher called Dawn Rifle, how come it feels like I’ve seen him on the field before?" Wang Jiexi asked.

"He used to be part of Everlasting," Ye Xiu said.

"The ex pro team you eliminated from the Challenger League?" Wang Jiexi said.

"You read the papers?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Qiao Yifan has become very accustomed to the Phantom Demon class as well." Wang Jiexi commented.

"This might just be the class that suits him the most." Ye Xiu said.

"Maybe!" Wang Jiexi replied.

Apart from the few just mentioned, there was also Steamed Bun Invasion, Concealed Light, Deception, Little Cold Hands, and Chasing Haze that Wang Jiexi hadn’t commented on, still observing them.

In reality, Ye Xiu knew that this guy wasn’t truly here to clear the dungeon, but was mostly here to see how Happy was doing. Although most people would be certain that this seasons Challenger League was no more than Excellent Era’s Revival Tournament, Wang Jiexi had never blindly gone with the masses, just like the Magician style he had once used. Though he might’ve changed his style to cooperate with the team, his personality wouldn’t change.

It was very much Wang Jiexi’s style to look to the underdog when everyone else was certain of Excellent Era’s victory.

Ye Xiu, of course, knew that he was here to observe and Wang Jiexi could clearly see that, so, he didn’t bother to hide it. When Ye Xiu asked, he would answer. The aforementioned four’s skill was rather eye catching, and no one would be surprised if they were a part of the Pro League.

As for the others...

Wang Jiexi continued to observe as he fought and, by the time he opened his mouth to comment again, he looked around only to see that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had charged off to fight and was no longer standing beside him.

Soon enough, the team arrived at the first boss of the Rebel Army’s Vanguard Camp. Sharp Blades Captain Leo. The mobs they had cleared on the way were all members of the Sharp Blades.　"Tank, pull the boss. Healers, watch our health. Everyone else, prepare to deal damage," Ye Xiu said.

With a new section, that was all he had to say as a command. Yet, those who were listening could tell that "everyone else, deal damage" had become "everyone else, prepare to deal damage". With the addition of two words, the entire meaning had changed. So, when Xu Bin’s Angelica charged up, everyone stayed where they were, instead of charging with him.

However, they were all experts. They might have been facing a boss, but no one was nervous, casually chatting with one another as they waited. For a moment, Sharp Blades Captain Leo was being taken care of by Tiny Herb’s Knight and the two healers. After a few minutes of fighting and still no orders from Ye Xiu, everyone was wondering that this should’ve been enough to figure out the boss, right? Cleric Yuan Baiqing couldn’t help but yell, "We should be able to start now, right?"

Yet it wasn’t Ye Xiu who replied, but Chen Guo’s awkward voice, "He went to the bathroom…"　"F*ck!" Yuan Baiqing’s voice was angered, but by then Ye Xiu had come back, immediately replying, "So, how is it?"

"Can we start already?!" Yuan Bai yelled.

"Does anyone else need to use the restroom?" Ye Xiu asked.

"....."

"What the f*ck, man!" Yuan Baiqing raged.

"F*cking hell, are you planning to give up on me?!" Xu Bin said with horror, thinking, if you’re angry, don’t take it out on me! I’ve been giving it my all, too!

"If no one needs to go, then let’s begin," Ye Xiu said.

"Have you figured out the boss?" Yuan Baiqing asked.

"Of course, I went to the bathroom only after I had the boss figured out," Ye Xiu said.

"..." Yuan Baiqing had no idea how to retort. That guy managed to do what he needed and still had time to go to the bathroom.

"Go on, go on, I don’t think I need to tell you guys how to fight this boss; there’s nothing surprising about him." Ye Xiu said.

This was something that everyone who had been observing the boss agreed with, so none of them said anything more, all swarming forth to DPS.

"Melee players, be careful of your positioning! Make sure to give the others and the ranged characters space to attack!" This was something Ye Xiu had to mention. Pro players were very much used to running in five man teams when cooperating with other players. Now, with 20 people together, and attacking the same target, too, they weren’t very used to the positioning and made it harder for many to attack at a time. This was something vital to hundred man dungeons. The reason for hundred man dungeons being the limit despite the amount of players in Glory, was because Glory didn’t let two players stand in the same space. If they didn’t watch rhythm and spacing with one hundred people fighting as one against a single target, it could easily become a situation where some attacked and most would just watch, only joining in when those in the front had died, causing the team to wipe.

So, the reason for larger team dungeons being harder was partially due to this. The more people there were, the harder it was for an individual to perform at their best, causing their overall strength to fall collective and making it harder to clear the dungeon.

In a ten-player dungeon, with both ranged and melee cooperating, this problem wasn’t as evident, but in a 20 person dungeon it was slightly more apparent. Especially in their team, where there were less healers and more DPSers.

Yet this team was also filled with experts and were able to deal with it much better than normal players. As soon as Ye Xiu spoke, everyone began to pay more attention. Without Ye Xiu having to arrange anything, the members of Team Tiny Herb became a cooperating fighting system.

At times like this, the difference between Happy and Tiny Herb was obvious. Happy wasn’t very good at this sort of thing. Especially since Tiny Herb had taken up half the space, leaving them with the rest, their synchronization was messy. Ye Xiu finally had to start speaking up more with his commands, mostly focusing on Happy’s side. He didn’t need to worry about Team Tiny Herb’s positioning.

Under these circumstances, Deception became the obvious odd one out.　Mo Fan had no idea what teamwork was. Whatever actions that looked like teamwork was really just Deception charging up to land a few hits after finding an opening, but the current situation wasn’t one where he could just charge up upon finding an opening. Many openings were purposefully created for specific uses, but Mo Fan didn’t understand this and Ye Xiu didn’t give him any orders either, so this guy seemed like he was just causing trouble on purpose and soon caused rage to spread.

The members of Team Tiny Herb didn’t express their rage at first, hoping that command would correct him, but Ye Xiu continued to lead the other members of Happy as a successful team, seeming to have completely forgotten Deception existed, completely ignoring him.

Then, when Mo Fan ran to steal another opening, messing up the system Team Tiny Herb had been using, the members of the champion team couldn’t take it anymore.

"Hey you! What the hell are you doing?!" Tiny Herb’s Berserker, Liang Fang, was a guy with a rather short fuse. Having his pace broken by Deception over and over again, he was the first to erupt.

"That’s right, why do you keep snatching our openings?" Xiao Yun asked. Melee classes like them were a lot more affected by Deception’s running around.

"My angle of attack sometimes even gets blocked," Sharpshooter Li Ji complained. Deception’s influence was very widespread indeed. This was only on Tiny Herb, too; Happy hadn’t even said anything! Mo Fan’s snatching of openings was indiscriminate; it didn’t matter if it was Happy’s or Tiny Herb’s!

"Leader, aren’t you forgetting someone?" Cleric Yuan Baiqing also spoke up. Though he might not be affected by what Deception was doing, it had messed up their rhythm and synchronization. A highly skilled healer would synchronize with the rhythm the team was battling at, like the accompaniment to a symphony. With the pace of the team in chaos, his methods would lose their meaning and he would become especially harried.

The continuous accusations made Mo Fan unsure of what to do. Was his method incorrect?

Chapter 880: Slowly

Even the usually indifferent Mo Fan couldn’t ignore all of the criticism coming his way. He stopped playing and Deception stood off to the side foolishly.

When he fought, all he did was make things worse. Not fighting was easier to accept than fighting. Team Tiny Herb had no objections. Their team immediately started operating perfectly again.

On Happy’s side, without Mo Fan causing trouble, although their coordination wasn’t as practiced as Team Tiny Herb’s, under Ye Xiu’s continuous instructions, their teamwork wasn’t bad either. After all, they were only fighting a dungeon boss. There weren’t too many variations to the battle. Team Happy wasn’t lacking in individual skill. It was only the coordination between them that needed more practice.

Because they needed to keep up their level of coordination, none of them had the spare time to see the expression on Mo Fan’s face, the person who had incited Tiny Herb to complain. They could only see that Deception was sitting on the side and staring into space with no idea what to do. For a person like Chen Guo with a sharp mouth but a soft heart, she felt sympathy for him long ago.

But she also knew that this probably wasn’t outside of Ye Xiu’s expectations. Ignoring Mo Fan when giving out instructions was definitely intentional. If not, with Mo Fan’s skill, if Ye Xiu was willing to bring him into the group and Mo Fan listened to the orders, there shouldn’t have been any problems. The problem was that Ye Xiu had no such intention. Mo Fan didn’t even have an opportunity to refuse in spite.

Now Mo Fan was just standing awkwardly to the side. Through his view of the battle, he realized where the issue lay.

When the two teams operated, opportunities to attack would often be left behind. However, these opportunities were intentionally given to others, but not to him.

The movements and attacks of both teams covered for each other, linking and flowing smoothly together. Everyone had something to do. No one was idle, especially on Team Tiny Herb’s side. The synergy between each member of the team was more perfect. Their coordination appeared relaxed, natural, and unforced. His previous "seize opportunities to attack" strategy completely disrupted their flow. If the other side appeared as one person, his interjection was equivalent to putting a malignant tumor in that person.

Yes, a team’s cancerous tumor…...

Mo Fan didn’t know where he had heard this term from, but he realized that he seemed to be one. He was one on Tiny Herb’s side. It was the same for Happy.

In the previous ten-player dungeons, he couldn’t output a noteworthy amount of damage.

In this twenty-player dungeon, he had directly been given the cold shoulder with no way to deal damage.

Mo Fan understood there was a relationship between these two outcomes. He could still fight in the ten player dungeon because there was a lot more room to move and attack. There were plenty of openings. but for this twenty player dungeon, against a boss and the team’s high-level coordination, the window for an opening was much more tight. To find an opening, there was only one method. Integrate into the team. If he didn’t, it would only be like before. As soon as he made a move, he would be yelled at. That wasn’t integrating, but using a knife and dissecting the team.

Then, how should I go about doing that?

Mo Fan didn’t plan on standing by idly and watching. He needed to find a way.

He knew that Ye Xiu definitely had a way of integrating him into the team, but Mo Fan would rather die than speak up and ask for help. Mo Fan was determined to rely on on himself. He carefully observed the teamwork on both sides and pondered over how he should be a part of it. He needed to seize an opening without hindering others.

The battle continued.

Because the teamwork on both sides was well-practiced, everyone knew what to do, so there wasn’t much need for any instructions unless a big mistake happened.

But Ye Xiu kept on ordering about, commanding the players on Happy to do this and that.

Was there really a need? Many didn’t think so. Against monsters, the shotcalling had been beyond simple. It was practically everyone doing their own things. Facing this boss, the command became extremely detailed. They thought Ye Qiu was just making a big fuss over nothing.　　

But Tiny Herb’s captain, Wang Jiexi, didn’t think so. He listened very carefully to Ye Qiu’s orders. From time to time, he would look over to see how Happy was operating.

He’s giving that Ninja openings! Wang Jiexi saw through it.

The previous Team Happy members that he mentioned before had all managed to catch his eye in some way or another. In comparison, Little Cold Hands, Concealed Light, and Chasing Haze were somewhat inferior. Apart from them, there was Steamed Bun Invasion and Deception. Wang Jiexi couldn’t get a good read on them, so he didn’t make any comments on them for now.

But from their technical skill, there was no need to question their skill. However, when evaluating a pro player, technical skill alone wasn’t everything.

This Steamed Bun Invasion sometimes made some strange and incomprehensible decisions. Even Wang Jiexi couldn’t make heads or tails out of it because he couldn’t see the intentions behind these decisions. It just looked like he was playing mindlessly.

As for Deception, Wang Jiexi had previously observed that while he was very determined, it just felt like he wasn’t compatible. When they began fighting the boss and he kept jumping in and disrupting the coordination of both sides, Wang Jiexi finally understood. His technical skill was at a pro level, but his team awareness was practically zero. This guy should be receiving more instructions from the leader, but Ye Qiu didn’t say a word.

In the beginning, Wang Jiexi couldn’t make any sense of the matter, but after noticing Ye Qiu’s commands, he understood that he was secretly urging the ninja to understood the importance of teamwork.

However, would that guy be able to understand it?

Wang Jiexi turned Vaccaria’s line of sight towards Deception. In-game characters were expressionless, so Wang Jiexi couldn’t penetrate into his mind. However, Wang Jiexi could clearly see the openings left by Ye Xiu’s side, but time and time again, Deception stood there, wasting these openings. Wang Jiexi even felt somewhat angry. He wanted to tell that piece of wood how to integrate himself into the team.

Besides Wang Jiexi, no one else realized this point. Everyone was doing their own part and had begun ignoring the previously annoying Deception. Wang Jiexi waited and waited. He was starting to feel numb. He was only feeling numb though. He reckoned that Ye Qiu was probably feeling extremely impatient, upon seeing Deception not realize it. From his commanding, it didn’t sound like he was irritated though.

Wang Jiexi was just thinking about all of this, when Team Happy exposed another unnecessary opening. This opening could be taken easily, allowing the player to integrate into the team. At this moment, Deception, who had been staring blankly for a long time, finally moved. A shadow flickered. Wang Jiexi was alerted. He turned Vaccaria’s line of sight to see where Deception would go.

Sure enough, he’s going there!

Wang Jiexi saw where Team Happy’s opening lay, as well as Deception’s movement direction. It was precisely this spot.

Rush in and attack…...

So he’s finally starting to understand.

As the team captain, Wang Jiexi was very meticulous towards these sorts of things. It was as if he were a coach. As soon as he saw Deception finally catch an opening, it was like a game of Tetris, when you stacked the tetrominoes high up and then cleared away four lines at once with an "I" block. But before he could finish feeling that bliss, he saw Deception pull away and let that opening flash by.

"What’s he doing?" Wang Jiexi was shocked. Soon afterwards, he understood why.

Wang Jiexi didn’t know whether to laugh or cry at the reality of things. Deception was too inexperienced. He rushed in and attacked once. He didn’t know how to take advantage of this opportunity to integrate into the flow and had no idea what to do afterwards. As a result, he decided to withdraw to avoid being a malignant tumor.

"My condolences!" Wang Jiexi sent Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim a message revealing his sympathy.

"Same to you." Ye Xiu replied. He knew what Wang Jiexi was pointing at, but in terms of guiding a new player, Wang Jiexi had gone to even greater lengths for Gao Yingjie.

Wang Jiexi sighed. He continued to watch Ye Xiu patiently help Deception using this method, but after this Deception took his first step, he once again started worrying people again. This guy was good at finding opportunities. He caught all of the openings that Ye Xiu left for him, but the problem was that he always only hit once and then retreated, waiting in satisfaction for the next one to come. It didn’t seem like he was aware that he had already opened the door, but instead of going through it, he seemed to want to play around by jumping in and out. No wonder it had to be so troublesome. What a stubborn guy! These were only Wang Jiexi’s thoughts. He didn’t know too many details about the relationship between Mo Fan and Ye Xiu.

Even after the first boss fell, Deception failed to completely make it through the door.

First Kill announcement.

Because the two guilds had joined together, the announcement did not mention the guild names, but the team members involved were still listed.

The uproar triggered by this announcement was far different from before.

The pro players were fine. Those in the chat group knew that Wang Jiexi and Ye Xiu had joined hands to run a twenty player dungeon. The normal players, on the other hand, saw the resplendent character names of Team Tiny Herb, as well as those half-praised half-hated guys of Team Happy.　

What’s going on? How did those guys from Team Happy ally with Team Tiny Herb and run a dungeon together?

The normal players just couldn’t understand. In the dungeon, the Tiny Herb players were going crazy. Wang Jiexi spoke to Ye Xiu in a serious tone: "This is no good. No good at all."

"I think it’s quite reasonable!" Ye Xiu said.　　

"Reasonable is no good!" Wang Jiexi seemed to be unable to find a reason to dispute Ye Xiu’s words. In the end, he vehemently objected: "Do you think that just because you’re an unspecialized, you need every piece of equipment? That’s too much of a cheat!"